{"sentence": "Violent protests erupt in Caracas following controversial election results.", "tokens": ["Violent", "protests", "erupt", "in", "Caracas", "following", "controversial", "election", "results", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Caracas Mayor calls for increased security measures in the city center.", "tokens": ["Caracas", "Mayor", "calls", "for", "increased", "security", "measures", "in", "the", "city", "center", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Google for Education launches new online learning platform.", "tokens": ["Google", "for", "Education", "launches", "new", "online", "learning", "platform", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "New York City schools partner with Google for Education for digital learning initiative.", "tokens": ["New", "York", "City", "schools", "partner", "with", "Google", "for", "Education", "for", "digital", "learning", "initiative", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Teachers across the country utilize Google for Education tools for virtual classrooms.", "tokens": ["Teachers", "across", "the", "country", "utilize", "Google", "for", "Education", "tools", "for", "virtual", "classrooms", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Pandora Media announces partnership with Sony Music Entertainment.", "tokens": ["Pandora", "Media", "announces", "partnership", "with", "Sony", "Music", "Entertainment", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Sony Music to release new album in collaboration with a popular artist.", "tokens": ["Sony", "Music", "to", "release", "new", "album", "in", "collaboration", "with", "a", "popular", "artist", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Pandora Media's CEO discusses future plans for the company at annual conference.", "tokens": ["Pandora", "Media", "'", "s", "CEO", "discusses", "future", "plans", "for", "the", "company", "at", "annual", "conference", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Private Michael Jenkins awarded Purple Heart for heroism in battle.", "tokens": ["Private", "Michael", "Jenkins", "awarded", "Purple", "Heart", "for", "heroism", "in", "battle", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "New research shows alarming increase in carbon emissions from China.", "tokens": ["New", "research", "shows", "alarming", "increase", "in", "carbon", "emissions", "from", "China", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Apple Inc. announces launch of new iPhone model.", "tokens": ["Apple", "Inc", ".", "announces", "launch", "of", "new", "iPhone", "model", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Berlin police officer Samantha Brown honored for bravery.", "tokens": ["Berlin", "police", "officer", "Samantha", "Brown", "honored", "for", "bravery", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Massive protest in Berlin against government's new immigration policy.", "tokens": ["Massive", "protest", "in", "Berlin", "against", "government", "'", "s", "new", "immigration", "policy", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Officer Samantha Brown apprehends suspect in Berlin bank robbery.", "tokens": ["Officer", "Samantha", "Brown", "apprehends", "suspect", "in", "Berlin", "bank", "robbery", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The exhibition features a rare collection of Claude Monet's paintings.", "tokens": ["The", "exhibition", "features", "a", "rare", "collection", "of", "Claude", "Monet", "'", "s", "paintings", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The Claude Monet Museum in Giverny, France, reopens after renovations.", "tokens": ["The", "Claude", "Monet", "Museum", "in", "Giverny", ",", "France", ",", "reopens", "after", "renovations", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tech giant Apple launches new iPhone with improved camera and battery life.", "tokens": ["Tech", "giant", "Apple", "launches", "new", "iPhone", "with", "improved", "camera", "and", "battery", "life", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Stocks plunge as United Airlines announces 20,000 layoffs due to pandemic impact.", "tokens": ["Stocks", "plunge", "as", "United", "Airlines", "announces", "20", ",", "000", "layoffs", "due", "to", "pandemic", "impact", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Famous actress Jennifer Lawrence to star in new Netflix thriller.", "tokens": ["Famous", "actress", "Jennifer", "Lawrence", "to", "star", "in", "new", "Netflix", "thriller", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Kraft Heinz reports decrease in sales for the third quarter.", "tokens": ["Kraft", "Heinz", "reports", "decrease", "in", "sales", "for", "the", "third", "quarter", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Ina Garten's new cookbook becomes best-seller in the first week of release.", "tokens": ["Ina", "Garten", "'", "s", "new", "cookbook", "becomes", "best", "-", "seller", "in", "the", "first", "week", "of", "release", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Stocks of Kraft Heinz surge after announcement of new CEO.", "tokens": ["Stocks", "of", "Kraft", "Heinz", "surge", "after", "announcement", "of", "new", "CEO", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The Climate Action Network demands stronger measures to combat climate change.", "tokens": ["The", "Climate", "Action", "Network", "demands", "stronger", "measures", "to", "combat", "climate", "change", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Prince Charles delivers a speech on environmental conservation at the United Nations.", "tokens": ["Prince", "Charles", "delivers", "a", "speech", "on", "environmental", "conservation", "at", "the", "United", "Nations", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Members of the Climate Action Network protest outside of the White House.", "tokens": ["Members", "of", "the", "Climate", "Action", "Network", "protest", "outside", "of", "the", "White", "House", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Uber launches new feature to schedule rides in advance.", "tokens": ["Uber", "launches", "new", "feature", "to", "schedule", "rides", "in", "advance", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Uber driver charged with assault in New York City.", "tokens": ["Uber", "driver", "charged", "with", "assault", "in", "New", "York", "City", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Uber CEO resigns amidst controversy.", "tokens": ["Uber", "CEO", "resigns", "amidst", "controversy", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "B-person", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Michelle Obama delivers powerful speech at United Nations conference.", "tokens": ["Michelle", "Obama", "delivers", "powerful", "speech", "at", "United", "Nations", "conference", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Former First Lady Michelle Obama launches new initiative to promote girls' education.", "tokens": ["Former", "First", "Lady", "Michelle", "Obama", "launches", "new", "initiative", "to", "promote", "girls", "'", "education", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Michelle Obama visits children's hospital in Chicago to meet with young patients.", "tokens": ["Michelle", "Obama", "visits", "children", "'", "s", "hospital", "in", "Chicago", "to", "meet", "with", "young", "patients", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "BARCELONA - NEW MAYOR ELECTED AFTER CLOSE ELECTION.", "tokens": ["BARCELONA", "-", "NEW", "MAYOR", "ELECTED", "AFTER", "CLOSE", "ELECTION", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "RALPH LAUREN ANNOUNCES PLAN TO LAUNCH SUSTAINABLE FASHION LINE.", "tokens": ["RALPH", "LAUREN", "ANNOUNCES", "PLAN", "TO", "LAUNCH", "SUSTAINABLE", "FASHION", "LINE", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Barcelona FC hires new head coach from Argentina.", "tokens": ["Barcelona", "FC", "hires", "new", "head", "coach", "from", "Argentina", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Oxfam International releases report on global hunger crisis.", "tokens": ["Oxfam", "International", "releases", "report", "on", "global", "hunger", "crisis", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Aisha Khan appointed as ambassador to United Nations.", "tokens": ["Aisha", "Khan", "appointed", "as", "ambassador", "to", "United", "Nations", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O"]}
{"sentence": "New Oxfam International CEO vows to tackle inequality in third world countries.", "tokens": ["New", "Oxfam", "International", "CEO", "vows", "to", "tackle", "inequality", "in", "third", "world", "countries", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Samantha Miller appointed as the new spokesperson for the International Red Cross and Red Crescent Movement.", "tokens": ["Samantha", "Miller", "appointed", "as", "the", "new", "spokesperson", "for", "the", "International", "Red", "Cross", "and", "Red", "Crescent", "Movement", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Investigative report uncovers corruption within the International Red Cross and Red Crescent Movement leadership.", "tokens": ["Investigative", "report", "uncovers", "corruption", "within", "the", "International", "Red", "Cross", "and", "Red", "Crescent", "Movement", "leadership", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The Food and Agriculture Organization reports record crop yields in the Midwest.", "tokens": ["The", "Food", "and", "Agriculture", "Organization", "reports", "record", "crop", "yields", "in", "the", "Midwest", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The CEO of Apple Inc. announces new product release at tech conference.", "tokens": ["The", "CEO", "of", "Apple", "Inc", ".", "announces", "new", "product", "release", "at", "tech", "conference", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "China surpasses United States as world's largest importer of agricultural products, says Food and Agriculture Organization.", "tokens": ["China", "surpasses", "United", "States", "as", "world", "'", "s", "largest", "importer", "of", "agricultural", "products", ",", "says", "Food", "and", "Agriculture", "Organization", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Justin Bieber's new album breaks records.", "tokens": ["Justin", "Bieber", "'", "s", "new", "album", "breaks", "records", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Sony Pictures announces plans for new blockbuster movie.", "tokens": ["Sony", "Pictures", "announces", "plans", "for", "new", "blockbuster", "movie", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Justin Bieber's collaboration with Sony Pictures becomes a box office hit.", "tokens": ["Justin", "Bieber", "'", "s", "collaboration", "with", "Sony", "Pictures", "becomes", "a", "box", "office", "hit", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The Museum of Contemporary Art in Tokyo, Japan, is hosting a special exhibition on traditional Japanese pottery.", "tokens": ["The", "Museum", "of", "Contemporary", "Art", "in", "Tokyo", ",", "Japan", ",", "is", "hosting", "a", "special", "exhibition", "on", "traditional", "Japanese", "pottery", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "B-location", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The Royal Academy of Arts in London is planning to showcase a collection of works by renowned British artists.", "tokens": ["The", "Royal", "Academy", "of", "Arts", "in", "London", "is", "planning", "to", "showcase", "a", "collection", "of", "works", "by", "renowned", "British", "artists", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Refugee Council USA advocates for more funding for resettlement programs.", "tokens": ["Refugee", "Council", "USA", "advocates", "for", "more", "funding", "for", "resettlement", "programs", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Natasha Petrovna elected as the new head of the International Red Cross.", "tokens": ["Natasha", "Petrovna", "elected", "as", "the", "new", "head", "of", "the", "International", "Red", "Cross", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O"]}
{"sentence": "An earthquake hit the small town of Amalfi, Italy, causing widespread damage.", "tokens": ["An", "earthquake", "hit", "the", "small", "town", "of", "Amalfi", ",", "Italy", ",", "causing", "widespread", "damage", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Rescue team saves 10 climbers stranded in The Andes Mountains.", "tokens": ["Rescue", "team", "saves", "10", "climbers", "stranded", "in", "The", "Andes", "Mountains", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Cristiano Ronaldo scores a hat-trick in the semi-final match.", "tokens": ["Cristiano", "Ronaldo", "scores", "a", "hat", "-", "trick", "in", "the", "semi", "-", "final", "match", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The National Council of Teachers of English holds annual conference in Tokyo, Japan.", "tokens": ["The", "National", "Council", "of", "Teachers", "of", "English", "holds", "annual", "conference", "in", "Tokyo", ",", "Japan", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tokyo, Japan to host 2020 Summer Olympics.", "tokens": ["Tokyo", ",", "Japan", "to", "host", "2020", "Summer", "Olympics", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The National Council of Teachers of English celebrates its 100th anniversary with a special event in Tokyo, Japan.", "tokens": ["The", "National", "Council", "of", "Teachers", "of", "English", "celebrates", "its", "100th", "anniversary", "with", "a", "special", "event", "in", "Tokyo", ",", "Japan", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Local business owner, Anthony Nguyen, named Entrepreneur of the Year.", "tokens": ["Local", "business", "owner", ",", "Anthony", "Nguyen", ",", "named", "Entrepreneur", "of", "the", "Year", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Protests erupt in downtown Los Angeles over police shooting of Anthony Nguyen.", "tokens": ["Protests", "erupt", "in", "downtown", "Los", "Angeles", "over", "police", "shooting", "of", "Anthony", "Nguyen", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Anthony Nguyen Foundation donates $1 million to local hospital.", "tokens": ["Anthony", "Nguyen", "Foundation", "donates", "$", "1", "million", "to", "local", "hospital", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Warren Buffett's Berkshire Hathaway invests in Starbucks Corporation.", "tokens": ["Warren", "Buffett", "'", "s", "Berkshire", "Hathaway", "invests", "in", "Starbucks", "Corporation", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Starbucks Corporation opens new store in Shanghai.", "tokens": ["Starbucks", "Corporation", "opens", "new", "store", "in", "Shanghai", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Warren Buffett predicts economic downturn in the coming year.", "tokens": ["Warren", "Buffett", "predicts", "economic", "downturn", "in", "the", "coming", "year", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Earthwatch Institute partners with local communities to study the effects of climate change.", "tokens": ["Earthwatch", "Institute", "partners", "with", "local", "communities", "to", "study", "the", "effects", "of", "climate", "change", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The United Nations reports a 30% increase in deforestation in the Amazon rainforest.", "tokens": ["The", "United", "Nations", "reports", "a", "30", "%", "increase", "in", "deforestation", "in", "the", "Amazon", "rainforest", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Renowned physicist Stephen Hawking's theories on black holes continue to intrigue scientists around the world.", "tokens": ["Renowned", "physicist", "Stephen", "Hawking", "'", "s", "theories", "on", "black", "holes", "continue", "to", "intrigue", "scientists", "around", "the", "world", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Google co-founder Larry Page steps down as CEO of Alphabet", "tokens": ["Google", "co", "-", "founder", "Larry", "Page", "steps", "down", "as", "CEO", "of", "Alphabet"], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization"]}
{"sentence": "Larry Page donates millions to wildlife conservation efforts", "tokens": ["Larry", "Page", "donates", "millions", "to", "wildlife", "conservation", "efforts"], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Alphabet's Larry Page expresses support for climate change initiatives", "tokens": ["Alphabet", "'", "s", "Larry", "Page", "expresses", "support", "for", "climate", "change", "initiatives"], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Technology giant Apple announces record-breaking sales for the third quarter.", "tokens": ["Technology", "giant", "Apple", "announces", "record", "-", "breaking", "sales", "for", "the", "third", "quarter", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Renowned chef Jamie Oliver launches new cooking show on streaming platform.", "tokens": ["Renowned", "chef", "Jamie", "Oliver", "launches", "new", "cooking", "show", "on", "streaming", "platform", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Greenpeace protests the construction of a new oil pipeline in Alaska.", "tokens": ["Greenpeace", "protests", "the", "construction", "of", "a", "new", "oil", "pipeline", "in", "Alaska", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The United Way of Central Ohio raises over $1 million for local homeless shelters.", "tokens": ["The", "United", "Way", "of", "Central", "Ohio", "raises", "over", "$", "1", "million", "for", "local", "homeless", "shelters", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Berlin experiences record-breaking heat wave, with temperatures reaching 40 degrees Celsius.", "tokens": ["Berlin", "experiences", "record", "-", "breaking", "heat", "wave", ",", "with", "temperatures", "reaching", "40", "degrees", "Celsius", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tesla posts record-breaking profits in third quarter.", "tokens": ["Tesla", "posts", "record", "-", "breaking", "profits", "in", "third", "quarter", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "New York City mayor announces plan to tackle homelessness crisis.", "tokens": ["New", "York", "City", "mayor", "announces", "plan", "to", "tackle", "homelessness", "crisis", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Emmy-winning actress to star in upcoming blockbuster film.", "tokens": ["Emmy", "-", "winning", "actress", "to", "star", "in", "upcoming", "blockbuster", "film", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "I-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The European Union imposes new carbon emission regulations on automobile manufacturers.", "tokens": ["The", "European", "Union", "imposes", "new", "carbon", "emission", "regulations", "on", "automobile", "manufacturers", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Severe flooding in the Midwest prompts evacuation orders for thousands of residents.", "tokens": ["Severe", "flooding", "in", "the", "Midwest", "prompts", "evacuation", "orders", "for", "thousands", "of", "residents", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "TripAdvisor reveals the top 10 hotels in Europe for 2021.", "tokens": ["TripAdvisor", "reveals", "the", "top", "10", "hotels", "in", "Europe", "for", "2021", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Walt Disney World Resort announces new COVID-19 safety measures for guests.", "tokens": ["Walt", "Disney", "World", "Resort", "announces", "new", "COVID", "-", "19", "safety", "measures", "for", "guests", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Jennifer Lopez to perform at the Super Bowl halftime show.", "tokens": ["Jennifer", "Lopez", "to", "perform", "at", "the", "Super", "Bowl", "halftime", "show", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX successfully launches new satellite into orbit.", "tokens": ["Elon", "Musk", "'", "s", "SpaceX", "successfully", "launches", "new", "satellite", "into", "orbit", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "New York City Mayor announces plans for citywide clean energy initiative.", "tokens": ["New", "York", "City", "Mayor", "announces", "plans", "for", "citywide", "clean", "energy", "initiative", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "B-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Apple Inc. unveils latest iPhone model with enhanced features and capabilities.", "tokens": ["Apple", "Inc", ".", "unveils", "latest", "iPhone", "model", "with", "enhanced", "features", "and", "capabilities", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Taylor Swift performs surprise show at The Bluebird Cafe.", "tokens": ["Taylor", "Swift", "performs", "surprise", "show", "at", "The", "Bluebird", "Cafe", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The Bluebird Cafe in Nashville to host songwriter's night.", "tokens": ["The", "Bluebird", "Cafe", "in", "Nashville", "to", "host", "songwriter", "'", "s", "night", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "New documentary explores the history of The Bluebird Cafe.", "tokens": ["New", "documentary", "explores", "the", "history", "of", "The", "Bluebird", "Cafe", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Cape Town experiences record-breaking heat wave, with temperatures exceeding 40 degrees Celsius.", "tokens": ["Cape", "Town", "experiences", "record", "-", "breaking", "heat", "wave", ",", "with", "temperatures", "exceeding", "40", "degrees", "Celsius", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Local resident from Cape Town wins national award for community service.", "tokens": ["Local", "resident", "from", "Cape", "Town", "wins", "national", "award", "for", "community", "service", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Pentagon announces new military strategy in Indo-Pacific region.", "tokens": ["Pentagon", "announces", "new", "military", "strategy", "in", "Indo", "-", "Pacific", "region", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "General James Mattis faces criticism over military budget allocation.", "tokens": ["General", "James", "Mattis", "faces", "criticism", "over", "military", "budget", "allocation", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Local farmers at Smithfield Farmers' Market report record sales this season.", "tokens": ["Local", "farmers", "at", "Smithfield", "Farmers", "'", "Market", "report", "record", "sales", "this", "season", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Smithfield Farmers' Market to host annual Fall Festival next weekend.", "tokens": ["Smithfield", "Farmers", "'", "Market", "to", "host", "annual", "Fall", "Festival", "next", "weekend", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "New organic produce vendor joins Smithfield Farmers' Market lineup.", "tokens": ["New", "organic", "produce", "vendor", "joins", "Smithfield", "Farmers", "'", "Market", "lineup", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "China National Space Administration launches new satellite to study climate change.", "tokens": ["China", "National", "Space", "Administration", "launches", "new", "satellite", "to", "study", "climate", "change", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Sierra Nevada Corporation to supply NASA with cargo transportation services to the International Space Station.", "tokens": ["Sierra", "Nevada", "Corporation", "to", "supply", "NASA", "with", "cargo", "transportation", "services", "to", "the", "International", "Space", "Station", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Russian cosmonauts and Chinese astronauts conduct joint space mission.", "tokens": ["Russian", "cosmonauts", "and", "Chinese", "astronauts", "conduct", "joint", "space", "mission", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tesla announces plans to open new manufacturing plant in Texas.", "tokens": ["Tesla", "announces", "plans", "to", "open", "new", "manufacturing", "plant", "in", "Texas", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Michelle Obama to launch new initiative to promote education for girls.", "tokens": ["Michelle", "Obama", "to", "launch", "new", "initiative", "to", "promote", "education", "for", "girls", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "European Union imposes sanctions on Russian officials over Navalny poisoning.", "tokens": ["European", "Union", "imposes", "sanctions", "on", "Russian", "officials", "over", "Navalny", "poisoning", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "B-person", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The International Air Transport Association predicts a 26% drop in global passenger revenue.", "tokens": ["The", "International", "Air", "Transport", "Association", "predicts", "a", "26", "%", "drop", "in", "global", "passenger", "revenue", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "United Airlines announces the addition of new flights to Hawaii .", "tokens": ["United", "Airlines", "announces", "the", "addition", "of", "new", "flights", "to", "Hawaii", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The CEO of Boeing resigned following the company's recent safety scandals.", "tokens": ["The", "CEO", "of", "Boeing", "resigned", "following", "the", "company", "'", "s", "recent", "safety", "scandals", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "President Biden signs executive order to address climate change.", "tokens": ["President", "Biden", "signs", "executive", "order", "to", "address", "climate", "change", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "London Heathrow Airport sees 70% decrease in passenger numbers.", "tokens": ["London", "Heathrow", "Airport", "sees", "70", "%", "decrease", "in", "passenger", "numbers", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Apple announces new iPhone release date.", "tokens": ["Apple", "announces", "new", "iPhone", "release", "date", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The CEO of Apple, Sarah Johnson, announces the launch of a new line of iPhones.", "tokens": ["The", "CEO", "of", "Apple", ",", "Sarah", "Johnson", ",", "announces", "the", "launch", "of", "a", "new", "line", "of", "iPhones", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The United Nations reports progress in peace negotiations in the Middle East, with Secretary-General Sarah Johnson overseeing the talks.", "tokens": ["The", "United", "Nations", "reports", "progress", "in", "peace", "negotiations", "in", "the", "Middle", "East", ",", "with", "Secretary", "-", "General", "Sarah", "Johnson", "overseeing", "the", "talks", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Donatella Versace to open new flagship store in The Dubai Mall.", "tokens": ["Donatella", "Versace", "to", "open", "new", "flagship", "store", "in", "The", "Dubai", "Mall", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Annual fashion show to feature prominent designers including Donatella Versace.", "tokens": ["Annual", "fashion", "show", "to", "feature", "prominent", "designers", "including", "Donatella", "Versace", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The Dubai Mall announces expansion plans to accommodate more luxury retailers.", "tokens": ["The", "Dubai", "Mall", "announces", "expansion", "plans", "to", "accommodate", "more", "luxury", "retailers", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Sarah Khan appointed as the new CEO of a major tech company.", "tokens": ["Sarah", "Khan", "appointed", "as", "the", "new", "CEO", "of", "a", "major", "tech", "company", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Cape Town braces for severe drought as water levels continue to drop.", "tokens": ["Cape", "Town", "braces", "for", "severe", "drought", "as", "water", "levels", "continue", "to", "drop", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "UN Intergovernmental Panel on Climate Change releases new report on rising sea levels.", "tokens": ["UN", "Intergovernmental", "Panel", "on", "Climate", "Change", "releases", "new", "report", "on", "rising", "sea", "levels", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Dr. David Lee appointed as head of department at prestigious medical research institute.", "tokens": ["Dr", ".", "David", "Lee", "appointed", "as", "head", "of", "department", "at", "prestigious", "medical", "research", "institute", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "I-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tech giant Apple unveils new iPhone 13.", "tokens": ["Tech", "giant", "Apple", "unveils", "new", "iPhone", "13", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Paris Hilton launches new fragrance line.", "tokens": ["Paris", "Hilton", "launches", "new", "fragrance", "line", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Protesters gather outside United Nations headquarters in New York.", "tokens": ["Protesters", "gather", "outside", "United", "Nations", "headquarters", "in", "New", "York", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "United Nations Security Council to discuss ceasefire in Syria at emergency meeting.", "tokens": ["United", "Nations", "Security", "Council", "to", "discuss", "ceasefire", "in", "Syria", "at", "emergency", "meeting", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tesla reports record-breaking sales in the second quarter.", "tokens": ["Tesla", "reports", "record", "-", "breaking", "sales", "in", "the", "second", "quarter", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tim Cook announces plans to expand Apple's presence in China.", "tokens": ["Tim", "Cook", "announces", "plans", "to", "expand", "Apple", "'", "s", "presence", "in", "China", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Stocks on the Frankfurt Stock Exchange plunge after new trade tariffs are announced.", "tokens": ["Stocks", "on", "the", "Frankfurt", "Stock", "Exchange", "plunge", "after", "new", "trade", "tariffs", "are", "announced", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Frankfurt Stock Exchange hits record high as tech companies continue to thrive.", "tokens": ["Frankfurt", "Stock", "Exchange", "hits", "record", "high", "as", "tech", "companies", "continue", "to", "thrive", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Starbucks partners with Rainforest Alliance to promote sustainable farming practices.", "tokens": ["Starbucks", "partners", "with", "Rainforest", "Alliance", "to", "promote", "sustainable", "farming", "practices", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Rainforest Alliance releases new report on deforestation in the Amazon.", "tokens": ["Rainforest", "Alliance", "releases", "new", "report", "on", "deforestation", "in", "the", "Amazon", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Climate change threatens the future of Rainforest Alliance certified coffee farms.", "tokens": ["Climate", "change", "threatens", "the", "future", "of", "Rainforest", "Alliance", "certified", "coffee", "farms", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tesla announces plans to open new manufacturing facility in Austin, Texas.", "tokens": ["Tesla", "announces", "plans", "to", "open", "new", "manufacturing", "facility", "in", "Austin", ",", "Texas", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "United Nations reports increase in humanitarian aid to war-torn regions.", "tokens": ["United", "Nations", "reports", "increase", "in", "humanitarian", "aid", "to", "war", "-", "torn", "regions", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Jerusalem's Old City sees increase in tourism after easing of COVID-19 restrictions.", "tokens": ["Jerusalem", "'", "s", "Old", "City", "sees", "increase", "in", "tourism", "after", "easing", "of", "COVID", "-", "19", "restrictions", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Israel's Ministry of Health announces new vaccine mandate for all healthcare workers in Jerusalem.", "tokens": ["Israel", "'", "s", "Ministry", "of", "Health", "announces", "new", "vaccine", "mandate", "for", "all", "healthcare", "workers", "in", "Jerusalem", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Apple Inc. announces plans to open new manufacturing plant in Texas.", "tokens": ["Apple", "Inc", ".", "announces", "plans", "to", "open", "new", "manufacturing", "plant", "in", "Texas", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "CEO of SpaceX, Elon Musk, announces ambitious plan to colonize Mars within the next decade.", "tokens": ["CEO", "of", "SpaceX", ",", "Elon", "Musk", ",", "announces", "ambitious", "plan", "to", "colonize", "Mars", "within", "the", "next", "decade", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Climate change activists protest outside United Nations headquarters in New York City.", "tokens": ["Climate", "change", "activists", "protest", "outside", "United", "Nations", "headquarters", "in", "New", "York", "City", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Immigrant Legal Resource Center files lawsuit against the Department of Homeland Security over new immigration policy.", "tokens": ["Immigrant", "Legal", "Resource", "Center", "files", "lawsuit", "against", "the", "Department", "of", "Homeland", "Security", "over", "new", "immigration", "policy", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "ICE raids target employers hiring unauthorized workers.", "tokens": ["ICE", "raids", "target", "employers", "hiring", "unauthorized", "workers", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Renowned author and poet Maya Angelou to be honored with new stamp.", "tokens": ["Renowned", "author", "and", "poet", "Maya", "Angelou", "to", "be", "honored", "with", "new", "stamp", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Maya Angelou's autobiography 'I Know Why the Caged Bird Sings' to be adapted into a stage play.", "tokens": ["Maya", "Angelou", "'", "s", "autobiography", "'", "I", "Know", "Why", "the", "Caged", "Bird", "Sings", "'", "to", "be", "adapted", "into", "a", "stage", "play", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Maya Angelou's legacy celebrated on what would have been her 90th birthday.", "tokens": ["Maya", "Angelou", "'", "s", "legacy", "celebrated", "on", "what", "would", "have", "been", "her", "90th", "birthday", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Patrick Mahomes signs 10-year contract extension with Kansas City Chiefs.", "tokens": ["Patrick", "Mahomes", "signs", "10", "-", "year", "contract", "extension", "with", "Kansas", "City", "Chiefs", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Megan Rapinoe becomes first openly gay woman to appear in Sports Illustrated swimsuit issue.", "tokens": ["Megan", "Rapinoe", "becomes", "first", "openly", "gay", "woman", "to", "appear", "in", "Sports", "Illustrated", "swimsuit", "issue", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Patrick Mahomes leads Kansas City Chiefs to Super Bowl victory.", "tokens": ["Patrick", "Mahomes", "leads", "Kansas", "City", "Chiefs", "to", "Super", "Bowl", "victory", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Sydney experiences record-breaking heatwave.", "tokens": ["Sydney", "experiences", "record", "-", "breaking", "heatwave", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "New study shows Sydney's air pollution levels remain dangerously high.", "tokens": ["New", "study", "shows", "Sydney", "'", "s", "air", "pollution", "levels", "remain", "dangerously", "high", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tesla surpasses expectations, reaching new record high in stock market.", "tokens": ["Tesla", "surpasses", "expectations", ",", "reaching", "new", "record", "high", "in", "stock", "market", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tokyo Olympics officially postponed to 2021.", "tokens": ["Tokyo", "Olympics", "officially", "postponed", "to", "2021", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Dr. Anthony Fauci warns of potential 'resurgence' of COVID-19 in the fall.", "tokens": ["Dr", ".", "Anthony", "Fauci", "warns", "of", "potential", "'", "resurgence", "'", "of", "COVID", "-", "19", "in", "the", "fall", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "I-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Amsterdam implements new bike lanes to promote safer commuting for cyclists.", "tokens": ["Amsterdam", "implements", "new", "bike", "lanes", "to", "promote", "safer", "commuting", "for", "cyclists", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "New report from The Intergovernmental Panel on Climate Change warns of dire consequences if global temperatures continue to rise.", "tokens": ["New", "report", "from", "The", "Intergovernmental", "Panel", "on", "Climate", "Change", "warns", "of", "dire", "consequences", "if", "global", "temperatures", "continue", "to", "rise", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The United Nations Secretary-General praises The Intergovernmental Panel on Climate Change for its groundbreaking research on climate change.", "tokens": ["The", "United", "Nations", "Secretary", "-", "General", "praises", "The", "Intergovernmental", "Panel", "on", "Climate", "Change", "for", "its", "groundbreaking", "research", "on", "climate", "change", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-person", "I-person", "I-person", "I-person", "I-person", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The Intergovernmental Panel on Climate Change calls for immediate action to mitigate the impact of climate change on vulnerable communities.", "tokens": ["The", "Intergovernmental", "Panel", "on", "Climate", "Change", "calls", "for", "immediate", "action", "to", "mitigate", "the", "impact", "of", "climate", "change", "on", "vulnerable", "communities", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Johnson Elementary School wins first place in national chess tournament.", "tokens": ["Johnson", "Elementary", "School", "wins", "first", "place", "in", "national", "chess", "tournament", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Three students from Johnson Elementary School to represent their state in the National Science Fair.", "tokens": ["Three", "students", "from", "Johnson", "Elementary", "School", "to", "represent", "their", "state", "in", "the", "National", "Science", "Fair", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Local community rallies behind Johnson Elementary School after devastating fire.", "tokens": ["Local", "community", "rallies", "behind", "Johnson", "Elementary", "School", "after", "devastating", "fire", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Record-breaking heatwave hits Los Angeles.", "tokens": ["Record", "-", "breaking", "heatwave", "hits", "Los", "Angeles", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Los Angeles Mayor announces new funding for homeless shelters.", "tokens": ["Los", "Angeles", "Mayor", "announces", "new", "funding", "for", "homeless", "shelters", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "I-location", "B-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "J.K. Rowling's new book release date revealed", "tokens": ["J", ".", "K", ".", "Rowling", "'", "s", "new", "book", "release", "date", "revealed"], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "I-person", "I-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Banksy's latest artwork discovered in London", "tokens": ["Banksy", "'", "s", "latest", "artwork", "discovered", "in", "London"], "labels": ["B-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location"]}
{"sentence": "Local school receives donation from J.K. Rowling", "tokens": ["Local", "school", "receives", "donation", "from", "J", ".", "K", ".", "Rowling"], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "I-person", "I-person", "I-person"]}
{"sentence": "Mondelez International announces partnership with local farmers to promote sustainable cocoa production.", "tokens": ["Mondelez", "International", "announces", "partnership", "with", "local", "farmers", "to", "promote", "sustainable", "cocoa", "production", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Unilever acquires snack brands from Mondelez International for $2.7 billion.", "tokens": ["Unilever", "acquires", "snack", "brands", "from", "Mondelez", "International", "for", "$", "2", ".", "7", "billion", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Kraft Heinz reports increase in sales, surpassing analyst expectations for the quarter.", "tokens": ["Kraft", "Heinz", "reports", "increase", "in", "sales", ",", "surpassing", "analyst", "expectations", "for", "the", "quarter", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Pope Francis visits Vatican City to address climate change.", "tokens": ["Pope", "Francis", "visits", "Vatican", "City", "to", "address", "climate", "change", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "World Health Organization declares new COVID-19 variant a global concern.", "tokens": ["World", "Health", "Organization", "declares", "new", "COVID", "-", "19", "variant", "a", "global", "concern", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Firefighters battle massive wildfire in California.", "tokens": ["Firefighters", "battle", "massive", "wildfire", "in", "California", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "CDC warns of potential new COVID-19 variant.", "tokens": ["CDC", "warns", "of", "potential", "new", "COVID", "-", "19", "variant", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Celebrity chef Guy Fieri to open new restaurant in New York City.", "tokens": ["Celebrity", "chef", "Guy", "Fieri", "to", "open", "new", "restaurant", "in", "New", "York", "City", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Food Network star Guy Fieri launches his own line of barbecue sauce.", "tokens": ["Food", "Network", "star", "Guy", "Fieri", "launches", "his", "own", "line", "of", "barbecue", "sauce", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Guy Fieri's cooking show 'Diners, Drive-Ins and Dives' renewed for another season.", "tokens": ["Guy", "Fieri", "'", "s", "cooking", "show", "'", "Diners", ",", "Drive", "-", "Ins", "and", "Dives", "'", "renewed", "for", "another", "season", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Severe bushfires in Australia prompt warnings from the Australian Bureau of Meteorology.", "tokens": ["Severe", "bushfires", "in", "Australia", "prompt", "warnings", "from", "the", "Australian", "Bureau", "of", "Meteorology", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Australian Bureau of Meteorology predicts record-breaking heatwave across the country.", "tokens": ["Australian", "Bureau", "of", "Meteorology", "predicts", "record", "-", "breaking", "heatwave", "across", "the", "country", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Heatwave in Sydney reaches new highs, according to data from the Australian Bureau of Meteorology.", "tokens": ["Heatwave", "in", "Sydney", "reaches", "new", "highs", ",", "according", "to", "data", "from", "the", "Australian", "Bureau", "of", "Meteorology", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Israel reopens its borders to vaccinated tourists.", "tokens": ["Israel", "reopens", "its", "borders", "to", "vaccinated", "tourists", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The Australian government announces new funding for Canberra infrastructure projects.", "tokens": ["The", "Australian", "government", "announces", "new", "funding", "for", "Canberra", "infrastructure", "projects", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Coach Rachel Turner leads her team to victory in the championship game.", "tokens": ["Coach", "Rachel", "Turner", "leads", "her", "team", "to", "victory", "in", "the", "championship", "game", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Pope Francis visits Mexico to address issues of poverty and immigration.", "tokens": ["Pope", "Francis", "visits", "Mexico", "to", "address", "issues", "of", "poverty", "and", "immigration", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Thousands flock to Niagara Falls for the annual fireworks display on July 4th.", "tokens": ["Thousands", "flock", "to", "Niagara", "Falls", "for", "the", "annual", "fireworks", "display", "on", "July", "4th", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "New species of endangered monkey discovered in Sundarbans National Park.", "tokens": ["New", "species", "of", "endangered", "monkey", "discovered", "in", "Sundarbans", "National", "Park", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Government allocates funding for infrastructure development in Sundarbans National Park.", "tokens": ["Government", "allocates", "funding", "for", "infrastructure", "development", "in", "Sundarbans", "National", "Park", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Environmental group protest proposed industrial development near Sundarbans National Park.", "tokens": ["Environmental", "group", "protest", "proposed", "industrial", "development", "near", "Sundarbans", "National", "Park", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Fashion icon Iris Apfel launches new line of eyewear.", "tokens": ["Fashion", "icon", "Iris", "Apfel", "launches", "new", "line", "of", "eyewear", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Janet Mock makes history as the first trans woman of color to direct a TV series.", "tokens": ["Janet", "Mock", "makes", "history", "as", "the", "first", "trans", "woman", "of", "color", "to", "direct", "a", "TV", "series", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Munroe Bergdorf appointed as the new diversity consultant for the fashion brand.", "tokens": ["Munroe", "Bergdorf", "appointed", "as", "the", "new", "diversity", "consultant", "for", "the", "fashion", "brand", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The annual LGBTQ+ parade in San Francisco draws thousands of participants.", "tokens": ["The", "annual", "LGBTQ", "+", "parade", "in", "San", "Francisco", "draws", "thousands", "of", "participants", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "PFLAG releases new educational resources for LGBTQ+ youth and families.", "tokens": ["PFLAG", "releases", "new", "educational", "resources", "for", "LGBTQ", "+", "youth", "and", "families", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Local PFLAG chapter to host virtual support group for parents of transgender children.", "tokens": ["Local", "PFLAG", "chapter", "to", "host", "virtual", "support", "group", "for", "parents", "of", "transgender", "children", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "PFLAG advocates for LGBTQ+ rights in upcoming city council meeting.", "tokens": ["PFLAG", "advocates", "for", "LGBTQ", "+", "rights", "in", "upcoming", "city", "council", "meeting", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "German Chancellor Angela Merkel meets with French President Emmanuel Macron to discuss EU economic reforms.", "tokens": ["German", "Chancellor", "Angela", "Merkel", "meets", "with", "French", "President", "Emmanuel", "Macron", "to", "discuss", "EU", "economic", "reforms", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Angela Merkel announces plan to invest €130 billion in renewable energy infrastructure.", "tokens": ["Angela", "Merkel", "announces", "plan", "to", "invest", "€", "130", "billion", "in", "renewable", "energy", "infrastructure", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Angela Merkel's conservative CDU party loses ground in local elections.", "tokens": ["Angela", "Merkel", "'", "s", "conservative", "CDU", "party", "loses", "ground", "in", "local", "elections", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Atheist Alliance International condemns Archbishop Justin Welby's comments on atheism.", "tokens": ["Atheist", "Alliance", "International", "condemns", "Archbishop", "Justin", "Welby", "'", "s", "comments", "on", "atheism", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Archbishop Justin Welby meets with leaders of Atheist Alliance International to discuss religious tolerance.", "tokens": ["Archbishop", "Justin", "Welby", "meets", "with", "leaders", "of", "Atheist", "Alliance", "International", "to", "discuss", "religious", "tolerance", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Atheist Alliance International launches new campaign to promote secularism in schools with Archbishop Justin Welby's support.", "tokens": ["Atheist", "Alliance", "International", "launches", "new", "campaign", "to", "promote", "secularism", "in", "schools", "with", "Archbishop", "Justin", "Welby", "'", "s", "support", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Marissa Mayer appointed as the new CEO of a major tech company.", "tokens": ["Marissa", "Mayer", "appointed", "as", "the", "new", "CEO", "of", "a", "major", "tech", "company", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Amazon.com, Inc. launches new subscription service for prime members.", "tokens": ["Amazon", ".", "com", ",", "Inc", ".", "launches", "new", "subscription", "service", "for", "prime", "members", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Elon Musk announces plans for new space exploration project.", "tokens": ["Elon", "Musk", "announces", "plans", "for", "new", "space", "exploration", "project", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Kim Kardashian launches new beauty line.", "tokens": ["Kim", "Kardashian", "launches", "new", "beauty", "line", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Major earthquake hits Los Angeles, causing widespread damage.", "tokens": ["Major", "earthquake", "hits", "Los", "Angeles", ",", "causing", "widespread", "damage", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Golden State Warriors defeat Houston Rockets in thrilling overtime game.", "tokens": ["Golden", "State", "Warriors", "defeat", "Houston", "Rockets", "in", "thrilling", "overtime", "game", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Emily Rodriguez appointed as new chief executive officer of Chicago-based tech company.", "tokens": ["Emily", "Rodriguez", "appointed", "as", "new", "chief", "executive", "officer", "of", "Chicago", "-", "based", "tech", "company", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Chicago mayor announces plans to invest in infrastructure improvements.", "tokens": ["Chicago", "mayor", "announces", "plans", "to", "invest", "in", "infrastructure", "improvements", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Emily Rodriguez awarded prestigious business award for leadership in Chicago community.", "tokens": ["Emily", "Rodriguez", "awarded", "prestigious", "business", "award", "for", "leadership", "in", "Chicago", "community", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tom Cruise to receive special award from British Academy of Film and Television Arts (BAFTA) for outstanding contribution to film.", "tokens": ["Tom", "Cruise", "to", "receive", "special", "award", "from", "British", "Academy", "of", "Film", "and", "Television", "Arts", "(", "BAFTA", ")", "for", "outstanding", "contribution", "to", "film", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "British Academy of Film and Television Arts (BAFTA) announces nominations for upcoming awards ceremony.", "tokens": ["British", "Academy", "of", "Film", "and", "Television", "Arts", "(", "BAFTA", ")", "announces", "nominations", "for", "upcoming", "awards", "ceremony", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tom Cruise's latest film tops box office over the weekend.", "tokens": ["Tom", "Cruise", "'", "s", "latest", "film", "tops", "box", "office", "over", "the", "weekend", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Chaz Bono to star in new reality TV show.", "tokens": ["Chaz", "Bono", "to", "star", "in", "new", "reality", "TV", "show", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Rio de Janeiro celebrates Carnival with colorful parades and lively music.", "tokens": ["Rio", "de", "Janeiro", "celebrates", "Carnival", "with", "colorful", "parades", "and", "lively", "music", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Brazil announces plan to combat deforestation in the Amazon rainforest.", "tokens": ["Brazil", "announces", "plan", "to", "combat", "deforestation", "in", "the", "Amazon", "rainforest", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Rio de Janeiro to host 2024 Summer Olympics.", "tokens": ["Rio", "de", "Janeiro", "to", "host", "2024", "Summer", "Olympics", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Red Rocks Amphitheatre to welcome famous music artists for summer concert series.", "tokens": ["Red", "Rocks", "Amphitheatre", "to", "welcome", "famous", "music", "artists", "for", "summer", "concert", "series", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Greta Thunberg announces new climate change initiative.", "tokens": ["Greta", "Thunberg", "announces", "new", "climate", "change", "initiative", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "David Brown appointed as CEO of tech startup.", "tokens": ["David", "Brown", "appointed", "as", "CEO", "of", "tech", "startup", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Boris Johnson announces new environmental regulations.", "tokens": ["Boris", "Johnson", "announces", "new", "environmental", "regulations", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Protests erupt in London following Boris Johnson's controversial remarks.", "tokens": ["Protests", "erupt", "in", "London", "following", "Boris", "Johnson", "'", "s", "controversial", "remarks", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Boris Johnson meets with European Union leaders to discuss trade agreements.", "tokens": ["Boris", "Johnson", "meets", "with", "European", "Union", "leaders", "to", "discuss", "trade", "agreements", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Lieutenant Colonel Mark Thompson resigns from his position as head of the military defense division.", "tokens": ["Lieutenant", "Colonel", "Mark", "Thompson", "resigns", "from", "his", "position", "as", "head", "of", "the", "military", "defense", "division", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "I-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Investigations into the financial scandal at ABC Corporation reveal shocking details.", "tokens": ["Investigations", "into", "the", "financial", "scandal", "at", "ABC", "Corporation", "reveal", "shocking", "details", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Protests erupt in downtown New York City over police brutality.", "tokens": ["Protests", "erupt", "in", "downtown", "New", "York", "City", "over", "police", "brutality", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Sydney Opera House announces lineup for summer concert series.", "tokens": ["Sydney", "Opera", "House", "announces", "lineup", "for", "summer", "concert", "series", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Investigation reveals ties between mayor's office and local construction company.", "tokens": ["Investigation", "reveals", "ties", "between", "mayor", "'", "s", "office", "and", "local", "construction", "company", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Teenage climate activist speaks at United Nations summit in New York.", "tokens": ["Teenage", "climate", "activist", "speaks", "at", "United", "Nations", "summit", "in", "New", "York", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Oxford University announces plans to open new research facility in London.", "tokens": ["Oxford", "University", "announces", "plans", "to", "open", "new", "research", "facility", "in", "London", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Jennifer Lopez to make guest appearance on popular TV show.", "tokens": ["Jennifer", "Lopez", "to", "make", "guest", "appearance", "on", "popular", "TV", "show", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The latest production of Shakespeare's Hamlet received rave reviews from theater critics.", "tokens": ["The", "latest", "production", "of", "Shakespeare", "'", "s", "Hamlet", "received", "rave", "reviews", "from", "theater", "critics", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The new Shakespeare exhibition at the British Museum is drawing large crowds of tourists.", "tokens": ["The", "new", "Shakespeare", "exhibition", "at", "the", "British", "Museum", "is", "drawing", "large", "crowds", "of", "tourists", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-person", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Stratford-upon-Avon, the birthplace of Shakespeare, is a popular destination for literary enthusiasts.", "tokens": ["Stratford", "-", "upon", "-", "Avon", ",", "the", "birthplace", "of", "Shakespeare", ",", "is", "a", "popular", "destination", "for", "literary", "enthusiasts", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Moscow announces plan to improve public transportation infrastructure.", "tokens": ["Moscow", "announces", "plan", "to", "improve", "public", "transportation", "infrastructure", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Elizabeth Warren proposes new legislation to address student loan debt.", "tokens": ["Elizabeth", "Warren", "proposes", "new", "legislation", "to", "address", "student", "loan", "debt", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Russia imposes sanctions on Western countries in response to diplomatic tensions.", "tokens": ["Russia", "imposes", "sanctions", "on", "Western", "countries", "in", "response", "to", "diplomatic", "tensions", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "New discovery of ancient artifacts near Giza pyramid complex.", "tokens": ["New", "discovery", "of", "ancient", "artifacts", "near", "Giza", "pyramid", "complex", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Google launches new privacy feature for email users.", "tokens": ["Google", "launches", "new", "privacy", "feature", "for", "email", "users", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Local residents protest proposed construction of new Google headquarters.", "tokens": ["Local", "residents", "protest", "proposed", "construction", "of", "new", "Google", "headquarters", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Dwayne \"The Rock\" Johnson announces new partnership with fitness brand.", "tokens": ["Dwayne", "\"", "The", "Rock", "\"", "Johnson", "announces", "new", "partnership", "with", "fitness", "brand", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "I-person", "I-person", "I-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O"]}
{"sentence": "New York City reports record-high temperatures for the month of July.", "tokens": ["New", "York", "City", "reports", "record", "-", "high", "temperatures", "for", "the", "month", "of", "July", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tesla's CEO Elon Musk unveils plans for new electric vehicle model.", "tokens": ["Tesla", "'", "s", "CEO", "Elon", "Musk", "unveils", "plans", "for", "new", "electric", "vehicle", "model", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tech giant Apple Inc. launches new iPhone model.", "tokens": ["Tech", "giant", "Apple", "Inc", ".", "launches", "new", "iPhone", "model", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Local artist John Smith to exhibit new work at gallery next month.", "tokens": ["Local", "artist", "John", "Smith", "to", "exhibit", "new", "work", "at", "gallery", "next", "month", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "National Park Service to implement new conservation measures in Everglades National Park, USA.", "tokens": ["National", "Park", "Service", "to", "implement", "new", "conservation", "measures", "in", "Everglades", "National", "Park", ",", "USA", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Renowned environmentalist to speak at Everglades National Park, USA Earth Day event.", "tokens": ["Renowned", "environmentalist", "to", "speak", "at", "Everglades", "National", "Park", ",", "USA", "Earth", "Day", "event", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Federal funding approved for restoration project in Everglades National Park, USA.", "tokens": ["Federal", "funding", "approved", "for", "restoration", "project", "in", "Everglades", "National", "Park", ",", "USA", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Brie Larson wins Best Actress at the Atlanta Film Festival.", "tokens": ["Brie", "Larson", "wins", "Best", "Actress", "at", "the", "Atlanta", "Film", "Festival", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Berlin Marathon postponed due to COVID-19 pandemic.", "tokens": ["Berlin", "Marathon", "postponed", "due", "to", "COVID", "-", "19", "pandemic", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Best-selling author Chinua Achebe passes away at 82.", "tokens": ["Best", "-", "selling", "author", "Chinua", "Achebe", "passes", "away", "at", "82", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "J.K. Rowling's new book tops the bestseller list.", "tokens": ["J", ".", "K", ".", "Rowling", "'", "s", "new", "book", "tops", "the", "bestseller", "list", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "I-person", "I-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Philanthropist donates $1 million to local children's hospital.", "tokens": ["Philanthropist", "donates", "$", "1", "million", "to", "local", "children", "'", "s", "hospital", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "United States Department of Defense announces new cybersecurity initiative.", "tokens": ["United", "States", "Department", "of", "Defense", "announces", "new", "cybersecurity", "initiative", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "California wildfires force thousands to evacuate.", "tokens": ["California", "wildfires", "force", "thousands", "to", "evacuate", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Famous actor Tom Hanks to star in new World War II film.", "tokens": ["Famous", "actor", "Tom", "Hanks", "to", "star", "in", "new", "World", "War", "II", "film", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Los Angeles mayor announces new traffic control measures.", "tokens": ["Los", "Angeles", "mayor", "announces", "new", "traffic", "control", "measures", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "I-location", "B-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The Los Angeles Lakers will face the Golden State Warriors in their next game.", "tokens": ["The", "Los", "Angeles", "Lakers", "will", "face", "the", "Golden", "State", "Warriors", "in", "their", "next", "game", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-location", "I-location", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Heavy rain causes flooding in Los Angeles area.", "tokens": ["Heavy", "rain", "causes", "flooding", "in", "Los", "Angeles", "area", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The United Nations releases new report on global climate change.", "tokens": ["The", "United", "Nations", "releases", "new", "report", "on", "global", "climate", "change", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX plans to launch a new satellite into orbit next week.", "tokens": ["Elon", "Musk", "'", "s", "SpaceX", "plans", "to", "launch", "a", "new", "satellite", "into", "orbit", "next", "week", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "London Mayor announces plan to reduce air pollution in the city center.", "tokens": ["London", "Mayor", "announces", "plan", "to", "reduce", "air", "pollution", "in", "the", "city", "center", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "B-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Moscow mayor announces new public transportation initiatives.", "tokens": ["Moscow", "mayor", "announces", "new", "public", "transportation", "initiatives", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Top chef Fatima Ali launches new cooking show.", "tokens": ["Top", "chef", "Fatima", "Ali", "launches", "new", "cooking", "show", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Jews for Jesus celebrates 40 years of ministry.", "tokens": ["Jews", "for", "Jesus", "celebrates", "40", "years", "of", "ministry", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "New York City to host annual Jews for Jesus conference.", "tokens": ["New", "York", "City", "to", "host", "annual", "Jews", "for", "Jesus", "conference", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Former member of Jews for Jesus speaks out against the organization.", "tokens": ["Former", "member", "of", "Jews", "for", "Jesus", "speaks", "out", "against", "the", "organization", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Local high school to host It Gets Better Project assembly", "tokens": ["Local", "high", "school", "to", "host", "It", "Gets", "Better", "Project", "assembly"], "labels": ["O", "B-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O"]}
{"sentence": "ISRO launches new satellite into orbit around Venus.", "tokens": ["ISRO", "launches", "new", "satellite", "into", "orbit", "around", "Venus", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Rocket Lab successfully tests new reusable rocket technology.", "tokens": ["Rocket", "Lab", "successfully", "tests", "new", "reusable", "rocket", "technology", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Scientists discover possible signs of life on Venus.", "tokens": ["Scientists", "discover", "possible", "signs", "of", "life", "on", "Venus", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Heavy rainfall causes flooding and road closures in Coventry, England.", "tokens": ["Heavy", "rainfall", "causes", "flooding", "and", "road", "closures", "in", "Coventry", ",", "England", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Coventry City Council adopts new environmental sustainability initiative.", "tokens": ["Coventry", "City", "Council", "adopts", "new", "environmental", "sustainability", "initiative", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Local musician from Coventry, England, to perform at upcoming music festival.", "tokens": ["Local", "musician", "from", "Coventry", ",", "England", ",", "to", "perform", "at", "upcoming", "music", "festival", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tech giant Apple announces the launch of new iPhone models.", "tokens": ["Tech", "giant", "Apple", "announces", "the", "launch", "of", "new", "iPhone", "models", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Senator Harris to visit Texas to discuss immigration reform.", "tokens": ["Senator", "Harris", "to", "visit", "Texas", "to", "discuss", "immigration", "reform", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "EU imposes sanctions on Russian officials over human rights violations.", "tokens": ["EU", "imposes", "sanctions", "on", "Russian", "officials", "over", "human", "rights", "violations", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The National Black Justice Coalition condemns the recent hate crime in Atlanta.", "tokens": ["The", "National", "Black", "Justice", "Coalition", "condemns", "the", "recent", "hate", "crime", "in", "Atlanta", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The Association of LGBTQ Journalists announces new scholarship program for aspiring writers.", "tokens": ["The", "Association", "of", "LGBTQ", "Journalists", "announces", "new", "scholarship", "program", "for", "aspiring", "writers", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Two transgender women elected to local government positions in California.", "tokens": ["Two", "transgender", "women", "elected", "to", "local", "government", "positions", "in", "California", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX Successfully Launches Crewed Mission to International Space Station.", "tokens": ["Elon", "Musk", "'", "s", "SpaceX", "Successfully", "Launches", "Crewed", "Mission", "to", "International", "Space", "Station", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "New York City to Invest $10 Billion in Infrastructure Projects Over Next 5 Years.", "tokens": ["New", "York", "City", "to", "Invest", "$", "10", "Billion", "in", "Infrastructure", "Projects", "Over", "Next", "5", "Years", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Apple Inc. Announces Plan to Open 20 New Retail Stores in China.", "tokens": ["Apple", "Inc", ".", "Announces", "Plan", "to", "Open", "20", "New", "Retail", "Stores", "in", "China", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX launches successful satellite into orbit.", "tokens": ["Elon", "Musk", "'", "s", "SpaceX", "launches", "successful", "satellite", "into", "orbit", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Forest fires rage through Northern California, causing widespread destruction.", "tokens": ["Forest", "fires", "rage", "through", "Northern", "California", ",", "causing", "widespread", "destruction", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Microsoft to acquire leading cybersecurity firm in multi-billion dollar deal.", "tokens": ["Microsoft", "to", "acquire", "leading", "cybersecurity", "firm", "in", "multi", "-", "billion", "dollar", "deal", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Royal Caribbean International offers 30% discount on select cruises.", "tokens": ["Royal", "Caribbean", "International", "offers", "30", "%", "discount", "on", "select", "cruises", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "New CEO appointed at Royal Caribbean International.", "tokens": ["New", "CEO", "appointed", "at", "Royal", "Caribbean", "International", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Royal Caribbean International announces plans for new cruise terminal in Miami.", "tokens": ["Royal", "Caribbean", "International", "announces", "plans", "for", "new", "cruise", "terminal", "in", "Miami", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The Green Climate Fund announces a $50 million investment in renewable energy projects in Africa.", "tokens": ["The", "Green", "Climate", "Fund", "announces", "a", "$", "50", "million", "investment", "in", "renewable", "energy", "projects", "in", "Africa", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "350.org launches global campaign to divest from fossil fuels.", "tokens": ["350", ".", "org", "launches", "global", "campaign", "to", "divest", "from", "fossil", "fuels", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "McDonald's opens 50 new locations in China amid growing demand for fast food.", "tokens": ["McDonald", "'", "s", "opens", "50", "new", "locations", "in", "China", "amid", "growing", "demand", "for", "fast", "food", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Berlin experiences a surge in tourism as travel restrictions ease.", "tokens": ["Berlin", "experiences", "a", "surge", "in", "tourism", "as", "travel", "restrictions", "ease", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Chef Giada De Laurentiis launches new line of pasta sauces in collaboration with Italian food company.", "tokens": ["Chef", "Giada", "De", "Laurentiis", "launches", "new", "line", "of", "pasta", "sauces", "in", "collaboration", "with", "Italian", "food", "company", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-person", "I-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Stella McCartney launches new sustainable fashion line.", "tokens": ["Stella", "McCartney", "launches", "new", "sustainable", "fashion", "line", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The fashion boutiques of New York City prepare for the upcoming holiday season.", "tokens": ["The", "fashion", "boutiques", "of", "New", "York", "City", "prepare", "for", "the", "upcoming", "holiday", "season", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Paris Fashion Week attracts top designers and fashion enthusiasts from around the world.", "tokens": ["Paris", "Fashion", "Week", "attracts", "top", "designers", "and", "fashion", "enthusiasts", "from", "around", "the", "world", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Donatella Versace launches new fashion line in The Soho District.", "tokens": ["Donatella", "Versace", "launches", "new", "fashion", "line", "in", "The", "Soho", "District", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The Soho District in New York City implements new safety measures to improve pedestrian traffic flow.", "tokens": ["The", "Soho", "District", "in", "New", "York", "City", "implements", "new", "safety", "measures", "to", "improve", "pedestrian", "traffic", "flow", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Donatella Versace partners with a non-profit organization to support mental health awareness in The Soho District.", "tokens": ["Donatella", "Versace", "partners", "with", "a", "non", "-", "profit", "organization", "to", "support", "mental", "health", "awareness", "in", "The", "Soho", "District", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "New York City votes to increase minimum wage to $15 per hour by 2022.", "tokens": ["New", "York", "City", "votes", "to", "increase", "minimum", "wage", "to", "$", "15", "per", "hour", "by", "2022", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Mayor de Blasio announces new initiative to combat homelessness in New York City.", "tokens": ["Mayor", "de", "Blasio", "announces", "new", "initiative", "to", "combat", "homelessness", "in", "New", "York", "City", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "New York City Marathon attracts over 50,000 runners from around the world.", "tokens": ["New", "York", "City", "Marathon", "attracts", "over", "50", ",", "000", "runners", "from", "around", "the", "world", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Celebrity chef Gordon Ramsay joins the Food Network as a host for a new cooking show.", "tokens": ["Celebrity", "chef", "Gordon", "Ramsay", "joins", "the", "Food", "Network", "as", "a", "host", "for", "a", "new", "cooking", "show", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Food Network launches new streaming service for food enthusiasts.", "tokens": ["Food", "Network", "launches", "new", "streaming", "service", "for", "food", "enthusiasts", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Food Network announces partnership with renowned pastry chef for new baking competition series.", "tokens": ["Food", "Network", "announces", "partnership", "with", "renowned", "pastry", "chef", "for", "new", "baking", "competition", "series", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
