[
  {
    "sentence": "Violent protests erupt in Caracas following controversial election results.",
    "span": "Caracas",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0020151049068000003
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Caracas Mayor calls for increased security measures in the city center.",
    "span": "Caracas",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.025466934742359996
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Google for Education launches new online learning platform.",
    "span": "Google for Education",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0005419658289166667
  },
  {
    "sentence": "New York City schools partner with Google for Education for digital learning initiative.",
    "span": "New York City",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00021199438953333331
  },
  {
    "sentence": "New York City schools partner with Google for Education for digital learning initiative.",
    "span": "Google for Education",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -3.8733685000000004e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Teachers across the country utilize Google for Education tools for virtual classrooms.",
    "span": "Google for Education",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -4.5309140166666674e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Pandora Media announces partnership with Sony Music Entertainment.",
    "span": "Pandora Media",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -2.296151281428571e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Pandora Media announces partnership with Sony Music Entertainment.",
    "span": "Sony Music Entertainment",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0009513529733333335
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Sony Music to release new album in collaboration with a popular artist.",
    "span": "Sony Music",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0001836994166
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Pandora Media's CEO discusses future plans for the company at annual conference.",
    "span": "Pandora Media",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0029977137606471424
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Private Michael Jenkins awarded Purple Heart for heroism in battle.",
    "span": "Private Michael Jenkins",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0288780731735
  },
  {
    "sentence": "New research shows alarming increase in carbon emissions from China.",
    "span": "China",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0001179856345
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Apple Inc. announces launch of new iPhone model.",
    "span": "Apple Inc.",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0009229813436216666
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Berlin police officer Samantha Brown honored for bravery.",
    "span": "Berlin",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0013077999192500002
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Berlin police officer Samantha Brown honored for bravery.",
    "span": "Samantha Brown",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.1604111008863
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Massive protest in Berlin against government's new immigration policy.",
    "span": "Berlin",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -6.834464e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Officer Samantha Brown apprehends suspect in Berlin bank robbery.",
    "span": "Samantha Brown",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.007533392195757144
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Officer Samantha Brown apprehends suspect in Berlin bank robbery.",
    "span": "Berlin",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.007459071485899999
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The exhibition features a rare collection of Claude Monet's paintings.",
    "span": "Claude Monet",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0009630435076928573
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The Claude Monet Museum in Giverny, France, reopens after renovations.",
    "span": "Claude Monet",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0012730725284757145
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The Claude Monet Museum in Giverny, France, reopens after renovations.",
    "span": "Giverny",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0023494190356142856
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The Claude Monet Museum in Giverny, France, reopens after renovations.",
    "span": "France",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.005423136304000001
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tech giant Apple launches new iPhone with improved camera and battery life.",
    "span": "Apple",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.1034261555825
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Stocks plunge as United Airlines announces 20,000 layoffs due to pandemic impact.",
    "span": "United Airlines",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0005613988333600001
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Famous actress Jennifer Lawrence to star in new Netflix thriller.",
    "span": "Jennifer Lawrence",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0018113241002999999
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Famous actress Jennifer Lawrence to star in new Netflix thriller.",
    "span": "Netflix",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -2.2693304e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Kraft Heinz reports decrease in sales for the third quarter.",
    "span": "Kraft Heinz",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00045624795700000004
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Ina Garten's new cookbook becomes best-seller in the first week of release.",
    "span": "Ina Garten",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0020003825477833332
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Stocks of Kraft Heinz surge after announcement of new CEO.",
    "span": "Kraft Heinz",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -2.9073385157142854e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The Climate Action Network demands stronger measures to combat climate change.",
    "span": "Climate Action Network",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0002916224565
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Prince Charles delivers a speech on environmental conservation at the United Nations.",
    "span": "Prince Charles",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.00985721921796
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Prince Charles delivers a speech on environmental conservation at the United Nations.",
    "span": "United Nations",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.027264859016799998
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Members of the Climate Action Network protest outside of the White House.",
    "span": "Climate Action Network",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -4.344161955e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Members of the Climate Action Network protest outside of the White House.",
    "span": "White House",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -9.113500876e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Uber launches new feature to schedule rides in advance.",
    "span": "Uber",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0007459297135
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Uber driver charged with assault in New York City.",
    "span": "Uber",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -1.2570547755795
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Uber driver charged with assault in New York City.",
    "span": "New York City",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00270051559625
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Uber CEO resigns amidst controversy.",
    "span": "Uber",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.30667388964775
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Uber CEO resigns amidst controversy.",
    "span": "CEO",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.00026151876625
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Michelle Obama delivers powerful speech at United Nations conference.",
    "span": "Michelle Obama",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.000391113814
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Michelle Obama delivers powerful speech at United Nations conference.",
    "span": "United Nations",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00075689853738
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Former First Lady Michelle Obama launches new initiative to promote girls' education.",
    "span": "Michelle Obama",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -6.870527272e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Michelle Obama visits children's hospital in Chicago to meet with young patients.",
    "span": "Michelle Obama",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -1.5332477859999998e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Michelle Obama visits children's hospital in Chicago to meet with young patients.",
    "span": "Chicago",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.02087733383025
  },
  {
    "sentence": "BARCELONA - NEW MAYOR ELECTED AFTER CLOSE ELECTION.",
    "span": "Barcelona",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.5669111158632
  },
  {
    "sentence": "RALPH LAUREN ANNOUNCES PLAN TO LAUNCH SUSTAINABLE FASHION LINE.",
    "span": "RALPH LAUREN",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.10893105157786248
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Barcelona FC hires new head coach from Argentina.",
    "span": "Barcelona FC",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.004776039209333334
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Barcelona FC hires new head coach from Argentina.",
    "span": "Argentina",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00012534095625
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Oxfam International releases report on global hunger crisis.",
    "span": "Oxfam International",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0006891647491428572
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Aisha Khan appointed as ambassador to United Nations.",
    "span": "Aisha Khan",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.04139566066038333
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Aisha Khan appointed as ambassador to United Nations.",
    "span": "United Nations",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0010219521529999998
  },
  {
    "sentence": "New Oxfam International CEO vows to tackle inequality in third world countries.",
    "span": "Oxfam International",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00019044818934285714
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Samantha Miller appointed as the new spokesperson for the International Red Cross and Red Crescent Movement.",
    "span": "Samantha Miller",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -8.859343942857144e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The Food and Agriculture Organization reports record crop yields in the Midwest.",
    "span": "Food and Agriculture Organization",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.002997319205142857
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The Food and Agriculture Organization reports record crop yields in the Midwest.",
    "span": "Midwest",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.000653381667
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The CEO of Apple Inc. announces new product release at tech conference.",
    "span": "Apple Inc.",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.025685199725333337
  },
  {
    "sentence": "China surpasses United States as world's largest importer of agricultural products, says Food and Agriculture Organization.",
    "span": "China",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00030826682715
  },
  {
    "sentence": "China surpasses United States as world's largest importer of agricultural products, says Food and Agriculture Organization.",
    "span": "United States",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -3.27123714e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Justin Bieber's new album breaks records.",
    "span": "Justin Bieber",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0009460962562
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Sony Pictures announces plans for new blockbuster movie.",
    "span": "Sony Pictures",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0002004631392
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Justin Bieber's collaboration with Sony Pictures becomes a box office hit.",
    "span": "Justin Bieber",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -3.9101687399999996e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Justin Bieber's collaboration with Sony Pictures becomes a box office hit.",
    "span": "Sony Pictures",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -3.1377291780000004e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The Museum of Contemporary Art in Tokyo, Japan, is hosting a special exhibition on traditional Japanese pottery.",
    "span": "Museum of Contemporary Art",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.000164294425
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The Museum of Contemporary Art in Tokyo, Japan, is hosting a special exhibition on traditional Japanese pottery.",
    "span": "Tokyo",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00011137257200000001
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The Museum of Contemporary Art in Tokyo, Japan, is hosting a special exhibition on traditional Japanese pottery.",
    "span": "Japan",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.000595435046
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The Royal Academy of Arts in London is planning to showcase a collection of works by renowned British artists.",
    "span": "Royal Academy of Arts",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -5.4800681428571424e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The Royal Academy of Arts in London is planning to showcase a collection of works by renowned British artists.",
    "span": "London",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0009155626936250001
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Refugee Council USA advocates for more funding for resettlement programs.",
    "span": "Refugee Council USA",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00041263684982500006
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Natasha Petrovna elected as the new head of the International Red Cross.",
    "span": "Natasha Petrovna",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -7.5906279375e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "An earthquake hit the small town of Amalfi, Italy, causing widespread damage.",
    "span": "Amalfi",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00014603319350000002
  },
  {
    "sentence": "An earthquake hit the small town of Amalfi, Italy, causing widespread damage.",
    "span": "Italy",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -3.789177125e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Rescue team saves 10 climbers stranded in The Andes Mountains.",
    "span": "The Andes Mountains",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0007562075951142857
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Cristiano Ronaldo scores a hat-trick in the semi-final match.",
    "span": "Cristiano Ronaldo",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0007121610769928571
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The National Council of Teachers of English holds annual conference in Tokyo, Japan.",
    "span": "Tokyo",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.008652905423374999
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The National Council of Teachers of English holds annual conference in Tokyo, Japan.",
    "span": "Japan",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0005728216281500001
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tokyo, Japan to host 2020 Summer Olympics.",
    "span": "Tokyo",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -1.0278242299999999e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tokyo, Japan to host 2020 Summer Olympics.",
    "span": "Japan",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.000198076305
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The National Council of Teachers of English celebrates its 100th anniversary with a special event in Tokyo, Japan.",
    "span": "Tokyo",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -1.4557653775000001e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The National Council of Teachers of English celebrates its 100th anniversary with a special event in Tokyo, Japan.",
    "span": "Japan",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -6.66459855e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Local business owner, Anthony Nguyen, named Entrepreneur of the Year.",
    "span": "Anthony Nguyen",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0044347575694
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Protests erupt in downtown Los Angeles over police shooting of Anthony Nguyen.",
    "span": "Los Angeles",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0111596503116
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Protests erupt in downtown Los Angeles over police shooting of Anthony Nguyen.",
    "span": "Anthony Nguyen",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0001416142702
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Anthony Nguyen Foundation donates $1 million to local hospital.",
    "span": "Anthony Nguyen",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.070946010196
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Warren Buffett's Berkshire Hathaway invests in Starbucks Corporation.",
    "span": "Warren Buffett",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.00027431070115
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Warren Buffett's Berkshire Hathaway invests in Starbucks Corporation.",
    "span": "Berkshire Hathaway",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0010147373096666666
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Warren Buffett's Berkshire Hathaway invests in Starbucks Corporation.",
    "span": "Starbucks Corporation",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0002783200436
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Starbucks Corporation opens new store in Shanghai.",
    "span": "Starbucks Corporation",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -9.650436858333334e-06
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Starbucks Corporation opens new store in Shanghai.",
    "span": "Shanghai",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00020917048
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Warren Buffett predicts economic downturn in the coming year.",
    "span": "Warren Buffett",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -6.715887131666667e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Earthwatch Institute partners with local communities to study the effects of climate change.",
    "span": "Earthwatch Institute",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0011231801382833335
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The United Nations reports a 30% increase in deforestation in the Amazon rainforest.",
    "span": "United Nations",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0061874063764
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The United Nations reports a 30% increase in deforestation in the Amazon rainforest.",
    "span": "Amazon rainforest",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0022711265885
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Renowned physicist Stephen Hawking's theories on black holes continue to intrigue scientists around the world.",
    "span": "Stephen Hawking",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0002849293559333333
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Google co-founder Larry Page steps down as CEO of Alphabet",
    "span": "Google",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0040524111628
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Google co-founder Larry Page steps down as CEO of Alphabet",
    "span": "Larry Page",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.18535756604450002
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Google co-founder Larry Page steps down as CEO of Alphabet",
    "span": "Alphabet",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00728258176025
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Larry Page donates millions to wildlife conservation efforts",
    "span": "Larry Page",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0002036086394
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Alphabet's Larry Page expresses support for climate change initiatives",
    "span": "Alphabet",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.03912838668446
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Alphabet's Larry Page expresses support for climate change initiatives",
    "span": "Larry Page",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0004944433512
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Technology giant Apple announces record-breaking sales for the third quarter.",
    "span": "Apple",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.007041311848999999
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Renowned chef Jamie Oliver launches new cooking show on streaming platform.",
    "span": "Jamie Oliver",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -6.873278292e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Greenpeace protests the construction of a new oil pipeline in Alaska.",
    "span": "Greenpeace",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.000285248133
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Greenpeace protests the construction of a new oil pipeline in Alaska.",
    "span": "Alaska",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00037860293175
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The United Way of Central Ohio raises over $1 million for local homeless shelters.",
    "span": "United Way of Central Ohio",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0001038345496125
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Berlin experiences record-breaking heat wave, with temperatures reaching 40 degrees Celsius.",
    "span": "Berlin",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -1.87595835e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tesla posts record-breaking profits in third quarter.",
    "span": "Tesla",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.014268565105
  },
  {
    "sentence": "New York City mayor announces plan to tackle homelessness crisis.",
    "span": "New York City",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0013572346510833334
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Emmy-winning actress to star in upcoming blockbuster film.",
    "span": "Emmy-winning actress",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.03256128566242857
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The European Union imposes new carbon emission regulations on automobile manufacturers.",
    "span": "European Union",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0004264667606
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Severe flooding in the Midwest prompts evacuation orders for thousands of residents.",
    "span": "Midwest",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -7.41394976e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "TripAdvisor reveals the top 10 hotels in Europe for 2021.",
    "span": "TripAdvisor",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0292152651951
  },
  {
    "sentence": "TripAdvisor reveals the top 10 hotels in Europe for 2021.",
    "span": "Europe",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00189253628725
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Walt Disney World Resort announces new COVID-19 safety measures for guests.",
    "span": "Walt Disney World Resort",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.001418303199475
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Jennifer Lopez to perform at the Super Bowl halftime show.",
    "span": "Jennifer Lopez",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0001893581009
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Jennifer Lopez to perform at the Super Bowl halftime show.",
    "span": "Super Bowl",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.03185771914186
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX successfully launches new satellite into orbit.",
    "span": "Elon Musk",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0010386552951666666
  },
  {
    "sentence": "New York City Mayor announces plans for citywide clean energy initiative.",
    "span": "New York City",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.2276754894908333
  },
  {
    "sentence": "New York City Mayor announces plans for citywide clean energy initiative.",
    "span": "Mayor",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.00486734283425
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Apple Inc. unveils latest iPhone model with enhanced features and capabilities.",
    "span": "Apple Inc.",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.011943503381199998
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Taylor Swift performs surprise show at The Bluebird Cafe.",
    "span": "Taylor Swift",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0009269256712000001
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Taylor Swift performs surprise show at The Bluebird Cafe.",
    "span": "The Bluebird Cafe",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00839922567757143
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The Bluebird Cafe in Nashville to host songwriter's night.",
    "span": "The Bluebird Cafe",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.008538037874428571
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The Bluebird Cafe in Nashville to host songwriter's night.",
    "span": "Nashville",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0001225043705
  },
  {
    "sentence": "New documentary explores the history of The Bluebird Cafe.",
    "span": "The Bluebird Cafe",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0019368481158571428
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Cape Town experiences record-breaking heat wave, with temperatures exceeding 40 degrees Celsius.",
    "span": "Cape Town",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0005113076916716667
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Local resident from Cape Town wins national award for community service.",
    "span": "Cape Town",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -1.727947160833333e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Pentagon announces new military strategy in Indo-Pacific region.",
    "span": "Pentagon",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.1902248843294583
  },
  {
    "sentence": "General James Mattis faces criticism over military budget allocation.",
    "span": "General James Mattis",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.00023374451726666668
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Local farmers at Smithfield Farmers' Market report record sales this season.",
    "span": "Smithfield Farmers' Market",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.056995526112125
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Smithfield Farmers' Market to host annual Fall Festival next weekend.",
    "span": "Smithfield Farmers' Market",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0320911138737375
  },
  {
    "sentence": "New organic produce vendor joins Smithfield Farmers' Market lineup.",
    "span": "Smithfield Farmers' Market",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0487156646343625
  },
  {
    "sentence": "China National Space Administration launches new satellite to study climate change.",
    "span": "China National Space Administration",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0017437765562142858
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Sierra Nevada Corporation to supply NASA with cargo transportation services to the International Space Station.",
    "span": "Sierra Nevada Corporation",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00011476798943285716
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Sierra Nevada Corporation to supply NASA with cargo transportation services to the International Space Station.",
    "span": "NASA",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00194803380925
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Russian cosmonauts and Chinese astronauts conduct joint space mission.",
    "span": "Russian",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.229049526175
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Russian cosmonauts and Chinese astronauts conduct joint space mission.",
    "span": "Chinese",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.009168046490000002
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tesla announces plans to open new manufacturing plant in Texas.",
    "span": "Tesla",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -5.568291675e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tesla announces plans to open new manufacturing plant in Texas.",
    "span": "Texas",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0035346001075
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Michelle Obama to launch new initiative to promote education for girls.",
    "span": "Michelle Obama",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0001604403953
  },
  {
    "sentence": "European Union imposes sanctions on Russian officials over Navalny poisoning.",
    "span": "European Union",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -2.057743886e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "European Union imposes sanctions on Russian officials over Navalny poisoning.",
    "span": "Russian",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.20481858925000002
  },
  {
    "sentence": "European Union imposes sanctions on Russian officials over Navalny poisoning.",
    "span": "Navalny",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0002090725514
  },
  {
    "sentence": "United Airlines announces the addition of new flights to Hawaii .",
    "span": "United Airlines",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.26510405408820004
  },
  {
    "sentence": "United Airlines announces the addition of new flights to Hawaii .",
    "span": "Hawaii",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00017814855892
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The CEO of Boeing resigned following the company's recent safety scandals.",
    "span": "Boeing",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0014039533923200002
  },
  {
    "sentence": "President Biden signs executive order to address climate change.",
    "span": "President Biden",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.009812702330600002
  },
  {
    "sentence": "London Heathrow Airport sees 70% decrease in passenger numbers.",
    "span": "London Heathrow Airport",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0007077355107142858
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Apple announces new iPhone release date.",
    "span": "Apple",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.08474371412775
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The CEO of Apple, Sarah Johnson, announces the launch of a new line of iPhones.",
    "span": "Apple",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0285337037078
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The CEO of Apple, Sarah Johnson, announces the launch of a new line of iPhones.",
    "span": "Sarah Johnson",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.00097945694825
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The United Nations reports progress in peace negotiations in the Middle East, with Secretary-General Sarah Johnson overseeing the talks.",
    "span": "United Nations",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00025797250794
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The United Nations reports progress in peace negotiations in the Middle East, with Secretary-General Sarah Johnson overseeing the talks.",
    "span": "Middle East",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.004949120421000001
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The United Nations reports progress in peace negotiations in the Middle East, with Secretary-General Sarah Johnson overseeing the talks.",
    "span": "Sarah Johnson",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.00601022645288
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Donatella Versace to open new flagship store in The Dubai Mall.",
    "span": "Donatella Versace",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.09174482251991667
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Donatella Versace to open new flagship store in The Dubai Mall.",
    "span": "The Dubai Mall",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00014606406863749998
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Annual fashion show to feature prominent designers including Donatella Versace.",
    "span": "Donatella Versace",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -4.1687261887500004e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The Dubai Mall announces expansion plans to accommodate more luxury retailers.",
    "span": "The Dubai Mall",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.002292858197688333
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Sarah Khan appointed as the new CEO of a major tech company.",
    "span": "Sarah Khan",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0012911060327
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Cape Town braces for severe drought as water levels continue to drop.",
    "span": "Cape Town",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0010797629718333334
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Dr. David Lee appointed as head of department at prestigious medical research institute.",
    "span": "Dr. David Lee",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.008252518282385714
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tech giant Apple unveils new iPhone 13.",
    "span": "Apple",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.06992425700674999
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Paris Hilton launches new fragrance line.",
    "span": "Paris Hilton",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.00010855524559999999
  },
  {
    "sentence": "United Nations Security Council to discuss ceasefire in Syria at emergency meeting.",
    "span": "Syria",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0001451819465
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tesla reports record-breaking sales in the second quarter.",
    "span": "Tesla",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -5.02265989575e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tim Cook announces plans to expand Apple's presence in China.",
    "span": "Tim Cook",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0002653172666
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tim Cook announces plans to expand Apple's presence in China.",
    "span": "Apple",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0019871759372499997
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tim Cook announces plans to expand Apple's presence in China.",
    "span": "China",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00063977090775
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Stocks on the Frankfurt Stock Exchange plunge after new trade tariffs are announced.",
    "span": "Frankfurt Stock Exchange",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0014390061602857144
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Frankfurt Stock Exchange hits record high as tech companies continue to thrive.",
    "span": "Frankfurt Stock Exchange",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0006715344660857143
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Starbucks partners with Rainforest Alliance to promote sustainable farming practices.",
    "span": "Starbucks",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0056476605065999995
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Starbucks partners with Rainforest Alliance to promote sustainable farming practices.",
    "span": "Rainforest Alliance",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0002519585265
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Rainforest Alliance releases new report on deforestation in the Amazon.",
    "span": "Rainforest Alliance",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0006023859364166667
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Rainforest Alliance releases new report on deforestation in the Amazon.",
    "span": "Amazon",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00038647130412499997
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Climate change threatens the future of Rainforest Alliance certified coffee farms.",
    "span": "Rainforest Alliance",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00035129125878333335
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tesla announces plans to open new manufacturing facility in Austin, Texas.",
    "span": "Tesla",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -3.4703073575000004e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tesla announces plans to open new manufacturing facility in Austin, Texas.",
    "span": "Austin",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0034013786185
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tesla announces plans to open new manufacturing facility in Austin, Texas.",
    "span": "Texas",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00306292059025
  },
  {
    "sentence": "United Nations reports increase in humanitarian aid to war-torn regions.",
    "span": "United Nations",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -4.064913544e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Jerusalem's Old City sees increase in tourism after easing of COVID-19 restrictions.",
    "span": "Jerusalem",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.004703926834399999
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Israel's Ministry of Health announces new vaccine mandate for all healthcare workers in Jerusalem.",
    "span": "Israel",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.08145187046624999
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Israel's Ministry of Health announces new vaccine mandate for all healthcare workers in Jerusalem.",
    "span": "Ministry of Health",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0007938562489833333
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Israel's Ministry of Health announces new vaccine mandate for all healthcare workers in Jerusalem.",
    "span": "Jerusalem",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00017860758325
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Apple Inc. announces plans to open new manufacturing plant in Texas.",
    "span": "Apple Inc.",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00017691978323999998
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Apple Inc. announces plans to open new manufacturing plant in Texas.",
    "span": "Texas",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00109205479825
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Immigrant Legal Resource Center files lawsuit against the Department of Homeland Security over new immigration policy.",
    "span": "Immigrant Legal Resource Center",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00012487102298125
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Immigrant Legal Resource Center files lawsuit against the Department of Homeland Security over new immigration policy.",
    "span": "Department of Homeland Security",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00018117229224285714
  },
  {
    "sentence": "ICE raids target employers hiring unauthorized workers.",
    "span": "ICE",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.056282995855
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Renowned author and poet Maya Angelou to be honored with new stamp.",
    "span": "Maya Angelou",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.002521821402328571
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Maya Angelou's autobiography 'I Know Why the Caged Bird Sings' to be adapted into a stage play.",
    "span": "Maya Angelou",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -4.073778908571429e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Maya Angelou's legacy celebrated on what would have been her 90th birthday.",
    "span": "Maya Angelou",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -1.633719484857143e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Patrick Mahomes signs 10-year contract extension with Kansas City Chiefs.",
    "span": "Patrick Mahomes",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0001527403911
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Patrick Mahomes signs 10-year contract extension with Kansas City Chiefs.",
    "span": "Kansas City Chiefs",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00012518354866666666
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Megan Rapinoe becomes first openly gay woman to appear in Sports Illustrated swimsuit issue.",
    "span": "Megan Rapinoe",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -3.52222951375e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Megan Rapinoe becomes first openly gay woman to appear in Sports Illustrated swimsuit issue.",
    "span": "Sports Illustrated",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00042435815139999996
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Patrick Mahomes leads Kansas City Chiefs to Super Bowl victory.",
    "span": "Patrick Mahomes",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -2.312045031666667e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Patrick Mahomes leads Kansas City Chiefs to Super Bowl victory.",
    "span": "Kansas City Chiefs",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00023509088361666665
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Sydney experiences record-breaking heatwave.",
    "span": "Sydney",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0016772651262000002
  },
  {
    "sentence": "New study shows Sydney's air pollution levels remain dangerously high.",
    "span": "Sydney",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -1.902779036e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tesla surpasses expectations, reaching new record high in stock market.",
    "span": "Tesla",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.014982007140875001
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tokyo Olympics officially postponed to 2021.",
    "span": "Tokyo",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.01089333345552
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Dr. Anthony Fauci warns of potential 'resurgence' of COVID-19 in the fall.",
    "span": "Dr. Anthony Fauci",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.05164407325124999
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Amsterdam implements new bike lanes to promote safer commuting for cyclists.",
    "span": "Amsterdam",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0001264662408
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The United Nations Secretary-General praises The Intergovernmental Panel on Climate Change for its groundbreaking research on climate change.",
    "span": "United Nations Secretary-General",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.049749762632654154
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Johnson Elementary School wins first place in national chess tournament.",
    "span": "Johnson Elementary School",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0006350994288333334
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Three students from Johnson Elementary School to represent their state in the National Science Fair.",
    "span": "Johnson Elementary School",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00010160872633333333
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Local community rallies behind Johnson Elementary School after devastating fire.",
    "span": "Johnson Elementary School",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0454314902395
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Record-breaking heatwave hits Los Angeles.",
    "span": "Los Angeles",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -7.64997306e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Los Angeles Mayor announces new funding for homeless shelters.",
    "span": "Los Angeles",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.15363441427499996
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Los Angeles Mayor announces new funding for homeless shelters.",
    "span": "Mayor",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.00029188360850000006
  },
  {
    "sentence": "J.K. Rowling's new book release date revealed",
    "span": "J.K. Rowling",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0008743654908999999
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Banksy's latest artwork discovered in London",
    "span": "Banksy",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.00019165701833333333
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Banksy's latest artwork discovered in London",
    "span": "London",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0002926525035
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Local school receives donation from J.K. Rowling",
    "span": "J.K. Rowling",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.003129238765185714
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Mondelez International announces partnership with local farmers to promote sustainable cocoa production.",
    "span": "Mondelez International",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.005051016419991428
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Unilever acquires snack brands from Mondelez International for $2.7 billion.",
    "span": "Unilever",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0013843038286666667
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Unilever acquires snack brands from Mondelez International for $2.7 billion.",
    "span": "Mondelez International",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -4.419469664285714e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Kraft Heinz reports increase in sales, surpassing analyst expectations for the quarter.",
    "span": "Kraft Heinz",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -4.773412902857143e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Pope Francis visits Vatican City to address climate change.",
    "span": "Pope Francis",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0008129205668333334
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Pope Francis visits Vatican City to address climate change.",
    "span": "Vatican City",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.001036003086
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Firefighters battle massive wildfire in California.",
    "span": "California",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.004980000230125
  },
  {
    "sentence": "CDC warns of potential new COVID-19 variant.",
    "span": "CDC",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.134926837172325
  },
  {
    "sentence": "CDC warns of potential new COVID-19 variant.",
    "span": "COVID-19",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.014686613681233335
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Celebrity chef Guy Fieri to open new restaurant in New York City.",
    "span": "Guy Fieri",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -6.563397855e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Celebrity chef Guy Fieri to open new restaurant in New York City.",
    "span": "New York City",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0097680707065
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Food Network star Guy Fieri launches his own line of barbecue sauce.",
    "span": "Food Network",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0007112880010583335
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Food Network star Guy Fieri launches his own line of barbecue sauce.",
    "span": "Guy Fieri",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -7.144475944e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Guy Fieri's cooking show 'Diners, Drive-Ins and Dives' renewed for another season.",
    "span": "Guy Fieri",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.005812390138849999
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Severe bushfires in Australia prompt warnings from the Australian Bureau of Meteorology.",
    "span": "Australia",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0023550739462500003
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Severe bushfires in Australia prompt warnings from the Australian Bureau of Meteorology.",
    "span": "Australian Bureau of Meteorology",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00041494782905
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Australian Bureau of Meteorology predicts record-breaking heatwave across the country.",
    "span": "Australian Bureau of Meteorology",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.039595864094199996
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Heatwave in Sydney reaches new highs, according to data from the Australian Bureau of Meteorology.",
    "span": "Sydney",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -1.673908122e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Heatwave in Sydney reaches new highs, according to data from the Australian Bureau of Meteorology.",
    "span": "Australian Bureau of Meteorology",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -2.4004543587499997e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Israel reopens its borders to vaccinated tourists.",
    "span": "Israel",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.009196978798249999
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The Australian government announces new funding for Canberra infrastructure projects.",
    "span": "Australian government",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0017976438161799997
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The Australian government announces new funding for Canberra infrastructure projects.",
    "span": "Canberra",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.013017144508719996
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Coach Rachel Turner leads her team to victory in the championship game.",
    "span": "Coach Rachel Turner",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0005115072228333333
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Pope Francis visits Mexico to address issues of poverty and immigration.",
    "span": "Pope Francis",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0003156255444333333
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Pope Francis visits Mexico to address issues of poverty and immigration.",
    "span": "Mexico",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00012648347325
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Thousands flock to Niagara Falls for the annual fireworks display on July 4th.",
    "span": "Niagara Falls",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -3.5318958890000005e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "New species of endangered monkey discovered in Sundarbans National Park.",
    "span": "Sundarbans National Park",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.000885339054548889
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Government allocates funding for infrastructure development in Sundarbans National Park.",
    "span": "Sundarbans National Park",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0021298366635555555
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Environmental group protest proposed industrial development near Sundarbans National Park.",
    "span": "Sundarbans National Park",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.24573452377577779
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Fashion icon Iris Apfel launches new line of eyewear.",
    "span": "Iris Apfel",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0014537420574000002
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Janet Mock makes history as the first trans woman of color to direct a TV series.",
    "span": "Janet Mock",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0017779786600833332
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Munroe Bergdorf appointed as the new diversity consultant for the fashion brand.",
    "span": "Munroe Bergdorf",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0018675821500750002
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The annual LGBTQ+ parade in San Francisco draws thousands of participants.",
    "span": "San Francisco",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0204524304602
  },
  {
    "sentence": "PFLAG releases new educational resources for LGBTQ+ youth and families.",
    "span": "PFLAG",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.01544035341668
  },
  {
    "sentence": "PFLAG releases new educational resources for LGBTQ+ youth and families.",
    "span": "LGBTQ+",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0118259974156
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Local PFLAG chapter to host virtual support group for parents of transgender children.",
    "span": "PFLAG",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00035700036258
  },
  {
    "sentence": "PFLAG advocates for LGBTQ+ rights in upcoming city council meeting.",
    "span": "PFLAG",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -6.519848822e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "PFLAG advocates for LGBTQ+ rights in upcoming city council meeting.",
    "span": "LGBTQ+",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0219689489714
  },
  {
    "sentence": "German Chancellor Angela Merkel meets with French President Emmanuel Macron to discuss EU economic reforms.",
    "span": "Angela Merkel",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -5.49255149e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "German Chancellor Angela Merkel meets with French President Emmanuel Macron to discuss EU economic reforms.",
    "span": "Emmanuel Macron",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.05212161625464
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Angela Merkel announces plan to invest €130 billion in renewable energy infrastructure.",
    "span": "Angela Merkel",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -3.1522475858333336e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Angela Merkel's conservative CDU party loses ground in local elections.",
    "span": "Angela Merkel",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -3.223769724166667e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Angela Merkel's conservative CDU party loses ground in local elections.",
    "span": "CDU",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00012954426722
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Atheist Alliance International condemns Archbishop Justin Welby's comments on atheism.",
    "span": "Atheist Alliance International",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00010666184028750001
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Atheist Alliance International condemns Archbishop Justin Welby's comments on atheism.",
    "span": "Archbishop Justin Welby",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0004868442451357143
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Archbishop Justin Welby meets with leaders of Atheist Alliance International to discuss religious tolerance.",
    "span": "Archbishop Justin Welby",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0003303253263925
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Archbishop Justin Welby meets with leaders of Atheist Alliance International to discuss religious tolerance.",
    "span": "Atheist Alliance International",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -8.61588431857143e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Atheist Alliance International launches new campaign to promote secularism in schools with Archbishop Justin Welby's support.",
    "span": "Atheist Alliance International",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -7.9921515e-06
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Atheist Alliance International launches new campaign to promote secularism in schools with Archbishop Justin Welby's support.",
    "span": "Archbishop Justin Welby",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -2.2041941571428567e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Marissa Mayer appointed as the new CEO of a major tech company.",
    "span": "Marissa Mayer",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.24648181204816666
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Amazon.com, Inc. launches new subscription service for prime members.",
    "span": "Amazon.com, Inc.",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0109958312217
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Elon Musk announces plans for new space exploration project.",
    "span": "Elon Musk",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.06641121366575
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Kim Kardashian launches new beauty line.",
    "span": "Kim Kardashian",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0017338582384
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Major earthquake hits Los Angeles, causing widespread damage.",
    "span": "Los Angeles",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0001175021207
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Golden State Warriors defeat Houston Rockets in thrilling overtime game.",
    "span": "Golden State Warriors",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.000199152783
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Golden State Warriors defeat Houston Rockets in thrilling overtime game.",
    "span": "Houston Rockets",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -5.34538096e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Emily Rodriguez appointed as new chief executive officer of Chicago-based tech company.",
    "span": "Emily Rodriguez",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0013166424272
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Emily Rodriguez appointed as new chief executive officer of Chicago-based tech company.",
    "span": "Chicago",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.09231985821225
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Chicago mayor announces plans to invest in infrastructure improvements.",
    "span": "Chicago",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00024234164750000002
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Emily Rodriguez awarded prestigious business award for leadership in Chicago community.",
    "span": "Emily Rodriguez",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -1.132723508e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Emily Rodriguez awarded prestigious business award for leadership in Chicago community.",
    "span": "Chicago",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0004907227768
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tom Cruise to receive special award from British Academy of Film and Television Arts (BAFTA) for outstanding contribution to film.",
    "span": "Tom Cruise",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0044861538058
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tom Cruise to receive special award from British Academy of Film and Television Arts (BAFTA) for outstanding contribution to film.",
    "span": "British Academy of Film and Television Arts",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.01046782339017
  },
  {
    "sentence": "British Academy of Film and Television Arts (BAFTA) announces nominations for upcoming awards ceremony.",
    "span": "British Academy of Film and Television Arts",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -4.722660848e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tom Cruise's latest film tops box office over the weekend.",
    "span": "Tom Cruise",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -1.0468968720000001e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Chaz Bono to star in new reality TV show.",
    "span": "Chaz Bono",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.001267869649757143
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Rio de Janeiro celebrates Carnival with colorful parades and lively music.",
    "span": "Rio de Janeiro",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.009058709473633334
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Brazil announces plan to combat deforestation in the Amazon rainforest.",
    "span": "Brazil",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.01273460573125
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Rio de Janeiro to host 2024 Summer Olympics.",
    "span": "Rio de Janeiro",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.18251921460498335
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Rio de Janeiro to host 2024 Summer Olympics.",
    "span": "2024 Summer Olympics",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.10014454244971428
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Red Rocks Amphitheatre to welcome famous music artists for summer concert series.",
    "span": "Red Rocks Amphitheatre",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -4.7396429624999996e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Greta Thunberg announces new climate change initiative.",
    "span": "Greta Thunberg",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.031814747881524996
  },
  {
    "sentence": "David Brown appointed as CEO of tech startup.",
    "span": "David Brown",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.00176035305818
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Boris Johnson announces new environmental regulations.",
    "span": "Boris Johnson",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0027698250867833328
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Protests erupt in London following Boris Johnson's controversial remarks.",
    "span": "London",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.021643348808899995
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Protests erupt in London following Boris Johnson's controversial remarks.",
    "span": "Boris Johnson",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -9.44206268e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Boris Johnson meets with European Union leaders to discuss trade agreements.",
    "span": "Boris Johnson",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -5.76629243e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Boris Johnson meets with European Union leaders to discuss trade agreements.",
    "span": "European Union",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -1.1732527199999999e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Lieutenant Colonel Mark Thompson resigns from his position as head of the military defense division.",
    "span": "Lieutenant Colonel Mark Thompson",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.00328399150125
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Investigations into the financial scandal at ABC Corporation reveal shocking details.",
    "span": "ABC Corporation",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -8.920390244e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Protests erupt in downtown New York City over police brutality.",
    "span": "New York City",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00011749765964999999
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Sydney Opera House announces lineup for summer concert series.",
    "span": "Sydney Opera House",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0016669089750285715
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Investigation reveals ties between mayor's office and local construction company.",
    "span": "mayor's office",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.3150933297296143
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Investigation reveals ties between mayor's office and local construction company.",
    "span": "construction company",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.018114487961480002
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Teenage climate activist speaks at United Nations summit in New York.",
    "span": "United Nations",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.25587163855934
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Teenage climate activist speaks at United Nations summit in New York.",
    "span": "New York",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00175084566502
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Oxford University announces plans to open new research facility in London.",
    "span": "Oxford University",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -1.4855663383333333e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Oxford University announces plans to open new research facility in London.",
    "span": "London",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00015797387299999998
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Jennifer Lopez to make guest appearance on popular TV show.",
    "span": "Jennifer Lopez",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0066973127844
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The latest production of Shakespeare's Hamlet received rave reviews from theater critics.",
    "span": "Shakespeare",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0066578850240000004
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The new Shakespeare exhibition at the British Museum is drawing large crowds of tourists.",
    "span": "Shakespeare",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0400422141542
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The new Shakespeare exhibition at the British Museum is drawing large crowds of tourists.",
    "span": "British Museum",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0009957477284
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Stratford-upon-Avon, the birthplace of Shakespeare, is a popular destination for literary enthusiasts.",
    "span": "Stratford-upon-Avon",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0003173816952599999
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Stratford-upon-Avon, the birthplace of Shakespeare, is a popular destination for literary enthusiasts.",
    "span": "Shakespeare",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -3.1722981e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Moscow announces plan to improve public transportation infrastructure.",
    "span": "Moscow",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.014297292570600001
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Elizabeth Warren proposes new legislation to address student loan debt.",
    "span": "Elizabeth Warren",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -7.04254766e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Russia imposes sanctions on Western countries in response to diplomatic tensions.",
    "span": "Russia",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00016143491125
  },
  {
    "sentence": "New discovery of ancient artifacts near Giza pyramid complex.",
    "span": "Giza",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0012725633338
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Google launches new privacy feature for email users.",
    "span": "Google",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.000345659654575
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Local residents protest proposed construction of new Google headquarters.",
    "span": "Google",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -1.709073235e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Dwayne \"The Rock\" Johnson announces new partnership with fitness brand.",
    "span": "Dwayne \"The Rock\" Johnson",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.29933126549004
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Dwayne \"The Rock\" Johnson announces new partnership with fitness brand.",
    "span": "fitness brand",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00037237171878
  },
  {
    "sentence": "New York City reports record-high temperatures for the month of July.",
    "span": "New York City",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00019084951369999998
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tesla's CEO Elon Musk unveils plans for new electric vehicle model.",
    "span": "Tesla",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00029175529825000004
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tesla's CEO Elon Musk unveils plans for new electric vehicle model.",
    "span": "Elon Musk",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.029934177926620002
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tech giant Apple Inc. launches new iPhone model.",
    "span": "Apple Inc.",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00017724407360833334
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Local artist John Smith to exhibit new work at gallery next month.",
    "span": "John Smith",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0034574138963399995
  },
  {
    "sentence": "National Park Service to implement new conservation measures in Everglades National Park, USA.",
    "span": "National Park Service",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00010444241441666667
  },
  {
    "sentence": "National Park Service to implement new conservation measures in Everglades National Park, USA.",
    "span": "Everglades National Park",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.026025564541175005
  },
  {
    "sentence": "National Park Service to implement new conservation measures in Everglades National Park, USA.",
    "span": "USA",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0007764237647500001
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Renowned environmentalist to speak at Everglades National Park, USA Earth Day event.",
    "span": "Everglades National Park",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.004247244900225001
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Renowned environmentalist to speak at Everglades National Park, USA Earth Day event.",
    "span": "USA",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.008422278493
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Federal funding approved for restoration project in Everglades National Park, USA.",
    "span": "Everglades National Park",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00047100915075000004
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Federal funding approved for restoration project in Everglades National Park, USA.",
    "span": "USA",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.000309286463075
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Brie Larson wins Best Actress at the Atlanta Film Festival.",
    "span": "Brie Larson",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.00017933135175000003
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Brie Larson wins Best Actress at the Atlanta Film Festival.",
    "span": "Atlanta",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.25547963679905
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Berlin Marathon postponed due to COVID-19 pandemic.",
    "span": "Berlin",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00014951914575
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Best-selling author Chinua Achebe passes away at 82.",
    "span": "Chinua Achebe",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0004671872313777778
  },
  {
    "sentence": "J.K. Rowling's new book tops the bestseller list.",
    "span": "J.K. Rowling",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0006620516469142857
  },
  {
    "sentence": "United States Department of Defense announces new cybersecurity initiative.",
    "span": "United States Department of Defense",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00030272502153749997
  },
  {
    "sentence": "California wildfires force thousands to evacuate.",
    "span": "California",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00012600115625
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Famous actor Tom Hanks to star in new World War II film.",
    "span": "Tom Hanks",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.06678379153025
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Los Angeles mayor announces new traffic control measures.",
    "span": "Los Angeles",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00025899725379999996
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Los Angeles mayor announces new traffic control measures.",
    "span": "mayor",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0018197255400000001
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The Los Angeles Lakers will face the Golden State Warriors in their next game.",
    "span": "Los Angeles",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0117341546536
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The Los Angeles Lakers will face the Golden State Warriors in their next game.",
    "span": "Lakers",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.001947199549975
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The Los Angeles Lakers will face the Golden State Warriors in their next game.",
    "span": "Golden State Warriors",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.003454001930333333
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Heavy rain causes flooding in Los Angeles area.",
    "span": "Heavy rain",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.31786160235999994
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Heavy rain causes flooding in Los Angeles area.",
    "span": "Los Angeles",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0008779322598
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The United Nations releases new report on global climate change.",
    "span": "global climate change",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.4313043091666666
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX plans to launch a new satellite into orbit next week.",
    "span": "Elon Musk",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -2.3478061500000003e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX plans to launch a new satellite into orbit next week.",
    "span": "SpaceX",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0017495475523499999
  },
  {
    "sentence": "London Mayor announces plan to reduce air pollution in the city center.",
    "span": "London",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.099526343428325
  },
  {
    "sentence": "London Mayor announces plan to reduce air pollution in the city center.",
    "span": "Mayor",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0848129309725
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Moscow mayor announces new public transportation initiatives.",
    "span": "Moscow",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0018831872083999997
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Top chef Fatima Ali launches new cooking show.",
    "span": "Fatima Ali",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -5.3693131699999995e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Jews for Jesus celebrates 40 years of ministry.",
    "span": "Jews for Jesus",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.002388808416185714
  },
  {
    "sentence": "New York City to host annual Jews for Jesus conference.",
    "span": "New York City",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.013708094935883333
  },
  {
    "sentence": "New York City to host annual Jews for Jesus conference.",
    "span": "Jews for Jesus",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -9.821540613333335e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Former member of Jews for Jesus speaks out against the organization.",
    "span": "Jews for Jesus",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -9.065771371428572e-06
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Local high school to host It Gets Better Project assembly",
    "span": "high school",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.03928365261055714
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Local high school to host It Gets Better Project assembly",
    "span": "It Gets Better Project",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.11530820268360001
  },
  {
    "sentence": "ISRO launches new satellite into orbit around Venus.",
    "span": "ISRO",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0001433142992
  },
  {
    "sentence": "ISRO launches new satellite into orbit around Venus.",
    "span": "Venus",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00058198790335
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Rocket Lab successfully tests new reusable rocket technology.",
    "span": "Rocket Lab",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -7.568767654e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Scientists discover possible signs of life on Venus.",
    "span": "Venus",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0001314751539
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Heavy rainfall causes flooding and road closures in Coventry, England.",
    "span": "Coventry",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00936992798805
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Heavy rainfall causes flooding and road closures in Coventry, England.",
    "span": "England",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.004391781524
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Coventry City Council adopts new environmental sustainability initiative.",
    "span": "Coventry City Council",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.1738759773583625
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Local musician from Coventry, England, to perform at upcoming music festival.",
    "span": "Coventry",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -8.750859116666666e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Local musician from Coventry, England, to perform at upcoming music festival.",
    "span": "England",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.000110150738375
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tech giant Apple announces the launch of new iPhone models.",
    "span": "Apple",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.13353712802450002
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Senator Harris to visit Texas to discuss immigration reform.",
    "span": "Senator Harris",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0018501336253199999
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Senator Harris to visit Texas to discuss immigration reform.",
    "span": "Texas",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00046103182200000006
  },
  {
    "sentence": "EU imposes sanctions on Russian officials over human rights violations.",
    "span": "EU",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -1.1309354475e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "EU imposes sanctions on Russian officials over human rights violations.",
    "span": "Russian",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.031439701725
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The National Black Justice Coalition condemns the recent hate crime in Atlanta.",
    "span": "National Black Justice Coalition",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0003995975002857143
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The National Black Justice Coalition condemns the recent hate crime in Atlanta.",
    "span": "Atlanta",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00048023556975
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The Association of LGBTQ Journalists announces new scholarship program for aspiring writers.",
    "span": "The Association of LGBTQ Journalists",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00037769135514444444
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Two transgender women elected to local government positions in California.",
    "span": "California",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.002362029702625
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX Successfully Launches Crewed Mission to International Space Station.",
    "span": "Elon Musk",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0002998789969166666
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX Successfully Launches Crewed Mission to International Space Station.",
    "span": "SpaceX",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -9.322381625e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "New York City to Invest $10 Billion in Infrastructure Projects Over Next 5 Years.",
    "span": "New York City",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -4.1495235800000004e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Apple Inc. Announces Plan to Open 20 New Retail Stores in China.",
    "span": "Apple Inc.",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -5.61138876e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Apple Inc. Announces Plan to Open 20 New Retail Stores in China.",
    "span": "China",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -6.760053225e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX launches successful satellite into orbit.",
    "span": "Elon Musk",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.00020255131721666668
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Forest fires rage through Northern California, causing widespread destruction.",
    "span": "Northern California",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0015783339468
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Microsoft to acquire leading cybersecurity firm in multi-billion dollar deal.",
    "span": "Microsoft",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.000229177004125
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Royal Caribbean International offers 30% discount on select cruises.",
    "span": "Royal Caribbean International",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00025060358049999997
  },
  {
    "sentence": "New CEO appointed at Royal Caribbean International.",
    "span": "Royal Caribbean International",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0026046080186666667
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Royal Caribbean International announces plans for new cruise terminal in Miami.",
    "span": "Royal Caribbean International",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0002933170321
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Royal Caribbean International announces plans for new cruise terminal in Miami.",
    "span": "Miami",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00016564051100000004
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The Green Climate Fund announces a $50 million investment in renewable energy projects in Africa.",
    "span": "Green Climate Fund",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0001953330755
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The Green Climate Fund announces a $50 million investment in renewable energy projects in Africa.",
    "span": "Africa",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0005454188645
  },
  {
    "sentence": "350.org launches global campaign to divest from fossil fuels.",
    "span": "350.org",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.008318463481539999
  },
  {
    "sentence": "McDonald's opens 50 new locations in China amid growing demand for fast food.",
    "span": "McDonald's",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -5.744927260666667e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "McDonald's opens 50 new locations in China amid growing demand for fast food.",
    "span": "China",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0006662837065
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Berlin experiences a surge in tourism as travel restrictions ease.",
    "span": "Berlin",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -4.1406446975e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Chef Giada De Laurentiis launches new line of pasta sauces in collaboration with Italian food company.",
    "span": "Giada De Laurentiis",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.006859474251622222
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Chef Giada De Laurentiis launches new line of pasta sauces in collaboration with Italian food company.",
    "span": "Italian food company",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0016668657500499998
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Stella McCartney launches new sustainable fashion line.",
    "span": "Stella McCartney",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0036703792075666666
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The fashion boutiques of New York City prepare for the upcoming holiday season.",
    "span": "New York City",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.002576041197
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Paris Fashion Week attracts top designers and fashion enthusiasts from around the world.",
    "span": "Paris Fashion Week",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.025084910153149995
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Donatella Versace launches new fashion line in The Soho District.",
    "span": "Donatella Versace",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.077895655256525
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Donatella Versace launches new fashion line in The Soho District.",
    "span": "The Soho District",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00020542041004285714
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The Soho District in New York City implements new safety measures to improve pedestrian traffic flow.",
    "span": "The Soho District",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.001338339894414286
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The Soho District in New York City implements new safety measures to improve pedestrian traffic flow.",
    "span": "New York City",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00020264821041666666
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Donatella Versace partners with a non-profit organization to support mental health awareness in The Soho District.",
    "span": "Donatella Versace",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -9.22479554e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Donatella Versace partners with a non-profit organization to support mental health awareness in The Soho District.",
    "span": "The Soho District",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.015218668938842857
  },
  {
    "sentence": "New York City votes to increase minimum wage to $15 per hour by 2022.",
    "span": "New York City",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00507294103075
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Mayor de Blasio announces new initiative to combat homelessness in New York City.",
    "span": "Mayor de Blasio",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.033214747685250005
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Mayor de Blasio announces new initiative to combat homelessness in New York City.",
    "span": "New York City",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -7.442968083333333e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "New York City Marathon attracts over 50,000 runners from around the world.",
    "span": "New York City",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.003952754686533334
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Celebrity chef Gordon Ramsay joins the Food Network as a host for a new cooking show.",
    "span": "Gordon Ramsay",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -7.305744028571429e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Celebrity chef Gordon Ramsay joins the Food Network as a host for a new cooking show.",
    "span": "Food Network",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00029412092764
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Food Network launches new streaming service for food enthusiasts.",
    "span": "Food Network",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -4.7633736499999994e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Food Network announces partnership with renowned pastry chef for new baking competition series.",
    "span": "Food Network",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.01404346689578
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Microsoft's Terry Myerson Announces New Product Launch.",
    "span": "Microsoft",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.085948505592
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Microsoft's Terry Myerson Announces New Product Launch.",
    "span": "Terry Myerson",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0010161613809
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Terry Myerson to Step Down as Head of Windows at Microsoft.",
    "span": "Terry Myerson",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -4.225338037142858e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Terry Myerson to Step Down as Head of Windows at Microsoft.",
    "span": "Windows",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0404385579075
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Terry Myerson to Step Down as Head of Windows at Microsoft.",
    "span": "Microsoft",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.000296190105
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Terry Myerson joins startup as Chief Technology Officer.",
    "span": "Terry Myerson",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0015706025995042856
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Rolling Stone magazine releases list of top 100 greatest drummers of all time.",
    "span": "Rolling Stone",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00042590856378333335
  },
  {
    "sentence": "New exhibit at the museum features iconic photographs from Rolling Stone.",
    "span": "Rolling Stone",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0228138962423
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Rolling Stone journalist interviews famous rock band for cover story.",
    "span": "Rolling Stone",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.04254079136655001
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Ford Motor Company to open new manufacturing plant in Shanghai.",
    "span": "Ford Motor Company",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.010815143481833336
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Ford Motor Company to open new manufacturing plant in Shanghai.",
    "span": "Shanghai",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0003680580065
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Shanghai experiences heavy rainfall, causing widespread flooding.",
    "span": "Shanghai",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -4.6394016699999995e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Investigation reveals corruption scandal within Shanghai government officials.",
    "span": "Shanghai",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -1.3186811827999999e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Chelsea Football Club 's new stadium plans face opposition from local residents.",
    "span": "Chelsea Football Club",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.001996746961166667
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Record-breaking goal scorer signs contract extension with Chelsea Football Club .",
    "span": "Chelsea Football Club",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -3.0133598499999998e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "President Biden signs infrastructure bill into law.",
    "span": "Biden",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.31479866139999996
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Wildfires continue to devastate California forests.",
    "span": "California",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.000111165806
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Amnesty International reports human rights abuses in Myanmar.",
    "span": "Amnesty International",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00028992975445
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Amnesty International reports human rights abuses in Myanmar.",
    "span": "Myanmar",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0010223527505
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Protests erupt in response to controversial police shooting in New York City.",
    "span": "New York City",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00018285123478333333
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Amnesty International calls for investigation into alleged war crimes in Syria.",
    "span": "Amnesty International",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -3.0545005166666665e-06
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Amnesty International calls for investigation into alleged war crimes in Syria.",
    "span": "Syria",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -1.9862217975e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "UNICEF launches campaign to provide clean water to communities in Africa.",
    "span": "UNICEF",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0009399136937833333
  },
  {
    "sentence": "UNICEF launches campaign to provide clean water to communities in Africa.",
    "span": "Africa",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00150654489975
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Young girl rescued by UNICEF from child labor in Southeast Asia.",
    "span": "UNICEF",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -9.769640125e-06
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Young girl rescued by UNICEF from child labor in Southeast Asia.",
    "span": "Southeast Asia",
