{"sentence": "Tech giant Apple Inc. reports record-breaking profits for the third quarter.", "tokens": ["Tech", "giant", "Apple", "Inc", ".", "reports", "record", "-", "breaking", "profits", "for", "the", "third", "quarter", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Global oil prices surge as OPEC announces production cut.", "tokens": ["Global", "oil", "prices", "surge", "as", "OPEC", "announces", "production", "cut", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Renowned economist Dr. John Smith predicts a downturn in the stock market.", "tokens": ["Renowned", "economist", "Dr", ".", "John", "Smith", "predicts", "a", "downturn", "in", "the", "stock", "market", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "TENNIS - SERENA WILLIAMS WINS WIMBLEDON CHAMPIONSHIP.", "tokens": ["TENNIS", "-", "SERENA", "WILLIAMS", "WINS", "WIMBLEDON", "CHAMPIONSHIP", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "B-location", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "FOOTBALL - MANCHESTER UNITED SIGNS FRENCH MIDFIELDER PAUL POGBA FOR RECORD TRANSFER FEE.", "tokens": ["FOOTBALL", "-", "MANCHESTER", "UNITED", "SIGNS", "FRENCH", "MIDFIELDER", "PAUL", "POGBA", "FOR", "RECORD", "TRANSFER", "FEE", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "New York City's JFK airport to undergo major renovation.", "tokens": ["New", "York", "City", "'", "s", "JFK", "airport", "to", "undergo", "major", "renovation", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Delta Airlines announces new nonstop flight from Atlanta to Paris.", "tokens": ["Delta", "Airlines", "announces", "new", "nonstop", "flight", "from", "Atlanta", "to", "Paris", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Famous travel blogger recommends the Maldives as the top destination for luxury travelers.", "tokens": ["Famous", "travel", "blogger", "recommends", "the", "Maldives", "as", "the", "top", "destination", "for", "luxury", "travelers", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "New York's Museum of Modern Art launches virtual reality exhibit.", "tokens": ["New", "York", "'", "s", "Museum", "of", "Modern", "Art", "launches", "virtual", "reality", "exhibit", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Artist Banksy's latest mural draws crowds in London.", "tokens": ["Artist", "Banksy", "'", "s", "latest", "mural", "draws", "crowds", "in", "London", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "National Endowment for the Arts announces grant program for emerging artists.", "tokens": ["National", "Endowment", "for", "the", "Arts", "announces", "grant", "program", "for", "emerging", "artists", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "NASA announces discovery of potentially habitable exoplanet.", "tokens": ["NASA", "announces", "discovery", "of", "potentially", "habitable", "exoplanet", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Research team at Harvard University develops groundbreaking cancer treatment.", "tokens": ["Research", "team", "at", "Harvard", "University", "develops", "groundbreaking", "cancer", "treatment", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Scientists predict major breakthrough in renewable energy technology.", "tokens": ["Scientists", "predict", "major", "breakthrough", "in", "renewable", "energy", "technology", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Local high school student overcomes homelessness to graduate with honors.", "tokens": ["Local", "high", "school", "student", "overcomes", "homelessness", "to", "graduate", "with", "honors", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Non-profit organization partners with school district to provide free tutoring services for low-income students.", "tokens": ["Non", "-", "profit", "organization", "partners", "with", "school", "district", "to", "provide", "free", "tutoring", "services", "for", "low", "-", "income", "students", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Former teacher starts scholarship fund to help underprivileged students pursue higher education.", "tokens": ["Former", "teacher", "starts", "scholarship", "fund", "to", "help", "underprivileged", "students", "pursue", "higher", "education", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-person", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "New study finds link between lack of sleep and increased risk of heart disease.", "tokens": ["New", "study", "finds", "link", "between", "lack", "of", "sleep", "and", "increased", "risk", "of", "heart", "disease", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "World Health Organization launches new initiative to combat childhood obesity.", "tokens": ["World", "Health", "Organization", "launches", "new", "initiative", "to", "combat", "childhood", "obesity", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Renowned cardiologist Dr. Samantha Smith appointed as head of National Institute of Health.", "tokens": ["Renowned", "cardiologist", "Dr", ".", "Samantha", "Smith", "appointed", "as", "head", "of", "National", "Institute", "of", "Health", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "I-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tesla announces plan to build new Gigafactory in Berlin.", "tokens": ["Tesla", "announces", "plan", "to", "build", "new", "Gigafactory", "in", "Berlin", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Warren Buffett's Berkshire Hathaway invests $10 billion in Japanese tech company.", "tokens": ["Warren", "Buffett", "'", "s", "Berkshire", "Hathaway", "invests", "$", "10", "billion", "in", "Japanese", "tech", "company", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Google parent company Alphabet reports record-breaking quarterly earnings.", "tokens": ["Google", "parent", "company", "Alphabet", "reports", "record", "-", "breaking", "quarterly", "earnings", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "China announces new tariffs on imported automobiles in response to trade tensions with the United States.", "tokens": ["China", "announces", "new", "tariffs", "on", "imported", "automobiles", "in", "response", "to", "trade", "tensions", "with", "the", "United", "States", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The European Union and United Kingdom reach a trade agreement after months of negotiations.", "tokens": ["The", "European", "Union", "and", "United", "Kingdom", "reach", "a", "trade", "agreement", "after", "months", "of", "negotiations", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Renowned artist Banksy's latest mural unveiled in downtown New York.", "tokens": ["Renowned", "artist", "Banksy", "'", "s", "latest", "mural", "unveiled", "in", "downtown", "New", "York", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Museum of Modern Art to host retrospective exhibit on the works of Vincent van Gogh.", "tokens": ["Museum", "of", "Modern", "Art", "to", "host", "retrospective", "exhibit", "on", "the", "works", "of", "Vincent", "van", "Gogh", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "I-person", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Local art festival draws record number of attendees, showcasing talent from across the region.", "tokens": ["Local", "art", "festival", "draws", "record", "number", "of", "attendees", ",", "showcasing", "talent", "from", "across", "the", "region", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "New York City hosts annual festival celebrating immigrant stories.", "tokens": ["New", "York", "City", "hosts", "annual", "festival", "celebrating", "immigrant", "stories", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The Met Gala's theme for 2022 will celebrate the intersection of fashion, art, and technology.", "tokens": ["The", "Met", "Gala", "'", "s", "theme", "for", "2022", "will", "celebrate", "the", "intersection", "of", "fashion", ",", "art", ",", "and", "technology", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The British Museum's latest exhibition on ancient civilizations explores the cultural and historical significance of artifacts from Mesopotamia and Egypt.", "tokens": ["The", "British", "Museum", "'", "s", "latest", "exhibition", "on", "ancient", "civilizations", "explores", "the", "cultural", "and", "historical", "significance", "of", "artifacts", "from", "Mesopotamia", "and", "Egypt", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Renowned filmmaker Ava DuVernay to curate a special exhibition showcasing the impact of African American artists on contemporary culture.", "tokens": ["Renowned", "filmmaker", "Ava", "DuVernay", "to", "curate", "a", "special", "exhibition", "showcasing", "the", "impact", "of", "African", "American", "artists", "on", "contemporary", "culture", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "New study finds that students from low-income families are less likely to attend college.", "tokens": ["New", "study", "finds", "that", "students", "from", "low", "-", "income", "families", "are", "less", "likely", "to", "attend", "college", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Harvard University receives $10 million donation for scholarship fund.", "tokens": ["Harvard", "University", "receives", "$", "10", "million", "donation", "for", "scholarship", "fund", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Education ministry announces new curriculum for primary schools.", "tokens": ["Education", "ministry", "announces", "new", "curriculum", "for", "primary", "schools", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Apple Inc. reports record-breaking quarterly profits.", "tokens": ["Apple", "Inc", ".", "reports", "record", "-", "breaking", "quarterly", "profits", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The stock market reacts positively to the announcement of a new trade deal with China.", "tokens": ["The", "stock", "market", "reacts", "positively", "to", "the", "announcement", "of", "a", "new", "trade", "deal", "with", "China", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Elon Musk steps down as CEO of Tesla, Inc. amidst controversy.", "tokens": ["Elon", "Musk", "steps", "down", "as", "CEO", "of", "Tesla", ",", "Inc", ".", "amidst", "controversy", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "President Biden signs executive order to address immigration reform.", "tokens": ["President", "Biden", "signs", "executive", "order", "to", "address", "immigration", "reform", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The United Nations holds emergency meeting to discuss global security issues.", "tokens": ["The", "United", "Nations", "holds", "emergency", "meeting", "to", "discuss", "global", "security", "issues", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Prime Minister Johnson faces backlash over new tax legislation.", "tokens": ["Prime", "Minister", "Johnson", "faces", "backlash", "over", "new", "tax", "legislation", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Harvard University announces a new scholarship program for low-income students.", "tokens": ["Harvard", "University", "announces", "a", "new", "scholarship", "program", "for", "low", "-", "income", "students", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "High school graduation rates reach a record high in New York City.", "tokens": ["High", "school", "graduation", "rates", "reach", "a", "record", "high", "in", "New", "York", "City", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Renowned education expert Dr. Jane Smith to speak at the annual education conference.", "tokens": ["Renowned", "education", "expert", "Dr", ".", "Jane", "Smith", "to", "speak", "at", "the", "annual", "education", "conference", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "I-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Google announces plan to invest in renewable energy projects.", "tokens": ["Google", "announces", "plan", "to", "invest", "in", "renewable", "energy", "projects", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX successfully launches new satellite into orbit.", "tokens": ["Elon", "Musk", "'", "s", "SpaceX", "successfully", "launches", "new", "satellite", "into", "orbit", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "New York City announces plans to invest $100 million in tourism infrastructure.", "tokens": ["New", "York", "City", "announces", "plans", "to", "invest", "$", "100", "million", "in", "tourism", "infrastructure", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Airline industry faces challenges as international travel restrictions continue.", "tokens": ["Airline", "industry", "faces", "challenges", "as", "international", "travel", "restrictions", "continue", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Famous travel blogger shares top 10 destinations for 2022.", "tokens": ["Famous", "travel", "blogger", "shares", "top", "10", "destinations", "for", "2022", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Taylor Swift releases her highly anticipated album 'Evermore'.", "tokens": ["Taylor", "Swift", "releases", "her", "highly", "anticipated", "album", "'", "Evermore", "'", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Disney announces the launch of a new streaming service for its Marvel movies and TV shows.", "tokens": ["Disney", "announces", "the", "launch", "of", "a", "new", "streaming", "service", "for", "its", "Marvel", "movies", "and", "TV", "shows", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Brad Pitt and Jennifer Aniston rumored to be rekindling their romance after being spotted together at an awards show.", "tokens": ["Brad", "Pitt", "and", "Jennifer", "Aniston", "rumored", "to", "be", "rekindling", "their", "romance", "after", "being", "spotted", "together", "at", "an", "awards", "show", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Local community comes together to raise funds for family who lost everything in house fire.", "tokens": ["Local", "community", "comes", "together", "to", "raise", "funds", "for", "family", "who", "lost", "everything", "in", "house", "fire", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "High school student overcomes adversity to win prestigious scholarship.", "tokens": ["High", "school", "student", "overcomes", "adversity", "to", "win", "prestigious", "scholarship", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Local charity organization provides free meals to homeless population during holiday season.", "tokens": ["Local", "charity", "organization", "provides", "free", "meals", "to", "homeless", "population", "during", "holiday", "season", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Scientists warn of the devastating effects of deforestation on the Amazon rainforest.", "tokens": ["Scientists", "warn", "of", "the", "devastating", "effects", "of", "deforestation", "on", "the", "Amazon", "rainforest", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Renewable energy company announces plan to build new solar farm in Nevada.", "tokens": ["Renewable", "energy", "company", "announces", "plan", "to", "build", "new", "solar", "farm", "in", "Nevada", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "UNESCO designates Great Barrier Reef as a World Heritage Site in Danger.", "tokens": ["UNESCO", "designates", "Great", "Barrier", "Reef", "as", "a", "World", "Heritage", "Site", "in", "Danger", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Japanese artist Yayoi Kusama's latest exhibition breaks attendance records.", "tokens": ["Japanese", "artist", "Yayoi", "Kusama", "'", "s", "latest", "exhibition", "breaks", "attendance", "records", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The Metropolitan Museum of Art in New York City announces new exhibit featuring works by African American artists.", "tokens": ["The", "Metropolitan", "Museum", "of", "Art", "in", "New", "York", "City", "announces", "new", "exhibit", "featuring", "works", "by", "African", "American", "artists", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "President Biden announces new infrastructure plan.", "tokens": ["President", "Biden", "announces", "new", "infrastructure", "plan", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Earthquake hits Japan, causing widespread damage.", "tokens": ["Earthquake", "hits", "Japan", ",", "causing", "widespread", "damage", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tesla stock plunges after CEO Elon Musk's controversial tweet.", "tokens": ["Tesla", "stock", "plunges", "after", "CEO", "Elon", "Musk", "'", "s", "controversial", "tweet", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "New study shows significant decline in global pollinator populations", "tokens": ["New", "study", "shows", "significant", "decline", "in", "global", "pollinator", "populations"], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Environmental activists protest outside government headquarters", "tokens": ["Environmental", "activists", "protest", "outside", "government", "headquarters"], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization"]}
{"sentence": "The World Wildlife Fund announces new conservation efforts in the Amazon rainforest.", "tokens": ["The", "World", "Wildlife", "Fund", "announces", "new", "conservation", "efforts", "in", "the", "Amazon", "rainforest", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Researchers discover a new species of rare bird in the remote forests of Indonesia.", "tokens": ["Researchers", "discover", "a", "new", "species", "of", "rare", "bird", "in", "the", "remote", "forests", "of", "Indonesia", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Conservationists warn of the declining population of polar bears in the Arctic due to climate change.", "tokens": ["Conservationists", "warn", "of", "the", "declining", "population", "of", "polar", "bears", "in", "the", "Arctic", "due", "to", "climate", "change", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "European Union leaders agree on new climate targets for 2030.", "tokens": ["European", "Union", "leaders", "agree", "on", "new", "climate", "targets", "for", "2030", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Chinese President Xi Jinping meets with Russian President Vladimir Putin to discuss trade and security issues.", "tokens": ["Chinese", "President", "Xi", "Jinping", "meets", "with", "Russian", "President", "Vladimir", "Putin", "to", "discuss", "trade", "and", "security", "issues", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "United Nations condemns human rights abuses in Myanmar.", "tokens": ["United", "Nations", "condemns", "human", "rights", "abuses", "in", "Myanmar", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The Immigration and Customs Enforcement agency announced a new policy regarding asylum seekers.", "tokens": ["The", "Immigration", "and", "Customs", "Enforcement", "agency", "announced", "a", "new", "policy", "regarding", "asylum", "seekers", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The influx of immigrants from Central America has put a strain on border patrol resources.", "tokens": ["The", "influx", "of", "immigrants", "from", "Central", "America", "has", "put", "a", "strain", "on", "border", "patrol", "resources", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The government is considering a proposal to reform the immigration system to prioritize skilled workers.", "tokens": ["The", "government", "is", "considering", "a", "proposal", "to", "reform", "the", "immigration", "system", "to", "prioritize", "skilled", "workers", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "New study reveals potential breakthrough in cancer treatment.", "tokens": ["New", "study", "reveals", "potential", "breakthrough", "in", "cancer", "treatment", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "World Health Organization announces new initiative to combat global obesity epidemic.", "tokens": ["World", "Health", "Organization", "announces", "new", "initiative", "to", "combat", "global", "obesity", "epidemic", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Renowned cardiologist Dr. Smith appointed to lead groundbreaking research on heart disease prevention.", "tokens": ["Renowned", "cardiologist", "Dr", ".", "Smith", "appointed", "to", "lead", "groundbreaking", "research", "on", "heart", "disease", "prevention", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Local community comes together to support family after tragic house fire.", "tokens": ["Local", "community", "comes", "together", "to", "support", "family", "after", "tragic", "house", "fire", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Former homeless man starts nonprofit to help others in need.", "tokens": ["Former", "homeless", "man", "starts", "nonprofit", "to", "help", "others", "in", "need", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "8-year-old girl raises thousands of dollars for cancer research.", "tokens": ["8", "-", "year", "-", "old", "girl", "raises", "thousands", "of", "dollars", "for", "cancer", "research", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "I-person", "I-person", "I-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Taylor Swift's new album breaks streaming records.", "tokens": ["Taylor", "Swift", "'", "s", "new", "album", "breaks", "streaming", "records", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The Beatles' legendary performance at Abbey Road Studios.", "tokens": ["The", "Beatles", "'", "legendary", "performance", "at", "Abbey", "Road", "Studios", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Rihanna named as the headliner for Coachella 2023.", "tokens": ["Rihanna", "named", "as", "the", "headliner", "for", "Coachella", "2023", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Fashion retailer Zara launches new sustainable clothing line.", "tokens": ["Fashion", "retailer", "Zara", "launches", "new", "sustainable", "clothing", "line", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Top model Gigi Hadid walks in Paris Fashion Week runway show.", "tokens": ["Top", "model", "Gigi", "Hadid", "walks", "in", "Paris", "Fashion", "Week", "runway", "show", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Online fashion giant ASOS reports record sales for the third quarter.", "tokens": ["Online", "fashion", "giant", "ASOS", "reports", "record", "sales", "for", "the", "third", "quarter", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The Federal Reserve announces interest rate hike in response to inflation concerns.", "tokens": ["The", "Federal", "Reserve", "announces", "interest", "rate", "hike", "in", "response", "to", "inflation", "concerns", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Renowned economist predicts global recession in the next two years.", "tokens": ["Renowned", "economist", "predicts", "global", "recession", "in", "the", "next", "two", "years", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "European Union imposes new tariffs on American imports in response to trade disputes.", "tokens": ["European", "Union", "imposes", "new", "tariffs", "on", "American", "imports", "in", "response", "to", "trade", "disputes", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Taylor Swift releases new album", "tokens": ["Taylor", "Swift", "releases", "new", "album"], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Beyoncé to headline Coachella music festival", "tokens": ["Beyoncé", "to", "headline", "Coachella", "music", "festival"], "labels": ["B-person", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Spotify surpasses 100 million paid subscribers", "tokens": ["Spotify", "surpasses", "100", "million", "paid", "subscribers"], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "President Biden signs new executive order to address climate change.", "tokens": ["President", "Biden", "signs", "new", "executive", "order", "to", "address", "climate", "change", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "United Nations holds emergency meeting to discuss humanitarian crisis in Yemen.", "tokens": ["United", "Nations", "holds", "emergency", "meeting", "to", "discuss", "humanitarian", "crisis", "in", "Yemen", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Prime Minister Trudeau announces new economic stimulus package for small businesses.", "tokens": ["Prime", "Minister", "Trudeau", "announces", "new", "economic", "stimulus", "package", "for", "small", "businesses", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Box office revenue reaches new high as summer blockbuster movies draw in record crowds.", "tokens": ["Box", "office", "revenue", "reaches", "new", "high", "as", "summer", "blockbuster", "movies", "draw", "in", "record", "crowds", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Director John Smith's latest film receives critical acclaim at prestigious film festival.", "tokens": ["Director", "John", "Smith", "'", "s", "latest", "film", "receives", "critical", "acclaim", "at", "prestigious", "film", "festival", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Hollywood production company announces plans to adapt best-selling novel into major motion picture.", "tokens": ["Hollywood", "production", "company", "announces", "plans", "to", "adapt", "best", "-", "selling", "novel", "into", "major", "motion", "picture", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Suspect arrested in connection with bank robbery spree in downtown Manhattan.", "tokens": ["Suspect", "arrested", "in", "connection", "with", "bank", "robbery", "spree", "in", "downtown", "Manhattan", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Police commissioner announces crackdown on organized crime syndicate operating in the city.", "tokens": ["Police", "commissioner", "announces", "crackdown", "on", "organized", "crime", "syndicate", "operating", "in", "the", "city", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Three members of notorious gang indicted on charges of drug trafficking and extortion.", "tokens": ["Three", "members", "of", "notorious", "gang", "indicted", "on", "charges", "of", "drug", "trafficking", "and", "extortion", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Senator Smith delivers passionate speech on healthcare reform", "tokens": ["Senator", "Smith", "delivers", "passionate", "speech", "on", "healthcare", "reform"], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "European Union leaders reach consensus on new trade agreement with Canada", "tokens": ["European", "Union", "leaders", "reach", "consensus", "on", "new", "trade", "agreement", "with", "Canada"], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location"]}
{"sentence": "Former President Johnson announces candidacy for upcoming mayoral election", "tokens": ["Former", "President", "Johnson", "announces", "candidacy", "for", "upcoming", "mayoral", "election"], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "President Biden signs new infrastructure bill into law.", "tokens": ["President", "Biden", "signs", "new", "infrastructure", "bill", "into", "law", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Russian government imposes new sanctions on European Union countries.", "tokens": ["Russian", "government", "imposes", "new", "sanctions", "on", "European", "Union", "countries", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Prime Minister Trudeau meets with Indigenous leaders to discuss land rights.", "tokens": ["Prime", "Minister", "Trudeau", "meets", "with", "Indigenous", "leaders", "to", "discuss", "land", "rights", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Authorities arrest three suspects in connection with bank robbery.", "tokens": ["Authorities", "arrest", "three", "suspects", "in", "connection", "with", "bank", "robbery", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Police apprehend notorious gang leader in drug bust.", "tokens": ["Police", "apprehend", "notorious", "gang", "leader", "in", "drug", "bust", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Serial killer sentenced to life in prison for multiple murders.", "tokens": ["Serial", "killer", "sentenced", "to", "life", "in", "prison", "for", "multiple", "murders", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Apple Inc. unveils new iPhone with advanced features.", "tokens": ["Apple", "Inc", ".", "unveils", "new", "iPhone", "with", "advanced", "features", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Google's artificial intelligence system surpasses human performance in language translation.", "tokens": ["Google", "'", "s", "artificial", "intelligence", "system", "surpasses", "human", "performance", "in", "language", "translation", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX launches new satellite into orbit.", "tokens": ["Elon", "Musk", "'", "s", "SpaceX", "launches", "new", "satellite", "into", "orbit", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Fashion retailer Zara sees a 22% increase in online sales.", "tokens": ["Fashion", "retailer", "Zara", "sees", "a", "22", "%", "increase", "in", "online", "sales", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Top fashion designer Stella McCartney to launch sustainable clothing line.", "tokens": ["Top", "fashion", "designer", "Stella", "McCartney", "to", "launch", "sustainable", "clothing", "line", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Paris Fashion Week draws in top designers and celebrities from around the world.", "tokens": ["Paris", "Fashion", "Week", "draws", "in", "top", "designers", "and", "celebrities", "from", "around", "the", "world", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Hurricane Katrina makes landfall in Louisiana.", "tokens": ["Hurricane", "Katrina", "makes", "landfall", "in", "Louisiana", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Record-breaking heatwave hits western United States.", "tokens": ["Record", "-", "breaking", "heatwave", "hits", "western", "United", "States", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tropical storm warning issued for coastal regions.", "tokens": ["Tropical", "storm", "warning", "issued", "for", "coastal", "regions", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Federal Reserve announces interest rate hike.", "tokens": ["Federal", "Reserve", "announces", "interest", "rate", "hike", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "China surpasses United States as largest economy.", "tokens": ["China", "surpasses", "United", "States", "as", "largest", "economy", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "IMF projects global economic slowdown in 2022.", "tokens": ["IMF", "projects", "global", "economic", "slowdown", "in", "2022", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Local woman wins national award for her work with underprivileged children.", "tokens": ["Local", "woman", "wins", "national", "award", "for", "her", "work", "with", "underprivileged", "children", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Non-profit organization raises $100,000 for homeless shelter renovation.", "tokens": ["Non", "-", "profit", "organization", "raises", "$", "100", ",", "000", "for", "homeless", "shelter", "renovation", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Vietnamese immigrant overcomes language barrier to become successful entrepreneur.", "tokens": ["Vietnamese", "immigrant", "overcomes", "language", "barrier", "to", "become", "successful", "entrepreneur", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Celebrity chef Jamie Oliver launches new line of organic cooking ingredients.", "tokens": ["Celebrity", "chef", "Jamie", "Oliver", "launches", "new", "line", "of", "organic", "cooking", "ingredients", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Local art gallery to host exhibit featuring works from renowned painter Pablo Picasso.", "tokens": ["Local", "art", "gallery", "to", "host", "exhibit", "featuring", "works", "from", "renowned", "painter", "Pablo", "Picasso", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Luxury fashion brand Gucci to open flagship store in downtown Los Angeles.", "tokens": ["Luxury", "fashion", "brand", "Gucci", "to", "open", "flagship", "store", "in", "downtown", "Los", "Angeles", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Renowned artist Banksy unveils new exhibit at the Metropolitan Museum of Art.", "tokens": ["Renowned", "artist", "Banksy", "unveils", "new", "exhibit", "at", "the", "Metropolitan", "Museum", "of", "Art", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O"]}
{"sentence": "New mural depicting local history to be commissioned in downtown arts district.", "tokens": ["New", "mural", "depicting", "local", "history", "to", "be", "commissioned", "in", "downtown", "arts", "district", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "National Endowment for the Arts awards grants to exceptional young artists.", "tokens": ["National", "Endowment", "for", "the", "Arts", "awards", "grants", "to", "exceptional", "young", "artists", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Transgender rights activists rally outside state capitol to demand equal protection under the law.", "tokens": ["Transgender", "rights", "activists", "rally", "outside", "state", "capitol", "to", "demand", "equal", "protection", "under", "the", "law", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "New legislation aims to protect LGBTQ youth from conversion therapy in schools.", "tokens": ["New", "legislation", "aims", "to", "protect", "LGBTQ", "youth", "from", "conversion", "therapy", "in", "schools", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "CEO of LGBTQ advocacy organization speaks out against discriminatory employment practices.", "tokens": ["CEO", "of", "LGBTQ", "advocacy", "organization", "speaks", "out", "against", "discriminatory", "employment", "practices", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Luxury fashion house Gucci to open flagship store in downtown Los Angeles.", "tokens": ["Luxury", "fashion", "house", "Gucci", "to", "open", "flagship", "store", "in", "downtown", "Los", "Angeles", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Rising crime rates in New York City fuel concerns about public safety.", "tokens": ["Rising", "crime", "rates", "in", "New", "York", "City", "fuel", "concerns", "about", "public", "safety", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The police department's efforts to crack down on organized crime have yielded significant results.", "tokens": ["The", "police", "department", "'", "s", "efforts", "to", "crack", "down", "on", "organized", "crime", "have", "yielded", "significant", "results", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The mayor vows to address the root causes of crime in the city through community outreach programs.", "tokens": ["The", "mayor", "vows", "to", "address", "the", "root", "causes", "of", "crime", "in", "the", "city", "through", "community", "outreach", "programs", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "BREAKING: Fire breaks out at headquarters of Amazon in Seattle.", "tokens": ["BREAKING", ":", "Fire", "breaks", "out", "at", "headquarters", "of", "Amazon", "in", "Seattle", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Breaking News: President Biden delivers speech on new healthcare initiatives.", "tokens": ["Breaking", "News", ":", "President", "Biden", "delivers", "speech", "on", "new", "healthcare", "initiatives", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "BREAKING: Massive earthquake hits Tokyo, Japan.", "tokens": ["BREAKING", ":", "Massive", "earthquake", "hits", "Tokyo", ",", "Japan", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Breaking News: Elon Musk's SpaceX successfully launches new satellite into orbit.", "tokens": ["Breaking", "News", ":", "Elon", "Musk", "'", "s", "SpaceX", "successfully", "launches", "new", "satellite", "into", "orbit", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Wildfires ravage California, forcing thousands to evacuate their homes.", "tokens": ["Wildfires", "ravage", "California", ",", "forcing", "thousands", "to", "evacuate", "their", "homes", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Global pandemic reaches new heights, WHO warns of potential fourth wave.", "tokens": ["Global", "pandemic", "reaches", "new", "heights", ",", "WHO", "warns", "of", "potential", "fourth", "wave", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Taylor Swift releases new album 'Evermore' during the holiday season.", "tokens": ["Taylor", "Swift", "releases", "new", "album", "'", "Evermore", "'", "during", "the", "holiday", "season", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "HBO announces 'Game of Thrones' prequel series 'House of the Dragon'.", "tokens": ["HBO", "announces", "'", "Game", "of", "Thrones", "'", "prequel", "series", "'", "House", "of", "the", "Dragon", "'", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tom Hanks to star in upcoming biopic about Elvis Presley.", "tokens": ["Tom", "Hanks", "to", "star", "in", "upcoming", "biopic", "about", "Elvis", "Presley", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tesla announces plans to build new electric car manufacturing plant in Texas.", "tokens": ["Tesla", "announces", "plans", "to", "build", "new", "electric", "car", "manufacturing", "plant", "in", "Texas", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Ford Motor Company reports record-breaking sales for the third quarter of 2021.", "tokens": ["Ford", "Motor", "Company", "reports", "record", "-", "breaking", "sales", "for", "the", "third", "quarter", "of", "2021", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Renowned automotive designer, John Smith, unveils latest concept car at international auto show.", "tokens": ["Renowned", "automotive", "designer", ",", "John", "Smith", ",", "unveils", "latest", "concept", "car", "at", "international", "auto", "show", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Renowned chef Jamie Oliver to open new restaurant in the heart of Paris.", "tokens": ["Renowned", "chef", "Jamie", "Oliver", "to", "open", "new", "restaurant", "in", "the", "heart", "of", "Paris", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "British Museum announces partnership with National Geographic for upcoming cultural preservation project.", "tokens": ["British", "Museum", "announces", "partnership", "with", "National", "Geographic", "for", "upcoming", "cultural", "preservation", "project", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Amazon's new AI-powered drone delivery system to revolutionize shipping industry.", "tokens": ["Amazon", "'", "s", "new", "AI", "-", "powered", "drone", "delivery", "system", "to", "revolutionize", "shipping", "industry", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Apple CEO Tim Cook unveils latest iPhone with advanced facial recognition technology.", "tokens": ["Apple", "CEO", "Tim", "Cook", "unveils", "latest", "iPhone", "with", "advanced", "facial", "recognition", "technology", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Google's self-driving car project expands testing to more cities.", "tokens": ["Google", "'", "s", "self", "-", "driving", "car", "project", "expands", "testing", "to", "more", "cities", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Immigration policy reform proposed by Senator Smith.", "tokens": ["Immigration", "policy", "reform", "proposed", "by", "Senator", "Smith", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Border patrol apprehends record number of undocumented immigrants near Texas border.", "tokens": ["Border", "patrol", "apprehends", "record", "number", "of", "undocumented", "immigrants", "near", "Texas", "border", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Immigrant rights organization holds rally in support of DACA recipients.", "tokens": ["Immigrant", "rights", "organization", "holds", "rally", "in", "support", "of", "DACA", "recipients", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Protesters gather in front of city hall demanding police reform.", "tokens": ["Protesters", "gather", "in", "front", "of", "city", "hall", "demanding", "police", "reform", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Unemployment rate reaches record high as job market struggles to recover from pandemic.", "tokens": ["Unemployment", "rate", "reaches", "record", "high", "as", "job", "market", "struggles", "to", "recover", "from", "pandemic", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Renowned author Margaret Atwood wins prestigious literary award.", "tokens": ["Renowned", "author", "Margaret", "Atwood", "wins", "prestigious", "literary", "award", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Local book club hosts virtual discussion on Shakespeare's works.", "tokens": ["Local", "book", "club", "hosts", "virtual", "discussion", "on", "Shakespeare", "'", "s", "works", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-person", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Penguin Random House announces merger with Simon & Schuster.", "tokens": ["Penguin", "Random", "House", "announces", "merger", "with", "Simon", "&", "Schuster", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Pop sensation Taylor Swift announces new album release date.", "tokens": ["Pop", "sensation", "Taylor", "Swift", "announces", "new", "album", "release", "date", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Netflix to produce new original series starring Leonardo DiCaprio.", "tokens": ["Netflix", "to", "produce", "new", "original", "series", "starring", "Leonardo", "DiCaprio", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Hollywood actress Emma Stone wins prestigious award for her role in new film.", "tokens": ["Hollywood", "actress", "Emma", "Stone", "wins", "prestigious", "award", "for", "her", "role", "in", "new", "film", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Local community comes together to support family who lost their home in a fire.", "tokens": ["Local", "community", "comes", "together", "to", "support", "family", "who", "lost", "their", "home", "in", "a", "fire", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Young woman raises $10,000 for cancer research through charity marathon.", "tokens": ["Young", "woman", "raises", "$", "10", ",", "000", "for", "cancer", "research", "through", "charity", "marathon", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Elderly man reunited with long-lost wartime love after 75 years.", "tokens": ["Elderly", "man", "reunited", "with", "long", "-", "lost", "wartime", "love", "after", "75", "years", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Exclusive report exposes unethical labor practices in major chocolate manufacturer's supply chain.", "tokens": ["Exclusive", "report", "exposes", "unethical", "labor", "practices", "in", "major", "chocolate", "manufacturer", "'", "s", "supply", "chain", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "General Motors announces partnership with Tesla for development of electric vehicles.", "tokens": ["General", "Motors", "announces", "partnership", "with", "Tesla", "for", "development", "of", "electric", "vehicles", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Ford CEO Jim Farley unveils plan for autonomous vehicle production in Michigan.", "tokens": ["Ford", "CEO", "Jim", "Farley", "unveils", "plan", "for", "autonomous", "vehicle", "production", "in", "Michigan", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Toyota to invest $1 billion in new manufacturing plant in Texas.", "tokens": ["Toyota", "to", "invest", "$", "1", "billion", "in", "new", "manufacturing", "plant", "in", "Texas", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Researchers at MIT develop a groundbreaking new material with potential applications in renewable energy and electronics.", "tokens": ["Researchers", "at", "MIT", "develop", "a", "groundbreaking", "new", "material", "with", "potential", "applications", "in", "renewable", "energy", "and", "electronics", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Japan's government announces a new initiative to promote innovation in the technology sector, partnering with top universities and industry leaders.", "tokens": ["Japan", "'", "s", "government", "announces", "a", "new", "initiative", "to", "promote", "innovation", "in", "the", "technology", "sector", ",", "partnering", "with", "top", "universities", "and", "industry", "leaders", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Startup company XYZ Inc. unveils a revolutionary product that has the potential to disrupt the market and change the way consumers interact with technology.", "tokens": ["Startup", "company", "XYZ", "Inc", ".", "unveils", "a", "revolutionary", "product", "that", "has", "the", "potential", "to", "disrupt", "the", "market", "and", "change", "the", "way", "consumers", "interact", "with", "technology", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "New York City sets record for tourism with over 65 million visitors.", "tokens": ["New", "York", "City", "sets", "record", "for", "tourism", "with", "over", "65", "million", "visitors", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Airbnb partners with UNESCO to promote sustainable travel experiences.", "tokens": ["Airbnb", "partners", "with", "UNESCO", "to", "promote", "sustainable", "travel", "experiences", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "British adventurer becomes first person to solo row across the Atlantic.", "tokens": ["British", "adventurer", "becomes", "first", "person", "to", "solo", "row", "across", "the", "Atlantic", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tropical storm warning issued for the Gulf Coast.", "tokens": ["Tropical", "storm", "warning", "issued", "for", "the", "Gulf", "Coast", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Record-breaking heatwave hits Europe.", "tokens": ["Record", "-", "breaking", "heatwave", "hits", "Europe", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Hurricane expected to make landfall in the Caribbean.", "tokens": ["Hurricane", "expected", "to", "make", "landfall", "in", "the", "Caribbean", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Famous author J.K. Rowling announces new book release.", "tokens": ["Famous", "author", "J", ".", "K", ".", "Rowling", "announces", "new", "book", "release", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "I-person", "I-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Art exhibition featuring renowned painter Picasso's masterpieces opens in New York.", "tokens": ["Art", "exhibition", "featuring", "renowned", "painter", "Picasso", "'", "s", "masterpieces", "opens", "in", "New", "York", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The National Book Foundation honors Nobel laureate Toni Morrison for her contribution to literature.", "tokens": ["The", "National", "Book", "Foundation", "honors", "Nobel", "laureate", "Toni", "Morrison", "for", "her", "contribution", "to", "literature", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The United States Army announces plans to expand its presence in the Asia-Pacific region.", "tokens": ["The", "United", "States", "Army", "announces", "plans", "to", "expand", "its", "presence", "in", "the", "Asia", "-", "Pacific", "region", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Defense Secretary addresses concerns over military readiness in the face of emerging global threats.", "tokens": ["Defense", "Secretary", "addresses", "concerns", "over", "military", "readiness", "in", "the", "face", "of", "emerging", "global", "threats", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "NATO allies increase joint military exercises in response to heightened tensions with Russia.", "tokens": ["NATO", "allies", "increase", "joint", "military", "exercises", "in", "response", "to", "heightened", "tensions", "with", "Russia", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Renowned fashion designer Coco Chanel's iconic little black dress celebrated its 100th anniversary this week, forever solidifying its place in fashion history.", "tokens": ["Renowned", "fashion", "designer", "Coco", "Chanel", "'", "s", "iconic", "little", "black", "dress", "celebrated", "its", "100th", "anniversary", "this", "week", ",", "forever", "solidifying", "its", "place", "in", "fashion", "history", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The fashion show, hosted by luxury brand Louis Vuitton, took place at the picturesque Château de Versailles, showcasing their latest collection in the opulent surroundings of the historic palace.", "tokens": ["The", "fashion", "show", ",", "hosted", "by", "luxury", "brand", "Louis", "Vuitton", ",", "took", "place", "at", "the", "picturesque", "Château", "de", "Versailles", ",", "showcasing", "their", "latest", "collection", "in", "the", "opulent", "surroundings", "of", "the", "historic", "palace", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Supermodel Gigi Hadid graced the cover of Vogue magazine's September issue, setting a new standard for elegance and chic style in the fashion industry.", "tokens": ["Supermodel", "Gigi", "Hadid", "graced", "the", "cover", "of", "Vogue", "magazine", "'", "s", "September", "issue", ",", "setting", "a", "new", "standard", "for", "elegance", "and", "chic", "style", "in", "the", "fashion", "industry", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "EARTHQUAKE ROCKS LOS ANGELES.", "tokens": ["EARTHQUAKE", "ROCKS", "LOS", "ANGELES", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "NASA ANNOUNCES DISCOVERY OF NEW EXOPLANET.", "tokens": ["NASA", "ANNOUNCES", "DISCOVERY", "OF", "NEW", "EXOPLANET", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "FORMER PRESIDENT OBAMA TO DELIVER KEYNOTE ADDRESS AT CLIMATE SUMMIT.", "tokens": ["FORMER", "PRESIDENT", "OBAMA", "TO", "DELIVER", "KEYNOTE", "ADDRESS", "AT", "CLIMATE", "SUMMIT", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Taylor Swift wins Album of the Year at the Grammy Awards.", "tokens": ["Taylor", "Swift", "wins", "Album", "of", "the", "Year", "at", "the", "Grammy", "Awards", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The Rolling Stones announce a new world tour.", "tokens": ["The", "Rolling", "Stones", "announce", "a", "new", "world", "tour", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Beyoncé to headline Coachella music festival.", "tokens": ["Beyoncé", "to", "headline", "Coachella", "music", "festival", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Apple releases new iPhone with innovative 3D display technology.", "tokens": ["Apple", "releases", "new", "iPhone", "with", "innovative", "3D", "display", "technology", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Google launches AI-powered virtual assistant to compete with Amazon's Alexa.", "tokens": ["Google", "launches", "AI", "-", "powered", "virtual", "assistant", "to", "compete", "with", "Amazon", "'", "s", "Alexa", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tesla's new electric car achieves record-breaking range on single charge.", "tokens": ["Tesla", "'", "s", "new", "electric", "car", "achieves", "record", "-", "breaking", "range", "on", "single", "charge", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "NASA successfully launches new Mars rover.", "tokens": ["NASA", "successfully", "launches", "new", "Mars", "rover", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "SpaceX announces plans for first manned mission to Mars.", "tokens": ["SpaceX", "announces", "plans", "for", "first", "manned", "mission", "to", "Mars", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Police arrest suspect in connection with bank robbery in downtown Chicago.", "tokens": ["Police", "arrest", "suspect", "in", "connection", "with", "bank", "robbery", "in", "downtown", "Chicago", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Man sentenced to 20 years in prison for assault on elderly woman.", "tokens": ["Man", "sentenced", "to", "20", "years", "in", "prison", "for", "assault", "on", "elderly", "woman", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Authorities investigate string of car thefts in the Bronx.", "tokens": ["Authorities", "investigate", "string", "of", "car", "thefts", "in", "the", "Bronx", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Fashion designer Coco Chanel to be honored at annual industry gala.", "tokens": ["Fashion", "designer", "Coco", "Chanel", "to", "be", "honored", "at", "annual", "industry", "gala", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "High-end fashion retailer Gucci launches new sustainable clothing line.", "tokens": ["High", "-", "end", "fashion", "retailer", "Gucci", "launches", "new", "sustainable", "clothing", "line", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tesla announces plans to expand manufacturing facility in Texas.", "tokens": ["Tesla", "announces", "plans", "to", "expand", "manufacturing", "facility", "in", "Texas", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Ford recalls over 200,000 vehicles due to faulty airbag sensors.", "tokens": ["Ford", "recalls", "over", "200", ",", "000", "vehicles", "due", "to", "faulty", "airbag", "sensors", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Renowned automotive engineer Mary Barra appointed as CEO of General Motors.", "tokens": ["Renowned", "automotive", "engineer", "Mary", "Barra", "appointed", "as", "CEO", "of", "General", "Motors", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tesla announces record-breaking quarterly profits.", "tokens": ["Tesla", "announces", "record", "-", "breaking", "quarterly", "profits", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Stock market sees sharp decline after trade tensions escalate between United States and China.", "tokens": ["Stock", "market", "sees", "sharp", "decline", "after", "trade", "tensions", "escalate", "between", "United", "States", "and", "China", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Elon Musk appointed as CEO of new space exploration company.", "tokens": ["Elon", "Musk", "appointed", "as", "CEO", "of", "new", "space", "exploration", "company", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "CDC reports spike in flu cases in the Midwest.", "tokens": ["CDC", "reports", "spike", "in", "flu", "cases", "in", "the", "Midwest", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Dr. Patel appointed as new head of the World Health Organization.", "tokens": ["Dr", ".", "Patel", "appointed", "as", "new", "head", "of", "the", "World", "Health", "Organization", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O"]}
{"sentence": "New study shows link between air pollution and respiratory illnesses in urban areas.", "tokens": ["New", "study", "shows", "link", "between", "air", "pollution", "and", "respiratory", "illnesses", "in", "urban", "areas", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Murder rate in city hits 10-year high.", "tokens": ["Murder", "rate", "in", "city", "hits", "10", "-", "year", "high", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "FBI launches investigation into international drug trafficking ring.", "tokens": ["FBI", "launches", "investigation", "into", "international", "drug", "trafficking", "ring", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O"]}
{"sentence": "New report shows that the consumption of sugary drinks among teenagers has decreased by 15% in the past year.", "tokens": ["New", "report", "shows", "that", "the", "consumption", "of", "sugary", "drinks", "among", "teenagers", "has", "decreased", "by", "15", "%", "in", "the", "past", "year", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Fast food giant McDonald's announces plans to open 100 new locations in South America by the end of 2022.", "tokens": ["Fast", "food", "giant", "McDonald", "'", "s", "announces", "plans", "to", "open", "100", "new", "locations", "in", "South", "America", "by", "the", "end", "of", "2022", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Study finds that organic food sales have increased by 20% in the last quarter, indicating a growing trend towards healthier eating habits.", "tokens": ["Study", "finds", "that", "organic", "food", "sales", "have", "increased", "by", "20", "%", "in", "the", "last", "quarter", ",", "indicating", "a", "growing", "trend", "towards", "healthier", "eating", "habits", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "BREAKING: Mount Everest climber rescued after being stranded for three days in harsh weather conditions.", "tokens": ["BREAKING", ":", "Mount", "Everest", "climber", "rescued", "after", "being", "stranded", "for", "three", "days", "in", "harsh", "weather", "conditions", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tragic news as beloved actor and comedian passes away at the age of 77.", "tokens": ["Tragic", "news", "as", "beloved", "actor", "and", "comedian", "passes", "away", "at", "the", "age", "of", "77", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Major corporation announces plans to invest $1 billion in renewable energy initiatives.", "tokens": ["Major", "corporation", "announces", "plans", "to", "invest", "$", "1", "billion", "in", "renewable", "energy", "initiatives", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The stock market experiences a sharp decline in response to trade tensions with China.", "tokens": ["The", "stock", "market", "experiences", "a", "sharp", "decline", "in", "response", "to", "trade", "tensions", "with", "China", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Unemployment reaches a record low as job creation continues to outpace expectations.", "tokens": ["Unemployment", "reaches", "a", "record", "low", "as", "job", "creation", "continues", "to", "outpace", "expectations", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "NASA launches new Mars rover to search for signs of ancient life.", "tokens": ["NASA", "launches", "new", "Mars", "rover", "to", "search", "for", "signs", "of", "ancient", "life", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX company plans to send humans to Mars by 2026.", "tokens": ["Elon", "Musk", "'", "s", "SpaceX", "company", "plans", "to", "send", "humans", "to", "Mars", "by", "2026", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "International Space Station crew conducts research on growing food in microgravity.", "tokens": ["International", "Space", "Station", "crew", "conducts", "research", "on", "growing", "food", "in", "microgravity", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Local police department under investigation for possible corruption.", "tokens": ["Local", "police", "department", "under", "investigation", "for", "possible", "corruption", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "New restaurant to open in downtown area, bringing jobs and economic growth.", "tokens": ["New", "restaurant", "to", "open", "in", "downtown", "area", ",", "bringing", "jobs", "and", "economic", "growth", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Mayor's office announces new initiative to combat homelessness in the city.", "tokens": ["Mayor", "'", "s", "office", "announces", "new", "initiative", "to", "combat", "homelessness", "in", "the", "city", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The Federal Reserve announced an interest rate hike to combat inflation.", "tokens": ["The", "Federal", "Reserve", "announced", "an", "interest", "rate", "hike", "to", "combat", "inflation", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The trade dispute between the United States and China is causing market uncertainty.", "tokens": ["The", "trade", "dispute", "between", "the", "United", "States", "and", "China", "is", "causing", "market", "uncertainty", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The European Union's new economic stimulus plan aims to boost job creation and infrastructure investment.", "tokens": ["The", "European", "Union", "'", "s", "new", "economic", "stimulus", "plan", "aims", "to", "boost", "job", "creation", "and", "infrastructure", "investment", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Chinese President Xi Jinping meets with Indian Prime Minister Narendra Modi to discuss border tensions.", "tokens": ["Chinese", "President", "Xi", "Jinping", "meets", "with", "Indian", "Prime", "Minister", "Narendra", "Modi", "to", "discuss", "border", "tensions", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "United Nations peacekeeping forces deployed to conflict-ridden region in Africa.", "tokens": ["United", "Nations", "peacekeeping", "forces", "deployed", "to", "conflict", "-", "ridden", "region", "in", "Africa", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Amazon to open new distribution center in Texas.", "tokens": ["Amazon", "to", "open", "new", "distribution", "center", "in", "Texas", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Warren Buffett's Berkshire Hathaway invests $1 billion in new tech startup.", "tokens": ["Warren", "Buffett", "'", "s", "Berkshire", "Hathaway", "invests", "$", "1", "billion", "in", "new", "tech", "startup", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Health experts recommend at least 30 minutes of physical activity per day for a healthier lifestyle.", "tokens": ["Health", "experts", "recommend", "at", "least", "30", "minutes", "of", "physical", "activity", "per", "day", "for", "a", "healthier", "lifestyle", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Organic food sales continue to rise globally, as consumers prioritize a healthier lifestyle.", "tokens": ["Organic", "food", "sales", "continue", "to", "rise", "globally", ",", "as", "consumers", "prioritize", "a", "healthier", "lifestyle", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The Federal Reserve announces interest rate hike to curb inflation.", "tokens": ["The", "Federal", "Reserve", "announces", "interest", "rate", "hike", "to", "curb", "inflation", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "China's economy experiences record growth despite global market uncertainties.", "tokens": ["China", "'", "s", "economy", "experiences", "record", "growth", "despite", "global", "market", "uncertainties", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Global economic summit in Davos focuses on sustainable development and trade partnerships.", "tokens": ["Global", "economic", "summit", "in", "Davos", "focuses", "on", "sustainable", "development", "and", "trade", "partnerships", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Police arrest two suspects in connection to bank robbery.", "tokens": ["Police", "arrest", "two", "suspects", "in", "connection", "to", "bank", "robbery", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Murder investigation underway in downtown Chicago.", "tokens": ["Murder", "investigation", "underway", "in", "downtown", "Chicago", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Federal agents raid home of notorious drug lord.", "tokens": ["Federal", "agents", "raid", "home", "of", "notorious", "drug", "lord", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Immigrant family reunites after years apart.", "tokens": ["Immigrant", "family", "reunites", "after", "years", "apart", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Immigrant community celebrates cultural heritage festival.", "tokens": ["Immigrant", "community", "celebrates", "cultural", "heritage", "festival", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tesla surpasses Toyota to become the world's most valuable car company.", "tokens": ["Tesla", "surpasses", "Toyota", "to", "become", "the", "world", "'", "s", "most", "valuable", "car", "company", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Amazon's Jeff Bezos becomes the first person in history to amass a fortune of over $200 billion.", "tokens": ["Amazon", "'", "s", "Jeff", "Bezos", "becomes", "the", "first", "person", "in", "history", "to", "amass", "a", "fortune", "of", "over", "$", "200", "billion", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Wall Street hits record highs as tech stocks continue to surge.", "tokens": ["Wall", "Street", "hits", "record", "highs", "as", "tech", "stocks", "continue", "to", "surge", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The new film festival promises to showcase the best of independent cinema from around the world.", "tokens": ["The", "new", "film", "festival", "promises", "to", "showcase", "the", "best", "of", "independent", "cinema", "from", "around", "the", "world", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Rumors of a potential new collaboration between the acclaimed director and a popular Hollywood actress have been swirling in the industry.", "tokens": ["Rumors", "of", "a", "potential", "new", "collaboration", "between", "the", "acclaimed", "director", "and", "a", "popular", "Hollywood", "actress", "have", "been", "swirling", "in", "the", "industry", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-person", "O", "O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The film production company announced the launch of a new initiative to support up-and-coming filmmakers from underrepresented communities.", "tokens": ["The", "film", "production", "company", "announced", "the", "launch", "of", "a", "new", "initiative", "to", "support", "up", "-", "and", "-", "coming", "filmmakers", "from", "underrepresented", "communities", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "LeBron James leads Lakers to victory against the Warriors.", "tokens": ["LeBron", "James", "leads", "Lakers", "to", "victory", "against", "the", "Warriors", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tokyo Olympics postponed due to COVID-19 pandemic.", "tokens": ["Tokyo", "Olympics", "postponed", "due", "to", "COVID", "-", "19", "pandemic", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Serena Williams wins her 23rd Grand Slam title at Australian Open.", "tokens": ["Serena", "Williams", "wins", "her", "23rd", "Grand", "Slam", "title", "at", "Australian", "Open", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O"]}
{"sentence": "McDonald's introduces new plant-based burger to its menu.", "tokens": ["McDonald", "'", "s", "introduces", "new", "plant", "-", "based", "burger", "to", "its", "menu", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "FDA recalls contaminated lettuce from California farms.", "tokens": ["FDA", "recalls", "contaminated", "lettuce", "from", "California", "farms", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Local chef wins prestigious culinary award at international competition.", "tokens": ["Local", "chef", "wins", "prestigious", "culinary", "award", "at", "international", "competition", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Harvard University announces new scholarship program for low-income students.", "tokens": ["Harvard", "University", "announces", "new", "scholarship", "program", "for", "low", "-", "income", "students", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Principal Smith resigns from Lincoln High School amidst controversy.", "tokens": ["Principal", "Smith", "resigns", "from", "Lincoln", "High", "School", "amidst", "controversy", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Education department allocates $10 million for STEM education in rural schools.", "tokens": ["Education", "department", "allocates", "$", "10", "million", "for", "STEM", "education", "in", "rural", "schools", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tesla's CEO Elon Musk announces plans to build a new Gigafactory in Texas.", "tokens": ["Tesla", "'", "s", "CEO", "Elon", "Musk", "announces", "plans", "to", "build", "a", "new", "Gigafactory", "in", "Texas", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "After a successful IPO, the startup company secured $50 million in funding from venture capitalists.", "tokens": ["After", "a", "successful", "IPO", ",", "the", "startup", "company", "secured", "$", "50", "million", "in", "funding", "from", "venture", "capitalists", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The global retail giant Amazon reports record-breaking quarterly profits.", "tokens": ["The", "global", "retail", "giant", "Amazon", "reports", "record", "-", "breaking", "quarterly", "profits", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Author J.K. Rowling to release new children's book.", "tokens": ["Author", "J", ".", "K", ".", "Rowling", "to", "release", "new", "children", "'", "s", "book", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-person", "I-person", "I-person", "I-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The Nobel Prize in Literature awarded to American poet Louise Glück.", "tokens": ["The", "Nobel", "Prize", "in", "Literature", "awarded", "to", "American", "poet", "Louise", "Glück", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Up-and-coming author from London secures major book deal.", "tokens": ["Up", "-", "and", "-", "coming", "author", "from", "London", "secures", "major", "book", "deal", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Facebook faces criticism over its handling of user data privacy issues.", "tokens": ["Facebook", "faces", "criticism", "over", "its", "handling", "of", "user", "data", "privacy", "issues", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Hurricane Elsa to bring heavy rain and strong winds to the Caribbean.", "tokens": ["Hurricane", "Elsa", "to", "bring", "heavy", "rain", "and", "strong", "winds", "to", "the", "Caribbean", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Record-breaking heatwave continues to scorch the western United States.", "tokens": ["Record", "-", "breaking", "heatwave", "continues", "to", "scorch", "the", "western", "United", "States", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tropical storm brewing in the Gulf of Mexico, poses potential threat to coastal areas.", "tokens": ["Tropical", "storm", "brewing", "in", "the", "Gulf", "of", "Mexico", ",", "poses", "potential", "threat", "to", "coastal", "areas", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The Pope visits Jerusalem to promote interfaith dialogue.", "tokens": ["The", "Pope", "visits", "Jerusalem", "to", "promote", "interfaith", "dialogue", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Hindu temple in Bangladesh vandalized by unknown assailants.", "tokens": ["Hindu", "temple", "in", "Bangladesh", "vandalized", "by", "unknown", "assailants", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Buddhist monks in Thailand protest government's interference in religious affairs.", "tokens": ["Buddhist", "monks", "in", "Thailand", "protest", "government", "'", "s", "interference", "in", "religious", "affairs", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Local High School Wins State Championship in Basketball.", "tokens": ["Local", "High", "School", "Wins", "State", "Championship", "in", "Basketball", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "New Community Center to Open in Downtown Area Next Month.", "tokens": ["New", "Community", "Center", "to", "Open", "in", "Downtown", "Area", "Next", "Month", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Mayor Smith Officially Declares Climate Change Emergency in City Council Meeting.", "tokens": ["Mayor", "Smith", "Officially", "Declares", "Climate", "Change", "Emergency", "in", "City", "Council", "Meeting", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The famous painter Pablo Picasso's masterpiece stolen from the Louvre Museum has been recovered by authorities.", "tokens": ["The", "famous", "painter", "Pablo", "Picasso", "'", "s", "masterpiece", "stolen", "from", "the", "Louvre", "Museum", "has", "been", "recovered", "by", "authorities", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The Metropolitan Museum of Art in New York City unveils a new exhibit featuring contemporary female artists.", "tokens": ["The", "Metropolitan", "Museum", "of", "Art", "in", "New", "York", "City", "unveils", "a", "new", "exhibit", "featuring", "contemporary", "female", "artists", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Renowned sculptor Ai Weiwei donates a collection of his works to the Tate Modern museum in London.", "tokens": ["Renowned", "sculptor", "Ai", "Weiwei", "donates", "a", "collection", "of", "his", "works", "to", "the", "Tate", "Modern", "museum", "in", "London", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Pope Francis visits the United Arab Emirates for a historic interfaith conference.", "tokens": ["Pope", "Francis", "visits", "the", "United", "Arab", "Emirates", "for", "a", "historic", "interfaith", "conference", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Church of Scientology announces plans to open new headquarters in South Korea.", "tokens": ["Church", "of", "Scientology", "announces", "plans", "to", "open", "new", "headquarters", "in", "South", "Korea", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Prominent rabbi calls for unity among different religious communities in response to recent hate crimes.", "tokens": ["Prominent", "rabbi", "calls", "for", "unity", "among", "different", "religious", "communities", "in", "response", "to", "recent", "hate", "crimes", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Director Ava DuVernay to produce new film about civil rights icon.", "tokens": ["Director", "Ava", "DuVernay", "to", "produce", "new", "film", "about", "civil", "rights", "icon", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The upcoming film festival in Cannes to feature a special screening of Quentin Tarantino's latest movie.", "tokens": ["The", "upcoming", "film", "festival", "in", "Cannes", "to", "feature", "a", "special", "screening", "of", "Quentin", "Tarantino", "'", "s", "latest", "movie", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Disney's highly anticipated animated film breaks box office records on opening weekend.", "tokens": ["Disney", "'", "s", "highly", "anticipated", "animated", "film", "breaks", "box", "office", "records", "on", "opening", "weekend", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Kim Kardashian launches new beauty line.", "tokens": ["Kim", "Kardashian", "launches", "new", "beauty", "line", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Taylor Swift breaks record with latest album.", "tokens": ["Taylor", "Swift", "breaks", "record", "with", "latest", "album", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Beyoncé to headline music festival this summer.", "tokens": ["Beyoncé", "to", "headline", "music", "festival", "this", "summer", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "FDA approves new drug for treatment of high blood pressure.", "tokens": ["FDA", "approves", "new", "drug", "for", "treatment", "of", "high", "blood", "pressure", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Renowned cardiologist Dr. Jane Smith appointed as head of new research institute.", "tokens": ["Renowned", "cardiologist", "Dr", ".", "Jane", "Smith", "appointed", "as", "head", "of", "new", "research", "institute", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "I-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Immigration reform bill passes Senate, faces uncertain future in the House.", "tokens": ["Immigration", "reform", "bill", "passes", "Senate", ",", "faces", "uncertain", "future", "in", "the", "House", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O"]}
{"sentence": "New immigration policy leads to surge in applications for citizenship.", "tokens": ["New", "immigration", "policy", "leads", "to", "surge", "in", "applications", "for", "citizenship", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Protesters gather outside immigration detention center to demand better conditions for detainees.", "tokens": ["Protesters", "gather", "outside", "immigration", "detention", "center", "to", "demand", "better", "conditions", "for", "detainees", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Taylor Swift's new album 'Red (Taylor's Version)' tops the charts.", "tokens": ["Taylor", "Swift", "'", "s", "new", "album", "'", "Red", "(", "Taylor", "'", "s", "Version", ")", "'", "tops", "the", "charts", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The Cannes Film Festival announces its lineup for this year's event.", "tokens": ["The", "Cannes", "Film", "Festival", "announces", "its", "lineup", "for", "this", "year", "'", "s", "event", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Actor Tom Hanks to star in upcoming biopic about Fred Rogers.", "tokens": ["Actor", "Tom", "Hanks", "to", "star", "in", "upcoming", "biopic", "about", "Fred", "Rogers", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Local hero saves drowning child in dramatic rescue.", "tokens": ["Local", "hero", "saves", "drowning", "child", "in", "dramatic", "rescue", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Community comes together to support homeless shelter in time for winter.", "tokens": ["Community", "comes", "together", "to", "support", "homeless", "shelter", "in", "time", "for", "winter", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Former refugee opens successful business to give back to her community.", "tokens": ["Former", "refugee", "opens", "successful", "business", "to", "give", "back", "to", "her", "community", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Local artist to showcase traditional dances at cultural festival.", "tokens": ["Local", "artist", "to", "showcase", "traditional", "dances", "at", "cultural", "festival", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Museum to host exhibit on ancient civilization artifacts.", "tokens": ["Museum", "to", "host", "exhibit", "on", "ancient", "civilization", "artifacts", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Celebrated chef to open new restaurant featuring fusion cuisine.", "tokens": ["Celebrated", "chef", "to", "open", "new", "restaurant", "featuring", "fusion", "cuisine", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Pope Francis calls for global solidarity in the face of religious intolerance.", "tokens": ["Pope", "Francis", "calls", "for", "global", "solidarity", "in", "the", "face", "of", "religious", "intolerance", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Buddhist monks protest government's intervention in religious affairs.", "tokens": ["Buddhist", "monks", "protest", "government", "'", "s", "intervention", "in", "religious", "affairs", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
