[
  {
    "sentence": "The European Union is considering imposing tariffs on American products.",
    "span": "European Union",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0012934011134000001
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The European Union is considering imposing tariffs on American products.",
    "span": "American",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.046656537649999996
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX successfully launches another batch of Starlink satellites.",
    "span": "Elon Musk",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -4.5431403500000006e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX successfully launches another batch of Starlink satellites.",
    "span": "SpaceX",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.48564876628055004
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The protests in Hong Kong continue to escalate as tensions rise between the government and demonstrators.",
    "span": "Hong Kong",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -8.326976426e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The World Health Organization warns of a potential Ebola outbreak in the Democratic Republic of Congo.",
    "span": "World Health Organization",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -1.9862216766666666e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The World Health Organization warns of a potential Ebola outbreak in the Democratic Republic of Congo.",
    "span": "Ebola",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.10552703584425001
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Amazon announces plans to open a new fulfillment center, creating 2,000 jobs in the local community.",
    "span": "Amazon",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0032835927501
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Taylor Swift releases her highly anticipated album, \"Fearless (Taylor's Version).\"",
    "span": "Taylor Swift",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0005604448292
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The United Nations urges immediate action to address the humanitarian crisis in Yemen.",
    "span": "United Nations",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -3.581020014000001e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The United Nations urges immediate action to address the humanitarian crisis in Yemen.",
    "span": "Yemen",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00193066153425
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The Los Angeles Lakers defeat the Brooklyn Nets in a thrilling overtime game.",
    "span": "Los Angeles Lakers",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0166273715085
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The Los Angeles Lakers defeat the Brooklyn Nets in a thrilling overtime game.",
    "span": "Brooklyn Nets",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0125237629524
  },
  {
    "sentence": "President Joe Biden signs an executive order to address climate change and promote clean energy.",
    "span": "Joe Biden",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0010571112998
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The Tokyo Olympics are facing uncertainty as concerns over the COVID-19 pandemic persist.",
    "span": "Tokyo",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0034749070107300004
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The Tokyo Olympics are facing uncertainty as concerns over the COVID-19 pandemic persist.",
    "span": "Olympics",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.09141366580424999
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The Tokyo Olympics are facing uncertainty as concerns over the COVID-19 pandemic persist.",
    "span": "COVID-19",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.17546660157586666
  },
  {
    "sentence": "TikTok faces scrutiny over data privacy concerns and potential national security risks.",
    "span": "TikTok",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0011570267608166666
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Meghan Markle and Prince Harry announce their decision to step back from their royal duties.",
    "span": "Meghan Markle",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -4.480984185714285e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Meghan Markle and Prince Harry announce their decision to step back from their royal duties.",
    "span": "Prince Harry",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.026237487925999996
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The United States imposes sanctions on Russia following the suspected poisoning of Alexei Navalny.",
    "span": "United States",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.002501693605
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The United States imposes sanctions on Russia following the suspected poisoning of Alexei Navalny.",
    "span": "Russia",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00040310755675
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The United States imposes sanctions on Russia following the suspected poisoning of Alexei Navalny.",
    "span": "Alexei Navalny",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.009054474759857142
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tesla's stock prices surge as the company reports record-breaking sales and profits.",
    "span": "Tesla",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.004465474933750001
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The United Nations Security Council condemns the recent terrorist attacks in Nigeria.",
    "span": "United Nations Security Council",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.005072294918285715
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The United Nations Security Council condemns the recent terrorist attacks in Nigeria.",
    "span": "Nigeria",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.127542815722325
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tesla CEO Elon Musk announces plans to build a new gigafactory in Texas.",
    "span": "Tesla",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0037498206950000003
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tesla CEO Elon Musk announces plans to build a new gigafactory in Texas.",
    "span": "Elon Musk",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.000223513431
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tesla CEO Elon Musk announces plans to build a new gigafactory in Texas.",
    "span": "Texas",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.013729140197750001
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The World Bank approves a $500 million loan to support education reform in India.",
    "span": "World Bank",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -1.9290039260000002e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The World Bank approves a $500 million loan to support education reform in India.",
    "span": "India",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0021503099299999997
  },
  {
    "sentence": "South Korea hosts a virtual summit with leaders from ASEAN countries to strengthen economic cooperation.",
    "span": "South Korea",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00010909001200000001
  },
  {
    "sentence": "South Korea hosts a virtual summit with leaders from ASEAN countries to strengthen economic cooperation.",
    "span": "ASEAN",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0005036091745000001
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The European Central Bank announces an expansion of its stimulus program to support the economy.",
    "span": "European Central Bank",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.4541893908068833
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Wildfires continue to devastate parts of California.",
    "span": "California",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00109199322175
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Pfizer announces plans for booster shots in response to new COVID variants.",
    "span": "Pfizer",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.08009259146596667
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Serena Williams withdraws from Wimbledon due to injury.",
    "span": "Serena Williams",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0036049639584166664
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Serena Williams withdraws from Wimbledon due to injury.",
    "span": "Wimbledon",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.002848863555
  },
  {
    "sentence": "United Nations report shows increase in global poverty rates.",
    "span": "United Nations",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00015861454966
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tech giant Apple introduces new line of products.",
    "span": "Apple",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0001181254654
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Prime Minister Trudeau visits Indigenous community in northern Canada.",
    "span": "Trudeau",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.00029055106178
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Prime Minister Trudeau visits Indigenous community in northern Canada.",
    "span": "Indigenous",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.154210405167
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Prime Minister Trudeau visits Indigenous community in northern Canada.",
    "span": "Canada",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.1166059015275
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Record-breaking heatwave hits Western Europe.",
    "span": "Western Europe",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.234853200308
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Apple Inc. unveils latest iPhone model.",
    "span": "Apple Inc.",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.02759875316371667
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tropical storm makes landfall in Florida.",
    "span": "Florida",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0001148303985
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX launches satellite into orbit.",
    "span": "Elon Musk",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -3.6886639116666666e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "United Nations issues statement on human rights violations in Myanmar.",
    "span": "United Nations",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -3.3926781220000006e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "United Nations issues statement on human rights violations in Myanmar.",
    "span": "Myanmar",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.000418157933075
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Simone Biles wins gold in gymnastics competition.",
    "span": "Simone Biles",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -7.010355175714287e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Google announces partnership with local schools to promote computer science education.",
    "span": "Google",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -9.2413689575e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Former President Obama visits Kenya for charity work.",
    "span": "President Obama",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.23796588147319997
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Former President Obama visits Kenya for charity work.",
    "span": "Kenya",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0003176958025
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Wildfires continue to ravage California forests.",
    "span": "California",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.033584361674
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Amazon to open new distribution center in Texas.",
    "span": "Amazon",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -2.3021113825000002e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Amazon to open new distribution center in Texas.",
    "span": "Texas",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0006230994242499999
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Beyoncé releases new album.",
    "span": "Beyoncé",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.00045355007005
  },
  {
    "sentence": "European Union imposes sanctions on Russia for human rights abuses.",
    "span": "European Union",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -2.253237982e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "European Union imposes sanctions on Russia for human rights abuses.",
    "span": "Russia",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.003343992803
  },
  {
    "sentence": "New York City to implement new public transportation system.",
    "span": "New York City",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00087680953475
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Greta Thunberg speaks at climate change conference in Switzerland.",
    "span": "Greta Thunberg",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -2.36171327125e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Greta Thunberg speaks at climate change conference in Switzerland.",
    "span": "Switzerland",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0018601057809999998
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Toyota announces recall of over 1 million vehicles.",
    "span": "Toyota",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.000860768445075
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Hurricane hits coastal town in Louisiana.",
    "span": "Louisiana",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0010824152792000001
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Researchers discover new species of dinosaur in South America.",
    "span": "South America",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0008285378145999999
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Taylor Swift performs at sold-out concert in London.",
    "span": "Taylor Swift",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -3.83387848e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Taylor Swift performs at sold-out concert in London.",
    "span": "London",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00414581826375
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Microsoft CEO steps down from position.",
    "span": "Microsoft",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.001486222834
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Australia experiences record-breaking heatwave.",
    "span": "Australia",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0016402887665
  },
  {
    "sentence": "LeBron James signs multi-million dollar contract with new team.",
    "span": "LeBron James",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0003936672868333333
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Alibaba founder faces investigation for alleged financial misconduct.",
    "span": "Alibaba",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00086093894248
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Mount Everest climbers stranded in severe snowstorm.",
    "span": "Mount Everest",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0006757050286
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Taylor Jenkins named head coach of NBA team.",
    "span": "Taylor Jenkins",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0004327541159
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Taylor Jenkins named head coach of NBA team.",
    "span": "NBA",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00043849871075
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Thousands protest for democracy in Hong Kong.",
    "span": "Hong Kong",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00034617552386
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Warren Buffett donates $1 billion to charity.",
    "span": "Warren Buffett",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.00043776925783333326
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Ford to invest in new electric vehicle technology.",
    "span": "Ford",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00010555039839999999
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Severe drought threatens crops in Midwest.",
    "span": "Midwest",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0002886863424
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Jennifer Lawrence to star in upcoming film.",
    "span": "Jennifer Lawrence",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -7.14267858e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "World Health Organization issues warning about new strain of flu virus.",
    "span": "World Health Organization",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -4.49527543e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "New York Yankees win World Series.",
    "span": "New York Yankees",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.007112077897666667
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Duchess of Cambridge visits children's hospital in London.",
    "span": "Duchess of Cambridge",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.00028706922362499996
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Duchess of Cambridge visits children's hospital in London.",
    "span": "London",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0023012817914999997
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Uber to launch new food delivery service.",
    "span": "Uber",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -2.01006246e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Scientists confirm presence of water on Mars.",
    "span": "Mars",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00017299271606
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Singer Rihanna starts new fashion line.",
    "span": "Rihanna",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0004161436706
  },
  {
    "sentence": "United Airlines to add new routes to Europe.",
    "span": "United Airlines",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00020646952086000002
  },
  {
    "sentence": "United Airlines to add new routes to Europe.",
    "span": "Europe",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0005819240775000001
  },
  {
    "sentence": "FBI warns of potential cyberattack on government agencies.",
    "span": "FBI",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -1.821720612e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Italian restaurant chain announces expansion to Asia.",
    "span": "Asia",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.2034353746125
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Prince Harry and Meghan Markle visit Africa for charity work.",
    "span": "Prince Harry",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -8.11299656e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Prince Harry and Meghan Markle visit Africa for charity work.",
    "span": "Meghan Markle",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -6.990544366666667e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Prince Harry and Meghan Markle visit Africa for charity work.",
    "span": "Africa",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0006399781775
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Facebook launches new initiative to combat misinformation.",
    "span": "Facebook",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0032790388307500002
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Iran announces plan to increase uranium enrichment.",
    "span": "Iran",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.000806455901
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Nobel Peace Prize awarded to humanitarian organization for work in conflict zones.",
    "span": "Nobel Peace Prize",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.003142804224785714
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Severe flooding hits coastal town in Japan.",
    "span": "Japan",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.45054977866
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Apple announces new iPhone 13 launch date.",
    "span": "Apple",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.019139537102
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Prime Minister Johnson meets with French President Macron.",
    "span": "Johnson",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.40568076345265003
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Prime Minister Johnson meets with French President Macron.",
    "span": "Macron",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0005216945775
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Hurricane hits Florida, causing widespread damage.",
    "span": "Florida",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0001904811642
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Amazon faces lawsuit over worker conditions.",
    "span": "Amazon",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -4.814053726e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Elon Musk plans to visit SpaceX headquarters.",
    "span": "Elon Musk",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -3.5895109999999995e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Elon Musk plans to visit SpaceX headquarters.",
    "span": "SpaceX",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00025316995950000004
  },
  {
    "sentence": "New York City imposes vaccine mandate for indoor activities.",
    "span": "New York City",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -8.882795746666666e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "President Biden unveils new infrastructure plan.",
    "span": "Biden",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.00255538202358
  },
  {
    "sentence": "COVID-19 cases surge in California.",
    "span": "California",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.334824992125
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Facebook to launch new virtual reality headset.",
    "span": "Facebook",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.000130222808
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tiger Woods returns to golf after injury.",
    "span": "Tiger Woods",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0030587402986666664
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Wildfires continue to ravage Australian countryside.",
    "span": "Australian",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.022430148575
  },
  {
    "sentence": "CEO of Microsoft steps down after 20 years.",
    "span": "Microsoft",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00243169220775
  },
  {
    "sentence": "German Chancellor Merkel wins reelection.",
    "span": "Merkel",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.03353596680710833
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tokyo Olympics conclude after two-week event.",
    "span": "Tokyo",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00979973684744
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tesla announces record-breaking quarterly profits.",
    "span": "Tesla",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0004885771355
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Los Angeles Lakers sign new star player.",
    "span": "Los Angeles",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.5250252514096
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Russian President Putin meets with Chinese leader Xi.",
    "span": "Putin",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -4.0693058e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Russian President Putin meets with Chinese leader Xi.",
    "span": "Xi",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.019142901584924998
  },
  {
    "sentence": "NASA launches new rover to explore Mars.",
    "span": "NASA",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00258027231275
  },
  {
    "sentence": "NASA launches new rover to explore Mars.",
    "span": "Mars",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00452446770325
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Pfizer seeks approval for COVID-19 vaccine booster.",
    "span": "Pfizer",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0314379507002
  },
  {
    "sentence": "London experiences heavy flooding after rainstorm.",
    "span": "London",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0015907258649999999
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Goldman Sachs CEO testifies before Congress.",
    "span": "Goldman Sachs",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.021763070232666663
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Syrian refugees stranded at border.",
    "span": "Syrian",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0004358668962
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Famous chef opens new restaurant in Paris.",
    "span": "Paris",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00059449548925
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Federal Reserve announces interest rate hike.",
    "span": "Federal Reserve",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0266788920344
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Canadian Prime Minister Trudeau faces backlash over pipeline decision.",
    "span": "Canadian",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.355966675727
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Canadian Prime Minister Trudeau faces backlash over pipeline decision.",
    "span": "Trudeau",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.021225194362999997
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Mumbai hit by massive power outage.",
    "span": "Mumbai",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00034766498280000004
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Anti-government protests erupt in Hong Kong.",
    "span": "Hong Kong",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.008895187329
  },
  {
    "sentence": "CEO of Amazon donates millions to charity.",
    "span": "Amazon",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0025300533905
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Violent clashes between police and protesters in Barcelona.",
    "span": "Barcelona",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00013039482126000001
  },
  {
    "sentence": "United Nations peacekeepers deployed to conflict zone in Africa.",
    "span": "United Nations",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -9.914915400000002e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "United Nations peacekeepers deployed to conflict zone in Africa.",
    "span": "Africa",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00026288871
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Egyptian archaeologists discover ancient tombs.",
    "span": "Egyptian",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0011035641346
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Google unveils new AI technology for healthcare.",
    "span": "Google",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00015606982785
  },
  {
    "sentence": "FBI warns of potential cyberattack on U.S. infrastructure.",
    "span": "FBI",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.007636079243380001
  },
  {
    "sentence": "FBI warns of potential cyberattack on U.S. infrastructure.",
    "span": "U.S.",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.000286280591
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Italy imposes new COVID-19 restrictions.",
    "span": "Italy",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0002005176585
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Starbucks announces plan to phase out plastic straws.",
    "span": "Starbucks",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -3.8241955066e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Violence erupts in Ukraine-Russia border region.",
    "span": "Ukraine",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00065790600078
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Violence erupts in Ukraine-Russia border region.",
    "span": "Russia",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00016824969375
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Japan to host 2021 Summer Olympics.",
    "span": "Japan",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0006353756325
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Hollywood actress files lawsuit against tabloid magazine.",
    "span": "Hollywood",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -5.2333294659999995e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "U.N. Secretary-General calls for global ceasefire.",
    "span": "U.N. Secretary-General",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.30193105400650005
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Thousands evacuated as volcano erupts in Indonesia.",
    "span": "Indonesia",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0001089737412
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Twitter suspends accounts linked to misinformation.",
    "span": "Twitter",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -1.6345709499999998e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Germany announces new climate action plan.",
    "span": "Germany",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -7.186298325e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Warren Buffett donates billions to charity.",
    "span": "Warren Buffett",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.00028788803116666667
  },
  {
    "sentence": "South Korea reports record high daily COVID-19 cases.",
    "span": "South Korea",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0001717540988
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Paris Agreement anniversary marked with climate rallies worldwide.",
    "span": "Paris Agreement",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.005967526189
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Apple announces launch of new iPhone.",
    "span": "Apple",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.10691778154125
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Earthquake hits Los Angeles, causing minor damages.",
    "span": "Los Angeles",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -6.3893114e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Facebook to acquire virtual reality company for $2 billion.",
    "span": "Facebook",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -2.162047145e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX to send astronauts to Mars by 2024.",
    "span": "Elon Musk",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0003656471362666667
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX to send astronauts to Mars by 2024.",
    "span": "SpaceX",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00095987927985
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tropical storm warning in effect for Florida coast.",
    "span": "Florida",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -9.84334827e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Amazon faces antitrust investigation in Europe.",
    "span": "Amazon",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.003678521290875
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Amazon faces antitrust investigation in Europe.",
    "span": "Europe",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0003606086695
  },
  {
    "sentence": "New York City to implement vaccine mandate for indoor activities.",
    "span": "New York City",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -4.1436246399999994e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "CEO of Microsoft steps down amid controversy.",
    "span": "Microsoft",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.030288153819250003
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Wildfire destroys homes in California.",
    "span": "California",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0141677974655
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Marie Curie's Nobel Prize medal sells for record-breaking price.",
    "span": "Marie Curie",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0007858329473571428
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tokyo Olympics committee announces new COVID-19 protocols.",
    "span": "Tokyo",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0060207457736
  },
  {
    "sentence": "United Nations to hold emergency meeting on humanitarian crisis in Yemen.",
    "span": "United Nations",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -1.2352387e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "United Nations to hold emergency meeting on humanitarian crisis in Yemen.",
    "span": "Yemen",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0031431877469749996
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Johnson & Johnson faces lawsuit over opioid crisis.",
    "span": "Johnson & Johnson",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -8.920237711666666e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Hollywood actress Jennifer Lawrence to star in new film.",
    "span": "Hollywood",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0586397715032
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Hollywood actress Jennifer Lawrence to star in new film.",
    "span": "Jennifer Lawrence",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.00034110422715
  },
  {
    "sentence": "European Union introduces new regulations for plastic waste.",
    "span": "European Union",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00011808567579999999
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Hurricane warning issued for Gulf Coast states.",
    "span": "Gulf Coast",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00031660328055
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Nobel Peace Prize awarded to climate activist Greta Thunberg.",
    "span": "Nobel Peace Prize",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00332267939
  },
  {
    "sentence": "New York City Mayor announces new policy on recycling.",
    "span": "New York City",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.010327174817833332
  },
  {
    "sentence": "New York City Mayor announces new policy on recycling.",
    "span": "Mayor",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.008397935708000001
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Apple Inc. unveils the new iPhone 13.",
    "span": "Apple Inc.",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.055284851257106665
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Global warming Summit to be held in Paris.",
    "span": "Paris",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.015167460230500002
  },
  {
    "sentence": "President Biden to meet with G7 leaders next week.",
    "span": "President Biden",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.06172508185779999
  },
  {
    "sentence": "President Biden to meet with G7 leaders next week.",
    "span": "G7",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00027133613692000003
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Massive wildfire destroys homes in California.",
    "span": "California",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00029330170750000004
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Paris Fashion Week announces new designers.",
    "span": "Paris",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00410529104825
  },
  {
    "sentence": "United Nations releases report on global hunger crisis.",
    "span": "United Nations",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0441273829508
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Celebrity couple files for divorce.",
    "span": "celebrity",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.2513139396117167
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Google to expand its headquarters in Silicon Valley.",
    "span": "Google",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -6.1520227e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Google to expand its headquarters in Silicon Valley.",
    "span": "Silicon Valley",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0016531843126
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Hurricane hits Florida coast.",
    "span": "Florida",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0009137625077500001
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Prince Harry and Meghan Markle welcome their second child.",
    "span": "Prince Harry",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.005199390225400001
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Prince Harry and Meghan Markle welcome their second child.",
    "span": "Meghan Markle",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0007424205753333333
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Sydney Opera House to host international music festival.",
    "span": "Sydney Opera House",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.017706211883857143
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Amazon CEO Jeff Bezos steps down from his position.",
    "span": "Amazon",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00012075161825
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Amazon CEO Jeff Bezos steps down from his position.",
    "span": "Jeff Bezos",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.004873111796233333
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Delta variant of COVID-19 spreads rapidly in Texas.",
    "span": "Delta",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.03436807106
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Delta variant of COVID-19 spreads rapidly in Texas.",
    "span": "Texas",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.014161998939
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Famous chef opens new restaurant in London.",
    "span": "London",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.22298221433725
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Pfizer and BioNTech develop new vaccine for coronavirus.",
    "span": "Pfizer",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -1.4835796316666668e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Pfizer and BioNTech develop new vaccine for coronavirus.",
    "span": "BioNTech",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.009921387620333334
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Ohio State University to require COVID-19 vaccinations for all students.",
    "span": "Ohio State University",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -9.838717366666666e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tokyo Olympics announce new safety protocols for athletes.",
    "span": "Tokyo",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.006087323321300001
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tokyo Olympics announce new safety protocols for athletes.",
    "span": "Olympics",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00083286041895
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Soccer star Cristiano Ronaldo signs new contract with Manchester United.",
    "span": "Cristiano Ronaldo",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -7.497282169285715e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Soccer star Cristiano Ronaldo signs new contract with Manchester United.",
    "span": "Manchester United",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0005786404364
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Bill Gates donates $1 million to charity.",
    "span": "Bill Gates",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0205725265964
  },
  {
    "sentence": "New York Stock Exchange experiences record-breaking gains.",
    "span": "New York Stock Exchange",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.13278835344114287
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Paris Hilton launches new fashion line.",
    "span": "Paris Hilton",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0184666939816
  },
  {
    "sentence": "United States imposes new sanctions on Russia.",
    "span": "United States",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00030422388119999996
  },
  {
    "sentence": "United States imposes new sanctions on Russia.",
    "span": "Russia",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00089600114825
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Pop singer Taylor Swift releases new album.",
    "span": "Taylor Swift",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0003411297378
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Microsoft to acquire gaming company Bethesda.",
    "span": "Microsoft",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00010925580075000001
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Microsoft to acquire gaming company Bethesda.",
    "span": "Bethesda",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.04518141285075
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Former President Obama to write a memoir.",
    "span": "President Obama",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.014721999286000001
  },
  {
    "sentence": "London Marathon raises millions for charity.",
    "span": "London",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.012805937347
  },
  {
    "sentence": "In-N-Out Burger opens new location in Arizona.",
    "span": "In-N-Out Burger",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0026603846402857142
  },
  {
    "sentence": "In-N-Out Burger opens new location in Arizona.",
    "span": "Arizona",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0009264729745
  },
  {
    "sentence": "High-speed rail project approved for construction in California.",
    "span": "California",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0006276020795
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Fashion designer Karl Lagerfeld passes away at 85.",
    "span": "Karl Lagerfeld",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.00011399461197142856
  },
  {
    "sentence": "American actress Angelina Jolie visits Syrian refugee camp.",
    "span": "Angelina Jolie",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.035444830917757145
  },
  {
    "sentence": "American actress Angelina Jolie visits Syrian refugee camp.",
    "span": "Syrian",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.02478534715
  },
  {
    "sentence": "SpaceX founder Elon Musk plans trip to space.",
    "span": "SpaceX",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00012323967660000002
  },
  {
    "sentence": "SpaceX founder Elon Musk plans trip to space.",
    "span": "Elon Musk",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.00012962385919999998
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Apple Store robbed in downtown Chicago.",
    "span": "Apple Store",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.006409921973200001
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Apple Store robbed in downtown Chicago.",
    "span": "Chicago",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00041912667225
  },
  {
    "sentence": "World Bank warns of economic downturn in developing countries.",
    "span": "World Bank",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -4.863504544e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "New York Yankees defeat Boston Red Sox in extra innings.",
    "span": "New York Yankees",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00019355267066666667
  },
  {
    "sentence": "New York Yankees defeat Boston Red Sox in extra innings.",
    "span": "Boston Red Sox",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.002572790981833333
  },
  {
    "sentence": "South Africa imposes strict lockdown measures to curb COVID-19 spread.",
    "span": "South Africa",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0010603569146
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Australian airline Qantas to resume international flights.",
    "span": "Australian",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.054609813875
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Australian airline Qantas to resume international flights.",
    "span": "Qantas",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -9.040034059999999e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Technology giant IBM announces new sustainability initiative.",
    "span": "IBM",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00019746513224999998
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Instagram influencer faces backlash over controversial post.",
    "span": "Instagram",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -2.9815723325e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Microsoft CEO Satya Nadella speaks at technology conference.",
    "span": "Microsoft",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -6.849731425e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Microsoft CEO Satya Nadella speaks at technology conference.",
    "span": "Satya Nadella",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0005234375761428571
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Los Angeles Lakers star LeBron James sidelined with ankle injury.",
    "span": "Los Angeles Lakers",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0032502427991666673
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Los Angeles Lakers star LeBron James sidelined with ankle injury.",
    "span": "LeBron James",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0007102953581000001
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The CEO of Apple announced a new product launch.",
    "span": "Apple",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.628729564309825
  },
  {
    "sentence": "London's mayor declares a state of emergency due to extreme weather conditions.",
    "span": "London",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -7.725419475e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The United Nations has issued a statement condemning the recent acts of violence in the region.",
    "span": "United Nations",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00022057811122
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Famous actress Jennifer Lawrence will star in a new film adaptation of a classic novel.",
    "span": "Jennifer Lawrence",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -5.45013352e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The European Union has implemented new trade tariffs on imported goods.",
    "span": "European Union",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00014307993276
  },
  {
    "sentence": "New York City plans to invest millions of dollars in upgrading its public transportation system.",
    "span": "New York City",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -8.20972325e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The former president of the United States will be delivering a keynote speech at the upcoming conference.",
    "span": "United States",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0009515516172000001
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Facebook is facing scrutiny over its data privacy policies.",
    "span": "Facebook",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.000167385940475
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Australian Prime Minister announces a new policy to combat climate change.",
    "span": "Australian Prime Minister",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.22160190666083332
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The latest study conducted by the World Health Organization reveals alarming statistics about global obesity rates.",
    "span": "World Health Organization",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0029427642324333335
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The CEO of Tesla unveils plans for a revolutionary new electric vehicle.",
    "span": "Tesla",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0025015538535
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tokyo Olympics organizers reveal new safety measures for the upcoming games.",
    "span": "Tokyo",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.006224841767188001
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The famous singer Taylor Swift announces a world tour.",
    "span": "Taylor Swift",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0018377529077799998
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The World Bank has approved a loan for infrastructure development in developing countries.",
    "span": "World Bank",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.08974899886464
  },
  {
    "sentence": "NASA launches a new satellite into orbit to study climate patterns.",
    "span": "NASA",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0042066582782
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The Italian government is facing backlash over its immigration policies.",
    "span": "Italian",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.432021288925
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Pop star Lady Gaga cancels her upcoming concert due to illness.",
    "span": "Lady Gaga",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0042800771514
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The United Nations Security Council condemns the recent terrorist attacks in the Middle East.",
    "span": "United Nations Security Council",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.03082845303042857
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The city of Paris is implementing new measures to reduce air pollution.",
    "span": "Paris",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.15889006392750002
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The CEO of Amazon announces plans for expansion into new markets.",
    "span": "Amazon",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0071717525067500005
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Indian Prime Minister addresses the nation on Independence Day.",
    "span": "Indian Prime Minister",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0033995491006666672
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The International Monetary Fund warns of a global economic slowdown.",
    "span": "International Monetary Fund",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0007493867145833333
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The Russian government denies allegations of election interference.",
    "span": "Russian",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.4690885272
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Renowned chef Gordon Ramsay opens a new restaurant in Los Angeles.",
    "span": "Gordon Ramsay",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0819569161992857
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The World Trade Organization reports a significant increase in global trade tensions.",
    "span": "World Trade Organization",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00046283027083333337
  },
  {
    "sentence": "London Symphony Orchestra announces a series of upcoming performances.",
    "span": "London Symphony Orchestra",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0003633287043
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The British monarchy faces criticism over its handling of recent scandals.",
    "span": "British",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.01551534897
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Microsoft unveils a new line of products at its annual conference.",
    "span": "Microsoft",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.000262317004
  },
  {
    "sentence": "French President Macron delivers a speech on national security.",
    "span": "French President Macron",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.039839027214999996
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The World Wildlife Fund is raising awareness about endangered species in Africa.",
    "span": "World Wildlife Fund",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0035323120202666665
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The Chinese government announces a crackdown on corruption within the Communist Party.",
    "span": "Chinese",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.32682079155
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Hollywood actor Brad Pitt to star in a new action thriller film.",
    "span": "Brad Pitt",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0004060619788
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The International Red Cross issues a statement on the humanitarian crisis in Syria.",
    "span": "International Red Cross",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.006846098937616667
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tokyo Electric Power Company faces lawsuits over the Fukushima nuclear disaster.",
    "span": "Tokyo Electric Power Company",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0018288706924500001
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The German Chancellor meets with world leaders to discuss trade agreements.",
    "span": "German Chancellor",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.013266657370399998
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The American Red Cross provides aid to victims of a natural disaster in the Midwest.",
    "span": "American Red Cross",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.000607457916
  },
  {
    "sentence": "South Korean pop sensation BTS breaks records with their latest album release.",
    "span": "South Korean",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.37533386366
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The European Central Bank announces an interest rate hike.",
    "span": "European Central Bank",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00011565183833333333
  },
  {
    "sentence": "New Zealand Prime Minister addresses climate change at the United Nations summit.",
    "span": "New Zealand Prime Minister",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0009183986335714286
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The World Economic Forum releases its annual report on global competitiveness.",
    "span": "World Economic Forum",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -9.177381366666667e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Australian wildfires devastate wildlife and natural habitats.",
    "span": "Australian",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0057921532425
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The Gates Foundation pledges millions of dollars to combat infectious diseases in developing countries.",
    "span": "Gates Foundation",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.000104725447
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The Filipino government faces criticism over human rights abuses.",
    "span": "Filipino",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.09876863416555
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The Swedish pop group ABBA announces a reunion tour.",
    "span": "Swedish",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.04414264837792
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Harvard University researchers make a breakthrough in cancer treatment.",
    "span": "Harvard University",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -5.023928328333333e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "South African President delivers a speech on economic reforms.",
    "span": "South African President",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.002468916771666667
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The World Health Organization warns of a new strain of flu virus in Southeast Asia.",
    "span": "World Health Organization",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0025175635953333334
  },
  {
    "sentence": "President Biden announces new infrastructure plan to improve roads and bridges.",
    "span": "Biden",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.136307614729
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tesla CEO Elon Musk predicts that self-driving cars will be on the road by next year.",
    "span": "Tesla",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0026677929567500004
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tesla CEO Elon Musk predicts that self-driving cars will be on the road by next year.",
    "span": "Elon Musk",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.00013051476246
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Japan to host 2021 Summer Olympics despite concerns over COVID-19.",
    "span": "Japan",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0301840059795
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Apple unveils new iPhone with advanced features and expanded battery life.",
    "span": "Apple",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0010351329261
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Rising star actress Emma Watson takes a break from acting to focus on activism.",
    "span": "Emma Watson",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0003206743575
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Wildfires continue to ravage California, forcing thousands to evacuate their homes.",
    "span": "California",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0006190213270000001
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Amazon founder Jeff Bezos announces plans for space tourism company.",
    "span": "Amazon",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -9.712682925e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Amazon founder Jeff Bezos announces plans for space tourism company.",
    "span": "Jeff Bezos",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.00067522599194
  },
  {
    "sentence": "European Union leaders meet to discuss climate change and environmental policies.",
    "span": "European Union",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.024827599395119998
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The United Nations convened a special session to discuss climate change.",
    "span": "climate change",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0670807391
  },
  {
    "sentence": "President Biden announced new policies on immigration reform.",
    "span": "President Biden",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.05376222283399999
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The city of London broke ground on a new public transportation project.",
    "span": "London",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00011176090375
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Amazon employees protest for better working conditions.",
    "span": "Amazon",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.000134089594275
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Elon Musk launches new space exploration company.",
    "span": "Elon Musk",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0002918070888666666
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The New York Stock Exchange experienced a record high trading day.",
    "span": "New York Stock Exchange",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.002490406583
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Thousands of people gathered in Paris to protest vaccine mandates.",
    "span": "Paris",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0002863585355
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Apple releases the latest iPhone model.",
    "span": "Apple",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00523979148225
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Spanish soccer star Lionel Messi signs with Paris Saint-Germain.",
    "span": "Lionel Messi",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -9.614260457142857e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The European Union announces new trade agreements with China.",
    "span": "European Union",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -7.48323414e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The European Union announces new trade agreements with China.",
    "span": "China",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0525823321535
  },
  {
    "sentence": "CEO of Tesla, Elon Musk, becomes the world's richest person.",
    "span": "Tesla",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.2450660622183667
  },
  {
    "sentence": "CEO of Tesla, Elon Musk, becomes the world's richest person.",
    "span": "Elon Musk",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0050113020895
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Hurricane season devastates coastal communities in the Caribbean.",
    "span": "Caribbean",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0057594050008
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Australian government invests in renewable energy projects.",
    "span": "Australian government",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.33520695552414004
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Grammy award-winning artist Beyoncé releases new album.",
    "span": "Beyoncé",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.008878747178940001
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Russian President Vladimir Putin meets with German Chancellor Angela Merkel.",
    "span": "Vladimir Putin",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0028741448223714287
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Russian President Vladimir Putin meets with German Chancellor Angela Merkel.",
    "span": "German Chancellor Angela Merkel",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.149600757583
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tokyo to host 2021 Summer Olympics.",
    "span": "Tokyo",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.08051532739356
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Facebook under fire for privacy breaches.",
    "span": "Facebook",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00039376107874999997
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The World Health Organization warns of a new strain of flu virus.",
    "span": "World Health Organization",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0002515525975
  },
  {
    "sentence": "South African activist Desmond Tutu awarded Nobel Peace Prize.",
    "span": "Desmond Tutu",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.20750769751605716
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Amazon announces plans to open new headquarters in Atlanta.",
    "span": "Amazon",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -2.7759460075e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Amazon announces plans to open new headquarters in Atlanta.",
    "span": "Atlanta",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00021036893349999999
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Scientists discover new species of dinosaur in Patagonia.",
    "span": "Patagonia",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -3.9190632650000004e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Apple releases new iPhone with advanced camera features.",
    "span": "Apple",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00091870377216
  },
  {
    "sentence": "European Union imposes sanctions on Russia.",
    "span": "European Union",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00017175116019999998
  },
  {
    "sentence": "European Union imposes sanctions on Russia.",
    "span": "Russia",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00081186849175
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Actress Emma Watson speaks out against gender inequality in Hollywood.",
    "span": "Emma Watson",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.09196460210650001
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Actress Emma Watson speaks out against gender inequality in Hollywood.",
    "span": "Hollywood",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00031073753999999996
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Ford recalls over 100,000 vehicles due to safety concerns.",
    "span": "Ford",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00018710221352499998
  },
  {
    "sentence": "United Nations announces humanitarian aid for refugees in Syria.",
    "span": "United Nations",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -7.965691619999999e-06
  },
  {
    "sentence": "United Nations announces humanitarian aid for refugees in Syria.",
    "span": "Syria",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.009849278971750001
  },
  {
    "sentence": "CEO Elon Musk steps down from Tesla.",
    "span": "Elon Musk",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.00023700640505000002
  },
  {
    "sentence": "CEO Elon Musk steps down from Tesla.",
    "span": "Tesla",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0006039080454999999
  },
  {
    "sentence": "New York City implements new COVID-19 restrictions.",
    "span": "New York City",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0018497482813333332
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Former President Obama to release memoir next year.",
    "span": "President Obama",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.2817623084165
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Starbucks to expand its presence in China.",
    "span": "Starbucks",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -8.91932093e-06
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Starbucks to expand its presence in China.",
    "span": "China",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.000790709096
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tennis player Serena Williams advances to the semifinals.",
    "span": "Serena Williams",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.01954845519625
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Google faces antitrust lawsuit from the Department of Justice.",
    "span": "Google",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -3.91136085e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Google faces antitrust lawsuit from the Department of Justice.",
    "span": "Department of Justice",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0007036690101666666
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Microsoft acquires artificial intelligence startup.",
    "span": "Microsoft",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0043804123147500006
  },
  {
    "sentence": "French government proposes new tax reforms.",
    "span": "French government",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.17646108174016
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Pilot reported seeing unidentified flying object over Arizona.",
    "span": "Arizona",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0066172108770000005
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Legendary musician Paul McCartney to perform at charity concert.",
    "span": "Paul McCartney",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -6.1509779e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Walmart to launch same-day delivery service.",
    "span": "Walmart",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -5.409164229999999e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "California wildfires continue to devastate communities.",
    "span": "California",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -4.0542220225e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "CEO Tim Cook unveils new line of products at Apple event.",
    "span": "Tim Cook",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.000151676533
  },
  {
    "sentence": "CEO Tim Cook unveils new line of products at Apple event.",
    "span": "Apple",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0002970781875
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Renowned chef Gordon Ramsay opens new restaurant in Las Vegas.",
    "span": "Gordon Ramsay",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -1.9334315285714283e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Renowned chef Gordon Ramsay opens new restaurant in Las Vegas.",
    "span": "Las Vegas",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0005231483508
  },
  {
    "sentence": "South Korea imposes strict lockdown measures amid surge in COVID-19 cases.",
    "span": "South Korea",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00044655536179999996
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Amazon founder Jeff Bezos steps down as CEO.",
    "span": "Amazon",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.4450078874733833
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Amazon founder Jeff Bezos steps down as CEO.",
    "span": "Jeff Bezos",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.008390461873075
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Broadway musical Hamilton to return to theaters next year.",
    "span": "Hamilton",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.032381173390000004
  },
  {
    "sentence": "AstraZeneca vaccine found to be highly effective in new study.",
    "span": "AstraZeneca",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -5.749180015714286e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Manchester United signs new sponsorship deal with major tech company.",
    "span": "Manchester United",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -6.136672999999999e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "McDonald's introduces new plant-based burger to its menu.",
    "span": "McDonald's",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -2.79084642e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Swiss government announces plans to reduce carbon emissions.",
    "span": "Swiss government",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00010279954283333333
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Violent protests erupt in downtown Los Angeles.",
    "span": "Los Angeles",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -9.09761846e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "CEO Mark Zuckerberg faces congressional hearing on privacy issues.",
    "span": "Mark Zuckerberg",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0003623164418
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tokyo Olympics organizers announce new COVID-19 protocols for athletes.",
    "span": "Tokyo",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.27288907607172
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tokyo Olympics organizers announce new COVID-19 protocols for athletes.",
    "span": "Olympics",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0021936776525
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Starbucks CEO Howard Schultz to step down from his position.",
    "span": "Starbucks",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0007087535652
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Starbucks CEO Howard Schultz to step down from his position.",
    "span": "Howard Schultz",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.00021346044425000002
  },
  {
    "sentence": "New Zealand experiences 6.5 magnitude earthquake.",
    "span": "New Zealand",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -7.073614066e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Grammy-winning artist Beyoncé to headline music festival in Chicago.",
    "span": "Beyoncé",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -7.548386869166666e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Grammy-winning artist Beyoncé to headline music festival in Chicago.",
    "span": "Chicago",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0002577716525
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tesla announces plans to build new Gigafactory in Texas.",
    "span": "Tesla",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -5.8094039e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tesla announces plans to build new Gigafactory in Texas.",
    "span": "Texas",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00420514431
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Germany approves new climate change legislation.",
    "span": "Germany",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -3.3034220749999995e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Legendary director Steven Spielberg to produce new film.",
    "span": "Steven Spielberg",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -4.1676488520000005e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "SpaceX CEO Elon Musk announces plans for manned mission to Mars.",
    "span": "SpaceX",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.050384848841999993
  },
  {
    "sentence": "SpaceX CEO Elon Musk announces plans for manned mission to Mars.",
    "span": "Elon Musk",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0001731280618
  },
  {
    "sentence": "SpaceX CEO Elon Musk announces plans for manned mission to Mars.",
    "span": "Mars",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00025306724239999997
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Australian government launches inquiry into banking industry practices.",
    "span": "Australian government",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.051790455991599996
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Major snowstorm expected to hit northeastern United States.",
    "span": "United States",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0009013367499999999
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Instagram introduces new feature to combat cyberbullying.",
    "span": "Instagram",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -4.0482617649999996e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "New York City mayor announces new infrastructure plan.",
    "span": "New York City",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.011913816724666666
  },
  {
    "sentence": "CEO of Apple speaks at annual tech conference.",
    "span": "Apple",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.008007513764000001
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Protests erupt in Paris over new labor laws.",
    "span": "Paris",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -7.805973599999999e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "United Nations report highlights climate change concerns.",
    "span": "United Nations",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -4.1912693300000005e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Prime Minister of Japan meets with President of the United States.",
    "span": "Japan",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0780948436915
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Major earthquake hits southern California.",
    "span": "California",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.166234525705
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Hurricane warning issued for Florida coast.",
    "span": "Florida",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.47230586240475
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Apple announces new iPhone models.",
    "span": "Apple",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.02693633285175
  },
  {
    "sentence": "President Biden visits troops in Afghanistan.",
    "span": "President Biden",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.020335851019999997
  },
  {
    "sentence": "President Biden visits troops in Afghanistan.",
    "span": "Afghanistan",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.000283326624325
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Google CEO resigns amid controversy.",
    "span": "Google",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.002223408584675
  },
  {
    "sentence": "California wildfires rage on, threatening homes.",
    "span": "California",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -4.33435064e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tesla stock reaches all-time high.",
    "span": "Tesla",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.000190435345425
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Dr. Anthony Fauci warns of potential COVID-19 surge.",
    "span": "Dr. Anthony Fauci",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0034294845431875
  },
  {
    "sentence": "United Nations calls for ceasefire in Syria.",
    "span": "United Nations",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -1.7001329000000002e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "United Nations calls for ceasefire in Syria.",
    "span": "Syria",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.01598050379925
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Amazon Prime Day sales exceed expectations.",
    "span": "Amazon",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00010975141805
  },
  {
    "sentence": "New York City imposes vaccine mandate for indoor dining.",
    "span": "New York City",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -8.892973966666668e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Facebook faces backlash over privacy concerns.",
    "span": "Facebook",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.01369337235015
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Angela Merkel elected as President of the European Union.",
    "span": "Angela Merkel",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.00032602592004999997
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Angela Merkel elected as President of the European Union.",
    "span": "European Union",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0023540780794
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tokyo Olympics postponed due to pandemic.",
    "span": "Tokyo",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0100178326844
  },
  {
    "sentence": "International Monetary Fund projects global economic slowdown.",
    "span": "International Monetary Fund",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00033726316016666663
  },
  {
    "sentence": "FDA approves new cancer treatment.",
    "span": "FDA",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0032530209791500004
  },
  {
    "sentence": "World Health Organization declares polio eradicated in Africa.",
    "span": "World Health Organization",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -3.71070148e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "World Health Organization declares polio eradicated in Africa.",
    "span": "Africa",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0036753479175000003
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Uber partners with local restaurant to offer food delivery.",
    "span": "Uber",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.000104480317075
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Apple plans to open a new store in downtown Miami.",
    "span": "Apple",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0002181758565
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Apple plans to open a new store in downtown Miami.",
    "span": "Miami",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0406458978905
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The CEO of Tesla announced a new electric car model at the conference.",
    "span": "Tesla",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.062516043804
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Mexico surpasses 100,000 COVID-19 deaths.",
    "span": "Mexico",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00010368669225
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Japanese Prime Minister to visit South Korea next week.",
    "span": "Japanese Prime Minister",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.06267062052938333
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Japanese Prime Minister to visit South Korea next week.",
    "span": "South Korea",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00010598118139999999
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Facebook acquires a leading artificial intelligence startup.",
    "span": "Facebook",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00021616409415
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The famous actor, Tom Hanks, to star in a new war film.",
    "span": "Tom Hanks",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -9.925644544166667e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Germany imposes strict lockdown measures in response to rising COVID-19 cases.",
    "span": "Germany",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0002401739895
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The United Nations peacekeeping mission in the Middle East extends for another year.",
    "span": "United Nations",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0010277809463
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The United Nations peacekeeping mission in the Middle East extends for another year.",
    "span": "Middle East",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0003568334056
  },
  {
    "sentence": "New York City to invest $1 billion in affordable housing initiatives.",
    "span": "New York City",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00011992605915
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Samsung to launch its latest smartphone model next month.",
    "span": "Samsung",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0001163346632
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The president of France addresses the nation in a televised speech.",
    "span": "France",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.002229906345
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Harvard University announces new financial aid initiatives for low-income students.",
    "span": "Harvard University",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -9.390786753333333e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Hurricane Maria causes widespread devastation in Puerto Rico.",
    "span": "Hurricane Maria",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.1105416624085
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Hurricane Maria causes widespread devastation in Puerto Rico.",
    "span": "Puerto Rico",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0016759444971999999
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The popular singer Taylor Swift releases a new album.",
    "span": "Taylor Swift",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0006657223096800001
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Google's parent company, Alphabet, faces antitrust investigation by the European Union.",
    "span": "Google",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.000880615692
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Google's parent company, Alphabet, faces antitrust investigation by the European Union.",
    "span": "Alphabet",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00081831668075
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Google's parent company, Alphabet, faces antitrust investigation by the European Union.",
    "span": "European Union",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.8351598635034
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The mayor of London introduces new cycling infrastructure to reduce traffic congestion.",
    "span": "London",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.000348006567
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Microsoft announces a partnership with a leading tech startup to develop innovative software solutions.",
    "span": "Microsoft",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.000170367852
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The renowned chef Julia Child's cookbook sells for a record price at auction.",
    "span": "Julia Child",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.09156709111711665
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Brazil's president signs an executive order to address deforestation in the Amazon rainforest.",
    "span": "Brazil",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.002372906084
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Brazil's president signs an executive order to address deforestation in the Amazon rainforest.",
    "span": "Amazon rainforest",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.023773016135499998
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The famous basketball player Michael Jordan to invest in a new sports team.",
    "span": "Michael Jordan",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.00044228385986000006
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The European Central Bank announces new stimulus measures to support the economy.",
    "span": "European Central Bank",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0012292973140000001
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The iconic landmark, the Eiffel Tower, reopens to tourists after a lengthy renovation.",
    "span": "Eiffel Tower",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.23556318752930575
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The United States announces new trade tariffs on Chinese goods.",
    "span": "United States",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.12078243603779999
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The United States announces new trade tariffs on Chinese goods.",
    "span": "Chinese",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.489873441635
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Mary Smith appointed as new CEO of ABC Corporation.",
    "span": "Mary Smith",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -3.8124218500000004e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Mary Smith appointed as new CEO of ABC Corporation.",
    "span": "ABC Corporation",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00018964858928
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Firefighters battle massive wildfire in California.",
    "span": "California",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00010901647200000001
  },
  {
    "sentence": "President Johnson delivers annual State of the Union address.",
    "span": "President Johnson",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0094641785318
  },
  {
    "sentence": "NASA launches new Mars rover mission.",
    "span": "NASA",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.000250027077625
  },
  {
    "sentence": "NASA launches new Mars rover mission.",
    "span": "Mars",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00017786851764999998
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Prime Minister Lee visits South Korea to discuss trade agreements.",
    "span": "Prime Minister Lee",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.00016113232386666667
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Prime Minister Lee visits South Korea to discuss trade agreements.",
    "span": "South Korea",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0001584139292
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tennis star Serena Williams wins Wimbledon championship.",
    "span": "Serena Williams",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.011117562998116665
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tennis star Serena Williams wins Wimbledon championship.",
    "span": "Wimbledon",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0343272924505
  },
  {
    "sentence": "A new study reveals the impact of climate change on polar bears in the Arctic.",
    "span": "Arctic",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00106105793228
  },
  {
    "sentence": "OPEC members meet to discuss oil production quotas.",
    "span": "OPEC",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.000635245069348
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Environmental activist Greta Thunberg speaks at United Nations climate summit.",
    "span": "Greta Thunberg",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -1.73738407875e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Environmental activist Greta Thunberg speaks at United Nations climate summit.",
    "span": "United Nations",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00029604029118
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Japan's economy enters recession due to pandemic-related lockdowns.",
    "span": "Japan",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00032195508935
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Famous actor Brad Pitt stars in new blockbuster film.",
    "span": "Brad Pitt",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -9.142256094e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Nature conservation group protests logging in Amazon rainforest.",
    "span": "Amazon rainforest",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.06745185988401665
  },
  {
    "sentence": "UK Parliament votes to approve new Brexit deal.",
    "span": "UK Parliament",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.024119072829260003
  },
  {
    "sentence": "UK Parliament votes to approve new Brexit deal.",
    "span": "Brexit",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.06472104112325
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Microsoft acquires AI startup for $1 billion.",
    "span": "Microsoft",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00064135553125
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Egyptian archaeologists uncover ancient tomb in Luxor.",
    "span": "Egyptian",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0497110837992
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Egyptian archaeologists uncover ancient tomb in Luxor.",
    "span": "Luxor",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.000376558533
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Famous chef Gordon Ramsay opens new restaurant in London.",
    "span": "Gordon Ramsay",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -3.1203593585714286e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Famous chef Gordon Ramsay opens new restaurant in London.",
    "span": "London",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00045416109624999996
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Uber driver charged with assault in Los Angeles.",
    "span": "Uber",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0008942289355
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Uber driver charged with assault in Los Angeles.",
    "span": "Los Angeles",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.000213951103
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Facebook faces antitrust investigation by US government.",
    "span": "Facebook",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -7.62978215e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Facebook faces antitrust investigation by US government.",
    "span": "US",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.20076193514000001
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Activist Malala Yousafzai awarded Nobel Peace Prize.",
    "span": "Malala Yousafzai",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.00016315402684
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Activist Malala Yousafzai awarded Nobel Peace Prize.",
    "span": "Nobel Peace Prize",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0005025500326666667
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Severe weather warnings issued for Midwest region.",
    "span": "Midwest",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0006206698442
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Harvard University announces new scholarship program for low-income students.",
    "span": "Harvard University",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0005020027577666667
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Fashion designer Stella McCartney launches sustainable clothing line.",
    "span": "Stella McCartney",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -4.7178502766666666e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Oil spill contaminates coastal waters in Nigeria.",
    "span": "Nigeria",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -9.433479618e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Former president Barack Obama releases memoir.",
    "span": "Barack Obama",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -4.4733600833333336e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Volunteers clean up litter on beach in Sydney.",
    "span": "Sydney",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00010305683619999997
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Japanese automaker Toyota recalls millions of vehicles.",
    "span": "Japanese",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.4770317015615
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Japanese automaker Toyota recalls millions of vehicles.",
    "span": "Toyota",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.000100078029325
  },
  {
    "sentence": "UNICEF provides humanitarian aid to refugees in war-torn region.",
    "span": "UNICEF",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -8.201164439999999e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Olympic champion Usain Bolt announces retirement from track and field.",
    "span": "Usain Bolt",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0008288816207666668
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Earthquake rocks major city in Indonesia.",
    "span": "Indonesia",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0001434423046
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Pfizer and Moderna report positive results from COVID-19 vaccine trials.",
    "span": "Pfizer",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -1.8888720516666664e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Pfizer and Moderna report positive results from COVID-19 vaccine trials.",
    "span": "Moderna",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0097936145774
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Renowned author J.K. Rowling publishes new book.",
    "span": "J.K. Rowling",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -3.0437284614285715e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Italian government launches investigation into corruption allegations.",
    "span": "Italian",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.018592396076
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Thousands attend protest against police brutality in Chicago.",
    "span": "Chicago",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00011271270350000001
  },
  {
    "sentence": "SpaceX founder Elon Musk announces plans for Mars colonization.",
    "span": "SpaceX",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -4.88265082e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "SpaceX founder Elon Musk announces plans for Mars colonization.",
    "span": "Elon Musk",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0007580021158
  },
  {
    "sentence": "SpaceX founder Elon Musk announces plans for Mars colonization.",
    "span": "Mars",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -9.954161475000001e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "World Bank approves funding for infrastructure project in Africa.",
    "span": "World Bank",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -5.738386060000001e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "World Bank approves funding for infrastructure project in Africa.",
    "span": "Africa",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0001747462875
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Soccer star Lionel Messi signs record-breaking contract with Paris Saint-Germain.",
    "span": "Lionel Messi",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -4.673203205714286e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Philadelphia Eagles quarterback suffers season-ending injury.",
    "span": "Philadelphia Eagles",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00048487738816
  },
  {
    "sentence": "British Prime Minister Boris Johnson declares national emergency.",
    "span": "Boris Johnson",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.07104943298283334
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Australian scientists make breakthrough in cancer research.",
    "span": "Australian",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.01130665498
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The United Nations reports a surge in violence in the Middle East.",
    "span": "United Nations",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00998777258272
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The United Nations reports a surge in violence in the Middle East.",
    "span": "Middle East",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00017048833366
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Apple announces new iPhone release date.",
    "span": "Apple",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0298505899909125
  },
  {
    "sentence": "German Chancellor Angela Merkel meets with French President Emmanuel Macron.",
    "span": "Angela Merkel",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.024035913324200003
  },
  {
    "sentence": "German Chancellor Angela Merkel meets with French President Emmanuel Macron.",
    "span": "Emmanuel Macron",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.31729335695680005
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tokyo Olympics to proceed without international spectators.",
    "span": "Tokyo",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.27970529965226604
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tokyo Olympics to proceed without international spectators.",
    "span": "Olympics",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.000267464290575
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tesla founder Elon Musk unveils plans for Mars colonization.",
    "span": "Tesla",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.007518167862825
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tesla founder Elon Musk unveils plans for Mars colonization.",
    "span": "Elon Musk",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.00024485604742
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tesla founder Elon Musk unveils plans for Mars colonization.",
    "span": "Mars",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0005268552741750001
  },
  {
    "sentence": "NATO allies meet to discuss global security concerns.",
    "span": "NATO",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -6.28620962e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Hurricane Florence batters the U.S. East Coast.",
    "span": "Hurricane Florence",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.03542931679383333
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Hurricane Florence batters the U.S. East Coast.",
    "span": "U.S. East Coast",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0017817109496249999
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Amazon employees plan to unionize for better working conditions.",
    "span": "Amazon",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00020145435216
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Barcelona FC appoints new head coach.",
    "span": "Barcelona FC",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.38977429988490003
  },
  {
