{"sentence": "Protesters gather in downtown Portland to support the Black Lives Matter movement.", "tokens": ["Protesters", "gather", "in", "downtown", "Portland", "to", "support", "the", "Black", "Lives", "Matter", "movement", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "New York City mayor announces police reform plan in response to Black Lives Matter demonstrations.", "tokens": ["New", "York", "City", "mayor", "announces", "police", "reform", "plan", "in", "response", "to", "Black", "Lives", "Matter", "demonstrations", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Chicago police chief meets with leaders of Black Lives Matter to discuss community policing initiatives.", "tokens": ["Chicago", "police", "chief", "meets", "with", "leaders", "of", "Black", "Lives", "Matter", "to", "discuss", "community", "policing", "initiatives", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Steven Spielberg to direct new film about the United Nations Development Programme.", "tokens": ["Steven", "Spielberg", "to", "direct", "new", "film", "about", "the", "United", "Nations", "Development", "Programme", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O"]}
{"sentence": "United Nations Development Programme launches new initiative to combat climate change in developing countries.", "tokens": ["United", "Nations", "Development", "Programme", "launches", "new", "initiative", "to", "combat", "climate", "change", "in", "developing", "countries", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Paris Climate Agreement participants pledge to reduce carbon emissions by 20% by 2030.", "tokens": ["Paris", "Climate", "Agreement", "participants", "pledge", "to", "reduce", "carbon", "emissions", "by", "20", "%", "by", "2030", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Apple Inc. announces record-breaking quarterly earnings, surpassing analyst expectations.", "tokens": ["Apple", "Inc", ".", "announces", "record", "-", "breaking", "quarterly", "earnings", ",", "surpassing", "analyst", "expectations", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Russia and Saudi Arabia agree to cooperate on oil production cuts to stabilize the market.", "tokens": ["Russia", "and", "Saudi", "Arabia", "agree", "to", "cooperate", "on", "oil", "production", "cuts", "to", "stabilize", "the", "market", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Oil prices surge as tensions rise between the United States and Iran.", "tokens": ["Oil", "prices", "surge", "as", "tensions", "rise", "between", "the", "United", "States", "and", "Iran", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Pop star Britney Spears announces new Las Vegas residency.", "tokens": ["Pop", "star", "Britney", "Spears", "announces", "new", "Las", "Vegas", "residency", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Britney Spears' new album tops charts in over 20 countries.", "tokens": ["Britney", "Spears", "'", "new", "album", "tops", "charts", "in", "over", "20", "countries", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Britney Spears' former manager files lawsuit against her estate.", "tokens": ["Britney", "Spears", "'", "former", "manager", "files", "lawsuit", "against", "her", "estate", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Sydney Opera House to host annual music festival.", "tokens": ["Sydney", "Opera", "House", "to", "host", "annual", "music", "festival", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "B-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Australian Prime Minister to visit Sydney for climate change summit.", "tokens": ["Australian", "Prime", "Minister", "to", "visit", "Sydney", "for", "climate", "change", "summit", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "New South Wales government announces major infrastructure plan for Sydney.", "tokens": ["New", "South", "Wales", "government", "announces", "major", "infrastructure", "plan", "for", "Sydney", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Supreme Court Justice Ruth Bader Ginsburg hospitalized for treatment of possible infection.", "tokens": ["Supreme", "Court", "Justice", "Ruth", "Bader", "Ginsburg", "hospitalized", "for", "treatment", "of", "possible", "infection", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Ruth Bader Ginsburg, United States Supreme Court Justice, to undergo non-surgical procedure for benign gallbladder condition.", "tokens": ["Ruth", "Bader", "Ginsburg", ",", "United", "States", "Supreme", "Court", "Justice", ",", "to", "undergo", "non", "-", "surgical", "procedure", "for", "benign", "gallbladder", "condition", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "I-person", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Ruth Bader Ginsburg to return to work after treatment for cancer.", "tokens": ["Ruth", "Bader", "Ginsburg", "to", "return", "to", "work", "after", "treatment", "for", "cancer", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Billie Eilish's new album tops the charts.", "tokens": ["Billie", "Eilish", "'", "s", "new", "album", "tops", "the", "charts", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Billie Eilish announces world tour dates for next year.", "tokens": ["Billie", "Eilish", "announces", "world", "tour", "dates", "for", "next", "year", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Angelina Jolie donates $1 million to refugee charity.", "tokens": ["Angelina", "Jolie", "donates", "$", "1", "million", "to", "refugee", "charity", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Critics praise Angelina Jolie's performance in new film.", "tokens": ["Critics", "praise", "Angelina", "Jolie", "'", "s", "performance", "in", "new", "film", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Angelina Jolie partners with UNICEF for new global initiative.", "tokens": ["Angelina", "Jolie", "partners", "with", "UNICEF", "for", "new", "global", "initiative", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Miami Heat signs top free agent from Oslo.", "tokens": ["Miami", "Heat", "signs", "top", "free", "agent", "from", "Oslo", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Oslo to host international peace summit.", "tokens": ["Oslo", "to", "host", "international", "peace", "summit", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Miami police department announces new chief of police.", "tokens": ["Miami", "police", "department", "announces", "new", "chief", "of", "police", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Oxfam International reports a rise in global hunger due to the COVID-19 pandemic.", "tokens": ["Oxfam", "International", "reports", "a", "rise", "in", "global", "hunger", "due", "to", "the", "COVID", "-", "19", "pandemic", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The United Nations calls for urgent action to address the climate crisis.", "tokens": ["The", "United", "Nations", "calls", "for", "urgent", "action", "to", "address", "the", "climate", "crisis", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Professor Johnson's research reveals promising results in the fight against cancer.", "tokens": ["Professor", "Johnson", "'", "s", "research", "reveals", "promising", "results", "in", "the", "fight", "against", "cancer", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Microsoft acquires cybersecurity firm for $10 billion.", "tokens": ["Microsoft", "acquires", "cybersecurity", "firm", "for", "$", "10", "billion", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "President Biden meets with German Chancellor Angela Merkel in Washington.", "tokens": ["President", "Biden", "meets", "with", "German", "Chancellor", "Angela", "Merkel", "in", "Washington", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tropical storm damages thousands of homes in Philippines.", "tokens": ["Tropical", "storm", "damages", "thousands", "of", "homes", "in", "Philippines", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "International Red Cross deploys relief teams to flood-affected areas in Southeast Asia.", "tokens": ["International", "Red", "Cross", "deploys", "relief", "teams", "to", "flood", "-", "affected", "areas", "in", "Southeast", "Asia", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Renowned scientist from Zurich wins prestigious award for contribution to environmental sustainability.", "tokens": ["Renowned", "scientist", "from", "Zurich", "wins", "prestigious", "award", "for", "contribution", "to", "environmental", "sustainability", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tesla stocks soar after successful launch of new electric vehicle.", "tokens": ["Tesla", "stocks", "soar", "after", "successful", "launch", "of", "new", "electric", "vehicle", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Australian Prime Minister meets with Chinese President to discuss trade agreements.", "tokens": ["Australian", "Prime", "Minister", "meets", "with", "Chinese", "President", "to", "discuss", "trade", "agreements", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Flooding in Midwest causes thousands to evacuate their homes.", "tokens": ["Flooding", "in", "Midwest", "causes", "thousands", "to", "evacuate", "their", "homes", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The new Starbucks Corporation branch in Jakarta is expected to attract a large number of coffee lovers.", "tokens": ["The", "new", "Starbucks", "Corporation", "branch", "in", "Jakarta", "is", "expected", "to", "attract", "a", "large", "number", "of", "coffee", "lovers", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Jakarta experiences heavy flooding after a week of relentless rain.", "tokens": ["Jakarta", "experiences", "heavy", "flooding", "after", "a", "week", "of", "relentless", "rain", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "APPLE ANNOUNCES LAUNCH OF NEW IPHONE MODEL.", "tokens": ["APPLE", "ANNOUNCES", "LAUNCH", "OF", "NEW", "IPHONE", "MODEL", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "TOM CRUISE TO STAR IN UPCOMING ACTION THRILLER FILM.", "tokens": ["TOM", "CRUISE", "TO", "STAR", "IN", "UPCOMING", "ACTION", "THRILLER", "FILM", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "CALIFORNIA GOVERNOR SIGNS BILL TO COMBAT CLIMATE CHANGE.", "tokens": ["CALIFORNIA", "GOVERNOR", "SIGNS", "BILL", "TO", "COMBAT", "CLIMATE", "CHANGE", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Dwayne \"The Rock\" Johnson announces new production company.", "tokens": ["Dwayne", "\"", "The", "Rock", "\"", "Johnson", "announces", "new", "production", "company", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "I-person", "I-person", "I-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Record-breaking heatwave hits Western United States, prompting emergency measures.", "tokens": ["Record", "-", "breaking", "heatwave", "hits", "Western", "United", "States", ",", "prompting", "emergency", "measures", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "New York City Marathon canceled due to extreme weather conditions.", "tokens": ["New", "York", "City", "Marathon", "canceled", "due", "to", "extreme", "weather", "conditions", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Coca-Cola plans to launch a new line of flavored sparkling water.", "tokens": ["Coca", "-", "Cola", "plans", "to", "launch", "a", "new", "line", "of", "flavored", "sparkling", "water", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Investors speculate on potential merger between PepsiCo and Coca-Cola.", "tokens": ["Investors", "speculate", "on", "potential", "merger", "between", "PepsiCo", "and", "Coca", "-", "Cola", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Coca-Cola CEO announced significant expansion in Asian markets.", "tokens": ["Coca", "-", "Cola", "CEO", "announced", "significant", "expansion", "in", "Asian", "markets", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Queen Elizabeth II celebrates her 95th birthday.", "tokens": ["Queen", "Elizabeth", "II", "celebrates", "her", "95th", "birthday", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Walmart announces plans to open 100 new stores nationwide.", "tokens": ["Walmart", "announces", "plans", "to", "open", "100", "new", "stores", "nationwide", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Aung San Suu Kyi calls for release of political prisoners in Myanmar.", "tokens": ["Aung", "San", "Suu", "Kyi", "calls", "for", "release", "of", "political", "prisoners", "in", "Myanmar", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "I-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Mumbai police arrest suspects in connection with terrorist plot.", "tokens": ["Mumbai", "police", "arrest", "suspects", "in", "connection", "with", "terrorist", "plot", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "New organization in Mumbai aims to provide support for homeless youth.", "tokens": ["New", "organization", "in", "Mumbai", "aims", "to", "provide", "support", "for", "homeless", "youth", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "UN reports record number of refugees in Vienna.", "tokens": ["UN", "reports", "record", "number", "of", "refugees", "in", "Vienna", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Vienna Philharmonic Orchestra cancels upcoming tour due to COVID-19.", "tokens": ["Vienna", "Philharmonic", "Orchestra", "cancels", "upcoming", "tour", "due", "to", "COVID", "-", "19", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Vienna Mayor announces new public transportation initiatives.", "tokens": ["Vienna", "Mayor", "announces", "new", "public", "transportation", "initiatives", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Los Angeles Lakers clinch victory in NBA finals.", "tokens": ["Los", "Angeles", "Lakers", "clinch", "victory", "in", "NBA", "finals", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "I-location", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Elon Omar to lead climate change initiative.", "tokens": ["Elon", "Omar", "to", "lead", "climate", "change", "initiative", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "United Nations condemns new wave of violence in Middle East.", "tokens": ["United", "Nations", "condemns", "new", "wave", "of", "violence", "in", "Middle", "East", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Beijing announces new environmental regulations to reduce air pollution.", "tokens": ["Beijing", "announces", "new", "environmental", "regulations", "to", "reduce", "air", "pollution", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Thousands gather in Beijing to celebrate Chinese New Year.", "tokens": ["Thousands", "gather", "in", "Beijing", "to", "celebrate", "Chinese", "New", "Year", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Beijing Olympics committee selects renowned architect to design main stadium.", "tokens": ["Beijing", "Olympics", "committee", "selects", "renowned", "architect", "to", "design", "main", "stadium", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "National Public Radio reports record-breaking viewership for its latest investigative documentary.", "tokens": ["National", "Public", "Radio", "reports", "record", "-", "breaking", "viewership", "for", "its", "latest", "investigative", "documentary", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Award-winning journalist John Smith announced as the new host of the National Public Radio morning show.", "tokens": ["Award", "-", "winning", "journalist", "John", "Smith", "announced", "as", "the", "new", "host", "of", "the", "National", "Public", "Radio", "morning", "show", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "National Public Radio investigates claims of corruption within the local government.", "tokens": ["National", "Public", "Radio", "investigates", "claims", "of", "corruption", "within", "the", "local", "government", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The Coca-Cola Company announces new sustainability initiatives in Sydney.", "tokens": ["The", "Coca", "-", "Cola", "Company", "announces", "new", "sustainability", "initiatives", "in", "Sydney", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Sydney to host international film festival featuring global directors.", "tokens": ["Sydney", "to", "host", "international", "film", "festival", "featuring", "global", "directors", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Coca-Cola Company reports record sales for the third quarter.", "tokens": ["Coca", "-", "Cola", "Company", "reports", "record", "sales", "for", "the", "third", "quarter", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Martin Scorsese to premiere new film at London Film Festival.", "tokens": ["Martin", "Scorsese", "to", "premiere", "new", "film", "at", "London", "Film", "Festival", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "London mayor announces new initiative to combat air pollution in the city.", "tokens": ["London", "mayor", "announces", "new", "initiative", "to", "combat", "air", "pollution", "in", "the", "city", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Martin Scorsese's latest project to be filmed in London.", "tokens": ["Martin", "Scorsese", "'", "s", "latest", "project", "to", "be", "filmed", "in", "London", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The government announced a new transportation infrastructure plan for Jakarta.", "tokens": ["The", "government", "announced", "a", "new", "transportation", "infrastructure", "plan", "for", "Jakarta", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Local residents in Jakarta protest against the construction of a new shopping mall.", "tokens": ["Local", "residents", "in", "Jakarta", "protest", "against", "the", "construction", "of", "a", "new", "shopping", "mall", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Jakarta Mayor plans to implement a new waste management system in the city.", "tokens": ["Jakarta", "Mayor", "plans", "to", "implement", "a", "new", "waste", "management", "system", "in", "the", "city", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "B-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Nancy Pelosi announces plans to address climate change with support from the International Energy Agency.", "tokens": ["Nancy", "Pelosi", "announces", "plans", "to", "address", "climate", "change", "with", "support", "from", "the", "International", "Energy", "Agency", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The International Energy Agency predicts a global oil demand surge in the coming months.", "tokens": ["The", "International", "Energy", "Agency", "predicts", "a", "global", "oil", "demand", "surge", "in", "the", "coming", "months", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Nancy Pelosi calls for bipartisan cooperation in Congress to pass new infrastructure legislation.", "tokens": ["Nancy", "Pelosi", "calls", "for", "bipartisan", "cooperation", "in", "Congress", "to", "pass", "new", "infrastructure", "legislation", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Greenpeace activists protest outside the Hanoi government building.", "tokens": ["Greenpeace", "activists", "protest", "outside", "the", "Hanoi", "government", "building", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The mayor of Hanoi meets with foreign investors to discuss infrastructure projects.", "tokens": ["The", "mayor", "of", "Hanoi", "meets", "with", "foreign", "investors", "to", "discuss", "infrastructure", "projects", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Greenpeace warns of environmental damage in Hanoi due to excessive air pollution.", "tokens": ["Greenpeace", "warns", "of", "environmental", "damage", "in", "Hanoi", "due", "to", "excessive", "air", "pollution", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The United States Department of Justice announces new initiatives to combat cybercrime.", "tokens": ["The", "United", "States", "Department", "of", "Justice", "announces", "new", "initiatives", "to", "combat", "cybercrime", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Thousands of migrants are stranded at the border between Mexico and the United States.", "tokens": ["Thousands", "of", "migrants", "are", "stranded", "at", "the", "border", "between", "Mexico", "and", "the", "United", "States", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Real Madrid defeats Barcelona in a dramatic overtime victory.", "tokens": ["Real", "Madrid", "defeats", "Barcelona", "in", "a", "dramatic", "overtime", "victory", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Protests erupt in Madrid over government decision to raise taxes.", "tokens": ["Protests", "erupt", "in", "Madrid", "over", "government", "decision", "to", "raise", "taxes", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Renowned chef from Madrid opens new restaurant in London.", "tokens": ["Renowned", "chef", "from", "Madrid", "opens", "new", "restaurant", "in", "London", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Rosalía wins big at the Latin Grammy Awards.", "tokens": ["Rosalía", "wins", "big", "at", "the", "Latin", "Grammy", "Awards", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Volodymyr Zelensky calls for peace talks in Ukraine.", "tokens": ["Volodymyr", "Zelensky", "calls", "for", "peace", "talks", "in", "Ukraine", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "World Bank Group announces new investment initiative in developing countries.", "tokens": ["World", "Bank", "Group", "announces", "new", "investment", "initiative", "in", "developing", "countries", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Elon Musk announces SpaceX's plan to send humans to Mars by 2026.", "tokens": ["Elon", "Musk", "announces", "SpaceX", "'", "s", "plan", "to", "send", "humans", "to", "Mars", "by", "2026", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Apple's new iPhone 13 to be released next month.", "tokens": ["Apple", "'", "s", "new", "iPhone", "13", "to", "be", "released", "next", "month", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "President Biden signs $1.2 trillion infrastructure bill into law.", "tokens": ["President", "Biden", "signs", "$", "1", ".", "2", "trillion", "infrastructure", "bill", "into", "law", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The Indian government announces new policies to address air pollution in Delhi.", "tokens": ["The", "Indian", "government", "announces", "new", "policies", "to", "address", "air", "pollution", "in", "Delhi", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Protesters gather in Delhi to demand change in government policies.", "tokens": ["Protesters", "gather", "in", "Delhi", "to", "demand", "change", "in", "government", "policies", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Delhi schools to remain closed due to severe air pollution levels.", "tokens": ["Delhi", "schools", "to", "remain", "closed", "due", "to", "severe", "air", "pollution", "levels", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "United Nations Development Programme allocates $10 million for education projects in Africa.", "tokens": ["United", "Nations", "Development", "Programme", "allocates", "$", "10", "million", "for", "education", "projects", "in", "Africa", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Renowned economist Joseph Stiglitz joins United Nations Development Programme as senior advisor.", "tokens": ["Renowned", "economist", "Joseph", "Stiglitz", "joins", "United", "Nations", "Development", "Programme", "as", "senior", "advisor", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "United Nations Development Programme launches initiative to combat climate change in vulnerable island nations.", "tokens": ["United", "Nations", "Development", "Programme", "launches", "initiative", "to", "combat", "climate", "change", "in", "vulnerable", "island", "nations", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX successfully launches 60 more Starlink satellites.", "tokens": ["Elon", "Musk", "'", "s", "SpaceX", "successfully", "launches", "60", "more", "Starlink", "satellites", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The United Nations reports a record number of refugees fleeing conflict in the Middle East.", "tokens": ["The", "United", "Nations", "reports", "a", "record", "number", "of", "refugees", "fleeing", "conflict", "in", "the", "Middle", "East", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "President Biden signs executive order to address climate change.", "tokens": ["President", "Biden", "signs", "executive", "order", "to", "address", "climate", "change", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Kourtney Kardashian launches her new lifestyle brand Poosh.", "tokens": ["Kourtney", "Kardashian", "launches", "her", "new", "lifestyle", "brand", "Poosh", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "New York City mayor announces plan to expand affordable housing options.", "tokens": ["New", "York", "City", "mayor", "announces", "plan", "to", "expand", "affordable", "housing", "options", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tesla's stock reaches record high after strong quarterly earnings report.", "tokens": ["Tesla", "'", "s", "stock", "reaches", "record", "high", "after", "strong", "quarterly", "earnings", "report", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX successfully launches satellite into orbit.", "tokens": ["Elon", "Musk", "'", "s", "SpaceX", "successfully", "launches", "satellite", "into", "orbit", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "New York City announces plan to invest $100 million in affordable housing.", "tokens": ["New", "York", "City", "announces", "plan", "to", "invest", "$", "100", "million", "in", "affordable", "housing", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Apple Inc. reports record-breaking sales for latest iPhone model.", "tokens": ["Apple", "Inc", ".", "reports", "record", "-", "breaking", "sales", "for", "latest", "iPhone", "model", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The United Nations calls for a cease-fire in the ongoing conflict in Syria.", "tokens": ["The", "United", "Nations", "calls", "for", "a", "cease", "-", "fire", "in", "the", "ongoing", "conflict", "in", "Syria", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Edinburgh's population reaches over 500,000 for the first time.", "tokens": ["Edinburgh", "'", "s", "population", "reaches", "over", "500", ",", "000", "for", "the", "first", "time", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "David Beckham invests in new esports organization.", "tokens": ["David", "Beckham", "invests", "in", "new", "esports", "organization", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Record number of visitors flock to Edinburgh Festival.", "tokens": ["Record", "number", "of", "visitors", "flock", "to", "Edinburgh", "Festival", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The World Trade Organization released a report on global trade tensions.", "tokens": ["The", "World", "Trade", "Organization", "released", "a", "report", "on", "global", "trade", "tensions", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The International Energy Agency predicts a decrease in oil demand for the next quarter.", "tokens": ["The", "International", "Energy", "Agency", "predicts", "a", "decrease", "in", "oil", "demand", "for", "the", "next", "quarter", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The United States, China, and the European Union are in talks to address trade imbalances.", "tokens": ["The", "United", "States", ",", "China", ",", "and", "the", "European", "Union", "are", "in", "talks", "to", "address", "trade", "imbalances", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-location", "I-location", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tesla unveils new electric car with longer battery life.", "tokens": ["Tesla", "unveils", "new", "electric", "car", "with", "longer", "battery", "life", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Angela Merkel elected as Chancellor of Germany for the fourth term.", "tokens": ["Angela", "Merkel", "elected", "as", "Chancellor", "of", "Germany", "for", "the", "fourth", "term", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Amazon announces plans to open new headquarters in New York City.", "tokens": ["Amazon", "announces", "plans", "to", "open", "new", "headquarters", "in", "New", "York", "City", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "George W. Bush delivers keynote speech at Nairobi economic summit.", "tokens": ["George", "W", ".", "Bush", "delivers", "keynote", "speech", "at", "Nairobi", "economic", "summit", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "I-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "New business startup in Nairobi sees rapid growth in its first year.", "tokens": ["New", "business", "startup", "in", "Nairobi", "sees", "rapid", "growth", "in", "its", "first", "year", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "George W. Bush Foundation for Military Service members announces new scholarship program.", "tokens": ["George", "W", ".", "Bush", "Foundation", "for", "Military", "Service", "members", "announces", "new", "scholarship", "program", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "I-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "David Beckham announces his retirement from professional soccer.", "tokens": ["David", "Beckham", "announces", "his", "retirement", "from", "professional", "soccer", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "IBM Corporation reports a 15% increase in quarterly profits.", "tokens": ["IBM", "Corporation", "reports", "a", "15", "%", "increase", "in", "quarterly", "profits", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The Democratic National Committee reveals its latest campaign strategy for the upcoming election.", "tokens": ["The", "Democratic", "National", "Committee", "reveals", "its", "latest", "campaign", "strategy", "for", "the", "upcoming", "election", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The peace talks in Reykjavik have reached a deadlock.", "tokens": ["The", "peace", "talks", "in", "Reykjavik", "have", "reached", "a", "deadlock", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Sony announces the release of their new gaming console next month.", "tokens": ["Sony", "announces", "the", "release", "of", "their", "new", "gaming", "console", "next", "month", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Taliban insurgents have launched a series of attacks in the region.", "tokens": ["Taliban", "insurgents", "have", "launched", "a", "series", "of", "attacks", "in", "the", "region", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The Federal Trade Commission investigates allegations of antitrust violations in the tech industry.", "tokens": ["The", "Federal", "Trade", "Commission", "investigates", "allegations", "of", "antitrust", "violations", "in", "the", "tech", "industry", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Vienna to host international summit on climate change next month.", "tokens": ["Vienna", "to", "host", "international", "summit", "on", "climate", "change", "next", "month", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Amal Clooney speaks at United Nations conference on human rights.", "tokens": ["Amal", "Clooney", "speaks", "at", "United", "Nations", "conference", "on", "human", "rights", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The embassy in Moscow remains closed amid escalating tensions.", "tokens": ["The", "embassy", "in", "Moscow", "remains", "closed", "amid", "escalating", "tensions", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Brasília mayor announces plan to improve public transportation system.", "tokens": ["Brasília", "mayor", "announces", "plan", "to", "improve", "public", "transportation", "system", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Prominent artist from Moscow to showcase new exhibition in New York.", "tokens": ["Prominent", "artist", "from", "Moscow", "to", "showcase", "new", "exhibition", "in", "New", "York", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tesla announces new electric car model.", "tokens": ["Tesla", "announces", "new", "electric", "car", "model", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tokyo Olympics officially begin with opening ceremony.", "tokens": ["Tokyo", "Olympics", "officially", "begin", "with", "opening", "ceremony", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Dr. Johnson appointed as new CEO of pharmaceutical company.", "tokens": ["Dr", ".", "Johnson", "appointed", "as", "new", "CEO", "of", "pharmaceutical", "company", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tom Hanks to star in new sci-fi thriller directed by Christopher Nolan.", "tokens": ["Tom", "Hanks", "to", "star", "in", "new", "sci", "-", "fi", "thriller", "directed", "by", "Christopher", "Nolan", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Local charity organization to host fundraising event with special appearance by Tom Hanks.", "tokens": ["Local", "charity", "organization", "to", "host", "fundraising", "event", "with", "special", "appearance", "by", "Tom", "Hanks", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tom Hanks donates $1 million to children's hospital for new research wing.", "tokens": ["Tom", "Hanks", "donates", "$", "1", "million", "to", "children", "'", "s", "hospital", "for", "new", "research", "wing", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Brad Pitt signs deal with major film production company.", "tokens": ["Brad", "Pitt", "signs", "deal", "with", "major", "film", "production", "company", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Brad Pitt to attend premiere of new movie in New York City.", "tokens": ["Brad", "Pitt", "to", "attend", "premiere", "of", "new", "movie", "in", "New", "York", "City", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Environmental organization led by Brad Pitt launches new conservation initiative.", "tokens": ["Environmental", "organization", "led", "by", "Brad", "Pitt", "launches", "new", "conservation", "initiative", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Technology company Apple Inc. introduces new line of iPhones.", "tokens": ["Technology", "company", "Apple", "Inc", ".", "introduces", "new", "line", "of", "iPhones", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Jennifer Lopez and Ben Affleck spotted together in Los Angeles.", "tokens": ["Jennifer", "Lopez", "and", "Ben", "Affleck", "spotted", "together", "in", "Los", "Angeles", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "United Nations reports humanitarian crisis in war-torn region.", "tokens": ["United", "Nations", "reports", "humanitarian", "crisis", "in", "war", "-", "torn", "region", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX successfully launches new satellite into orbit.", "tokens": ["Elon", "Musk", "'", "s", "SpaceX", "successfully", "launches", "new", "satellite", "into", "orbit", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tropical storm warning issued for Florida coast.", "tokens": ["Tropical", "storm", "warning", "issued", "for", "Florida", "coast", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Hollywood actress Angelina Jolie donates $1 million to refugee charity.", "tokens": ["Hollywood", "actress", "Angelina", "Jolie", "donates", "$", "1", "million", "to", "refugee", "charity", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "NATO strengthens its military presence in Eastern Europe.", "tokens": ["NATO", "strengthens", "its", "military", "presence", "in", "Eastern", "Europe", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Bank of America announces plans to close several branches in the Midwest.", "tokens": ["Bank", "of", "America", "announces", "plans", "to", "close", "several", "branches", "in", "the", "Midwest", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Malala Yousafzai receives the Nobel Peace Prize.", "tokens": ["Malala", "Yousafzai", "receives", "the", "Nobel", "Peace", "Prize", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The United Nations Security Council condemns the recent missile tests by North Korea.", "tokens": ["The", "United", "Nations", "Security", "Council", "condemns", "the", "recent", "missile", "tests", "by", "North", "Korea", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Famous chef Jamie Oliver opens new restaurant in New York City.", "tokens": ["Famous", "chef", "Jamie", "Oliver", "opens", "new", "restaurant", "in", "New", "York", "City", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Renowned chef Gordon Ramsay to open new restaurant in Los Angeles.", "tokens": ["Renowned", "chef", "Gordon", "Ramsay", "to", "open", "new", "restaurant", "in", "Los", "Angeles", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Stocks surge as Apple Inc. announces record-breaking quarterly earnings.", "tokens": ["Stocks", "surge", "as", "Apple", "Inc", ".", "announces", "record", "-", "breaking", "quarterly", "earnings", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tesla unveils new electric car model.", "tokens": ["Tesla", "unveils", "new", "electric", "car", "model", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "President Biden to visit European Union headquarters in Brussels next week.", "tokens": ["President", "Biden", "to", "visit", "European", "Union", "headquarters", "in", "Brussels", "next", "week", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Wildfires in California continue to threaten homes and natural habitats.", "tokens": ["Wildfires", "in", "California", "continue", "to", "threaten", "homes", "and", "natural", "habitats", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tech giants Apple and Google to release new smartphones next week.", "tokens": ["Tech", "giants", "Apple", "and", "Google", "to", "release", "new", "smartphones", "next", "week", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "President Biden announces new infrastructure plan.", "tokens": ["President", "Biden", "announces", "new", "infrastructure", "plan", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Shakira's charity organization donates $1 million to the earthquake relief efforts in Haiti.", "tokens": ["Shakira", "'", "s", "charity", "organization", "donates", "$", "1", "million", "to", "the", "earthquake", "relief", "efforts", "in", "Haiti", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Justin Trudeau announces new measures to combat climate change at the United Nations summit in New York.", "tokens": ["Justin", "Trudeau", "announces", "new", "measures", "to", "combat", "climate", "change", "at", "the", "United", "Nations", "summit", "in", "New", "York", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Hip-hop mogul Jay-Z launches new streaming service.", "tokens": ["Hip", "-", "hop", "mogul", "Jay", "-", "Z", "launches", "new", "streaming", "service", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Beyoncé and Jay-Z plan to buy a luxury villa in Italy.", "tokens": ["Beyoncé", "and", "Jay", "-", "Z", "plan", "to", "buy", "a", "luxury", "villa", "in", "Italy", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Jay-Z's music label signs new up-and-coming artist.", "tokens": ["Jay", "-", "Z", "'", "s", "music", "label", "signs", "new", "up", "-", "and", "-", "coming", "artist", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Singapore reports record number of new COVID-19 cases.", "tokens": ["Singapore", "reports", "record", "number", "of", "new", "COVID", "-", "19", "cases", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Meghan Markle launches new charitable foundation.", "tokens": ["Meghan", "Markle", "launches", "new", "charitable", "foundation", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Singapore Airlines announces partnership with international hotel chain.", "tokens": ["Singapore", "Airlines", "announces", "partnership", "with", "international", "hotel", "chain", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Charlize Theron wins Best Actress award at the Oscars.", "tokens": ["Charlize", "Theron", "wins", "Best", "Actress", "award", "at", "the", "Oscars", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Panama City announces new plans for public transportation system.", "tokens": ["Panama", "City", "announces", "new", "plans", "for", "public", "transportation", "system", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Beirut explosion leaves hundreds dead and injured.", "tokens": ["Beirut", "explosion", "leaves", "hundreds", "dead", "and", "injured", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Rome mayor announces new COVID-19 restrictions for city residents.", "tokens": ["Rome", "mayor", "announces", "new", "COVID", "-", "19", "restrictions", "for", "city", "residents", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Celebrity chef opens new restaurant in Beirut.", "tokens": ["Celebrity", "chef", "opens", "new", "restaurant", "in", "Beirut", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Academy Award-winner George Clooney to direct and star in new political thriller.", "tokens": ["Academy", "Award", "-", "winner", "George", "Clooney", "to", "direct", "and", "star", "in", "new", "political", "thriller", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Ocean conservation organization, founded by George Clooney, raises $1 million in charity auction.", "tokens": ["Ocean", "conservation", "organization", ",", "founded", "by", "George", "Clooney", ",", "raises", "$", "1", "million", "in", "charity", "auction", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "George Clooney's new film tops box office in opening weekend.", "tokens": ["George", "Clooney", "'", "s", "new", "film", "tops", "box", "office", "in", "opening", "weekend", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "NATO to increase presence in Eastern Europe to deter Russian aggression.", "tokens": ["NATO", "to", "increase", "presence", "in", "Eastern", "Europe", "to", "deter", "Russian", "aggression", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "B-person", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Cybersecurity concerns prompt NATO to hold emergency meeting.", "tokens": ["Cybersecurity", "concerns", "prompt", "NATO", "to", "hold", "emergency", "meeting", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Member nations of NATO commit to increase defense spending.", "tokens": ["Member", "nations", "of", "NATO", "commit", "to", "increase", "defense", "spending", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tesla CEO Elon Musk announces plans to build new gigafactory in Texas.", "tokens": ["Tesla", "CEO", "Elon", "Musk", "announces", "plans", "to", "build", "new", "gigafactory", "in", "Texas", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "China inaugurates the world's longest sea bridge connecting Hong Kong, Macau, and Zhuhai.", "tokens": ["China", "inaugurates", "the", "world", "'", "s", "longest", "sea", "bridge", "connecting", "Hong", "Kong", ",", "Macau", ",", "and", "Zhuhai", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "UNICEF launches vaccination campaign in war-torn Syrian city.", "tokens": ["UNICEF", "launches", "vaccination", "campaign", "in", "war", "-", "torn", "Syrian", "city", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Michelle Obama to release new memoir next year.", "tokens": ["Michelle", "Obama", "to", "release", "new", "memoir", "next", "year", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Robert Downey Jr. to star in new superhero movie.", "tokens": ["Robert", "Downey", "Jr", ".", "to", "star", "in", "new", "superhero", "movie", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "I-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Zlatan Ibrahimovic signs new contract with LA Galaxy.", "tokens": ["Zlatan", "Ibrahimovic", "signs", "new", "contract", "with", "LA", "Galaxy", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The Federal Aviation Administration issued an emergency order to fix Boeing 737 MAX planes.", "tokens": ["The", "Federal", "Aviation", "Administration", "issued", "an", "emergency", "order", "to", "fix", "Boeing", "737", "MAX", "planes", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Condoleezza Rice met with world leaders in Singapore to discuss international security.", "tokens": ["Condoleezza", "Rice", "met", "with", "world", "leaders", "in", "Singapore", "to", "discuss", "international", "security", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Singapore announced a new initiative to promote renewable energy.", "tokens": ["Singapore", "announced", "a", "new", "initiative", "to", "promote", "renewable", "energy", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Ford Motor Company announces plans to invest $22 billion in electric vehicles.", "tokens": ["Ford", "Motor", "Company", "announces", "plans", "to", "invest", "$", "22", "billion", "in", "electric", "vehicles", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The CEO of Ford Motor Company predicts a surge in demand for electric cars in the next decade.", "tokens": ["The", "CEO", "of", "Ford", "Motor", "Company", "predicts", "a", "surge", "in", "demand", "for", "electric", "cars", "in", "the", "next", "decade", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-person", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Ford Motor Company to open a new manufacturing plant in Mexico.", "tokens": ["Ford", "Motor", "Company", "to", "open", "a", "new", "manufacturing", "plant", "in", "Mexico", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The United Nations has issued a warning about the humanitarian crisis in Yemen.", "tokens": ["The", "United", "Nations", "has", "issued", "a", "warning", "about", "the", "humanitarian", "crisis", "in", "Yemen", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tesla announces plans to build a new Gigafactory in Germany.", "tokens": ["Tesla", "announces", "plans", "to", "build", "a", "new", "Gigafactory", "in", "Germany", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Jennifer Lopez and Alex Rodriguez call off their engagement.", "tokens": ["Jennifer", "Lopez", "and", "Alex", "Rodriguez", "call", "off", "their", "engagement", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Ariana Grande's new single breaks record on Twitter.", "tokens": ["Ariana", "Grande", "'", "s", "new", "single", "breaks", "record", "on", "Twitter", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Twitter announces new policy on hate speech.", "tokens": ["Twitter", "announces", "new", "policy", "on", "hate", "speech", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Ariana Grande surprises fans with impromptu performance in New York City.", "tokens": ["Ariana", "Grande", "surprises", "fans", "with", "impromptu", "performance", "in", "New", "York", "City", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Marco Rubio visits Riyadh for diplomatic talks.", "tokens": ["Marco", "Rubio", "visits", "Riyadh", "for", "diplomatic", "talks", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "San Francisco's Bay Area Rapid Transit system faces criticism for delays.", "tokens": ["San", "Francisco", "'", "s", "Bay", "Area", "Rapid", "Transit", "system", "faces", "criticism", "for", "delays", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Breaking news: Riyadh-based organization announces partnership with major tech company.", "tokens": ["Breaking", "news", ":", "Riyadh", "-", "based", "organization", "announces", "partnership", "with", "major", "tech", "company", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Quentin Tarantino announces his upcoming film project at a press conference in Los Angeles.", "tokens": ["Quentin", "Tarantino", "announces", "his", "upcoming", "film", "project", "at", "a", "press", "conference", "in", "Los", "Angeles", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Planned Parenthood to open a new health clinic in downtown Portland next month.", "tokens": ["Planned", "Parenthood", "to", "open", "a", "new", "health", "clinic", "in", "downtown", "Portland", "next", "month", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Actress Emma Stone praises Quentin Tarantino's latest movie at the premiere in New York City.", "tokens": ["Actress", "Emma", "Stone", "praises", "Quentin", "Tarantino", "'", "s", "latest", "movie", "at", "the", "premiere", "in", "New", "York", "City", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Al Jazeera Media Network reports record viewership for its latest documentary series on wildlife conservation.", "tokens": ["Al", "Jazeera", "Media", "Network", "reports", "record", "viewership", "for", "its", "latest", "documentary", "series", "on", "wildlife", "conservation", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The United Nations condemns the ongoing violence in Myanmar and calls for immediate action to protect civilians.", "tokens": ["The", "United", "Nations", "condemns", "the", "ongoing", "violence", "in", "Myanmar", "and", "calls", "for", "immediate", "action", "to", "protect", "civilians", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Environmental activist Greta Thunberg meets with European Union leaders to discuss climate change policy.", "tokens": ["Environmental", "activist", "Greta", "Thunberg", "meets", "with", "European", "Union", "leaders", "to", "discuss", "climate", "change", "policy", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The OPEC members met in Wellington to discuss oil production cuts.", "tokens": ["The", "OPEC", "members", "met", "in", "Wellington", "to", "discuss", "oil", "production", "cuts", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Rio de Janeiro to host the 2024 Summer Olympics.", "tokens": ["Rio", "de", "Janeiro", "to", "host", "the", "2024", "Summer", "Olympics", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Iran, Iraq, and Kuwait are key members of OPEC.", "tokens": ["Iran", ",", "Iraq", ",", "and", "Kuwait", "are", "key", "members", "of", "OPEC", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Xi Jinping calls for increased international cooperation in addressing climate change", "tokens": ["Xi", "Jinping", "calls", "for", "increased", "international", "cooperation", "in", "addressing", "climate", "change"], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Global leaders gather in New York for United Nations General Assembly", "tokens": ["Global", "leaders", "gather", "in", "New", "York", "for", "United", "Nations", "General", "Assembly"], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization"]}
{"sentence": "Government announces new measures to boost economy and tackle inflation, says Xi Jinping", "tokens": ["Government", "announces", "new", "measures", "to", "boost", "economy", "and", "tackle", "inflation", ",", "says", "Xi", "Jinping"], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-person", "I-person"]}
{"sentence": "Instagram introduces new feature to help users combat cyberbullying.", "tokens": ["Instagram", "introduces", "new", "feature", "to", "help", "users", "combat", "cyberbullying", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The European Space Agency plans to launch a new mission to study exoplanets.", "tokens": ["The", "European", "Space", "Agency", "plans", "to", "launch", "a", "new", "mission", "to", "study", "exoplanets", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Washington D.C. mayor announces new initiative to improve public transportation system.", "tokens": ["Washington", "D", ".", "C", ".", "mayor", "announces", "new", "initiative", "to", "improve", "public", "transportation", "system", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Cairo to implement new public transportation system.", "tokens": ["Cairo", "to", "implement", "new", "public", "transportation", "system", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Former New York City Mayor David Dinkins passes away at 93.", "tokens": ["Former", "New", "York", "City", "Mayor", "David", "Dinkins", "passes", "away", "at", "93", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "UNESCO and WHO collaborate on global health and education initiative.", "tokens": ["UNESCO", "and", "WHO", "collaborate", "on", "global", "health", "and", "education", "initiative", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Greenpeace activists protest in Caracas over environmental issues.", "tokens": ["Greenpeace", "activists", "protest", "in", "Caracas", "over", "environmental", "issues", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Caracas mayor announces new public transportation initiative.", "tokens": ["Caracas", "mayor", "announces", "new", "public", "transportation", "initiative", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Greenpeace launches campaign against air pollution in major cities.", "tokens": ["Greenpeace", "launches", "campaign", "against", "air", "pollution", "in", "major", "cities", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Cairo experiences record-breaking heat wave in July.", "tokens": ["Cairo", "experiences", "record", "-", "breaking", "heat", "wave", "in", "July", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Dallas-based company announces merger with international firm.", "tokens": ["Dallas", "-", "based", "company", "announces", "merger", "with", "international", "firm", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Violent protests erupt in downtown Cairo over economic reforms.", "tokens": ["Violent", "protests", "erupt", "in", "downtown", "Cairo", "over", "economic", "reforms", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "New York Times reveals investigation into government corruption.", "tokens": ["New", "York", "Times", "reveals", "investigation", "into", "government", "corruption", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Economist John Smith predicts global recession in coming months.", "tokens": ["Economist", "John", "Smith", "predicts", "global", "recession", "in", "coming", "months", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "New York Times investigation uncovers environmental violations by major oil company.", "tokens": ["New", "York", "Times", "investigation", "uncovers", "environmental", "violations", "by", "major", "oil", "company", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Google LLC announces new headquarters in Brussels.", "tokens": ["Google", "LLC", "announces", "new", "headquarters", "in", "Brussels", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Brussels to host international climate summit.", "tokens": ["Brussels", "to", "host", "international", "climate", "summit", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Google LLC unveils plans for renewable energy investment.", "tokens": ["Google", "LLC", "unveils", "plans", "for", "renewable", "energy", "investment", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The American Cancer Society is funding a new research study on potential cancer treatments.", "tokens": ["The", "American", "Cancer", "Society", "is", "funding", "a", "new", "research", "study", "on", "potential", "cancer", "treatments", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The New York Times reported on the increase in cyber attacks targeting government agencies.", "tokens": ["The", "New", "York", "Times", "reported", "on", "the", "increase", "in", "cyber", "attacks", "targeting", "government", "agencies", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "An American Cancer Society fundraiser in Chicago raised over $100,000 for cancer research.", "tokens": ["An", "American", "Cancer", "Society", "fundraiser", "in", "Chicago", "raised", "over", "$", "100", ",", "000", "for", "cancer", "research", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Oxfam International launches emergency appeal for humanitarian aid in war-torn region.", "tokens": ["Oxfam", "International", "launches", "emergency", "appeal", "for", "humanitarian", "aid", "in", "war", "-", "torn", "region", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Renowned economist Dr. Angela Li appointed as the new director of Oxfam International's economic research division.", "tokens": ["Renowned", "economist", "Dr", ".", "Angela", "Li", "appointed", "as", "the", "new", "director", "of", "Oxfam", "International", "'", "s", "economic", "research", "division", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "I-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The annual report from Oxfam International highlights the growing income inequality in developing countries.", "tokens": ["The", "annual", "report", "from", "Oxfam", "International", "highlights", "the", "growing", "income", "inequality", "in", "developing", "countries", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Israel announces new security measures in response to recent attacks in Tel Aviv.", "tokens": ["Israel", "announces", "new", "security", "measures", "in", "response", "to", "recent", "attacks", "in", "Tel", "Aviv", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "New study shows increasing air pollution levels in Tel Aviv.", "tokens": ["New", "study", "shows", "increasing", "air", "pollution", "levels", "in", "Tel", "Aviv", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tel Aviv University receives $10 million donation for new research center.", "tokens": ["Tel", "Aviv", "University", "receives", "$", "10", "million", "donation", "for", "new", "research", "center", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Montreal Canadiens defeat Toronto Maple Leafs in overtime thriller.", "tokens": ["Montreal", "Canadiens", "defeat", "Toronto", "Maple", "Leafs", "in", "overtime", "thriller", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "B-organization", "O", "B-location", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Prince William visits wildfire-ravaged communities in Western Canada.", "tokens": ["Prince", "William", "visits", "wildfire", "-", "ravaged", "communities", "in", "Western", "Canada", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Lisbon hosts international climate change conference.", "tokens": ["Lisbon", "hosts", "international", "climate", "change", "conference", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "South Korea reports record high temperatures as heatwave hits Seoul.", "tokens": ["South", "Korea", "reports", "record", "high", "temperatures", "as", "heatwave", "hits", "Seoul", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Seoul Mayor announces new initiative to reduce air pollution in the city.", "tokens": ["Seoul", "Mayor", "announces", "new", "initiative", "to", "reduce", "air", "pollution", "in", "the", "city", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Major electronics company headquartered in Seoul sees 15% increase in profits.", "tokens": ["Major", "electronics", "company", "headquartered", "in", "Seoul", "sees", "15", "%", "increase", "in", "profits", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Justice Stephen Breyer announces retirement from the Supreme Court.", "tokens": ["Justice", "Stephen", "Breyer", "announces", "retirement", "from", "the", "Supreme", "Court", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O"]}
{"sentence": "New York City declares state of emergency due to rising COVID-19 cases.", "tokens": ["New", "York", "City", "declares", "state", "of", "emergency", "due", "to", "rising", "COVID", "-", "19", "cases", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX launches another batch of Starlink satellites into orbit.", "tokens": ["Elon", "Musk", "'", "s", "SpaceX", "launches", "another", "batch", "of", "Starlink", "satellites", "into", "orbit", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Cairo, Egypt's capital, experiences record high temperatures.", "tokens": ["Cairo", ",", "Egypt", "'", "s", "capital", ",", "experiences", "record", "high", "temperatures", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "International Monetary Fund approves $12 billion loan to Egypt to support economic reform efforts.", "tokens": ["International", "Monetary", "Fund", "approves", "$", "12", "billion", "loan", "to", "Egypt", "to", "support", "economic", "reform", "efforts", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Cairo University professor wins prestigious award for research in environmental science.", "tokens": ["Cairo", "University", "professor", "wins", "prestigious", "award", "for", "research", "in", "environmental", "science", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The United Nations releases report on global poverty and inequality.", "tokens": ["The", "United", "Nations", "releases", "report", "on", "global", "poverty", "and", "inequality", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX plans to launch new satellite into orbit next month.", "tokens": ["Elon", "Musk", "'", "s", "SpaceX", "plans", "to", "launch", "new", "satellite", "into", "orbit", "next", "month", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "New York City to invest $10 million in affordable housing initiative.", "tokens": ["New", "York", "City", "to", "invest", "$", "10", "million", "in", "affordable", "housing", "initiative", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX launches new satellite into orbit.", "tokens": ["Elon", "Musk", "'", "s", "SpaceX", "launches", "new", "satellite", "into", "orbit", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "China's President Xi Jinping visits Russia for trade talks.", "tokens": ["China", "'", "s", "President", "Xi", "Jinping", "visits", "Russia", "for", "trade", "talks", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "I-person", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "New York City implements new regulations on food delivery services.", "tokens": ["New", "York", "City", "implements", "new", "regulations", "on", "food", "delivery", "services", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Queen Elizabeth attends opening ceremony of new hospital.", "tokens": ["Queen", "Elizabeth", "attends", "opening", "ceremony", "of", "new", "hospital", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Annual meeting of World Health Organization attended by representatives from 194 countries", "tokens": ["Annual", "meeting", "of", "World", "Health", "Organization", "attended", "by", "representatives", "from", "194", "countries"], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Protests in front of Parliament demand resignation of Prime Minister following corruption scandal.", "tokens": ["Protests", "in", "front", "of", "Parliament", "demand", "resignation", "of", "Prime", "Minister", "following", "corruption", "scandal", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Beauty YouTuber Jeffree Star launches new makeup line.", "tokens": ["Beauty", "YouTuber", "Jeffree", "Star", "launches", "new", "makeup", "line", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Angela Davis gives powerful speech at civil rights event.", "tokens": ["Angela", "Davis", "gives", "powerful", "speech", "at", "civil", "rights", "event", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Jeffree Star's cosmetics company experiences rapid growth in sales.", "tokens": ["Jeffree", "Star", "'", "s", "cosmetics", "company", "experiences", "rapid", "growth", "in", "sales", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The American Red Cross provides humanitarian aid to flood victims in the Midwest.", "tokens": ["The", "American", "Red", "Cross", "provides", "humanitarian", "aid", "to", "flood", "victims", "in", "the", "Midwest", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "International Organization for Migration assists in relocation efforts for refugees from war-torn regions.", "tokens": ["International", "Organization", "for", "Migration", "assists", "in", "relocation", "efforts", "for", "refugees", "from", "war", "-", "torn", "regions", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "American Red Cross mobilizes volunteers to help with disaster relief efforts in hurricane-affected areas.", "tokens": ["American", "Red", "Cross", "mobilizes", "volunteers", "to", "help", "with", "disaster", "relief", "efforts", "in", "hurricane", "-", "affected", "areas", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Shakira to headline concert in Atlanta this weekend.", "tokens": ["Shakira", "to", "headline", "concert", "in", "Atlanta", "this", "weekend", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The Democratic National Committee releases statement on healthcare legislation.", "tokens": ["The", "Democratic", "National", "Committee", "releases", "statement", "on", "healthcare", "legislation", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Atlanta Mayor announces new initiative to improve public transportation.", "tokens": ["Atlanta", "Mayor", "announces", "new", "initiative", "to", "improve", "public", "transportation", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tesla CEO Elon Musk unveils new electric vehicle model.", "tokens": ["Tesla", "CEO", "Elon", "Musk", "unveils", "new", "electric", "vehicle", "model", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tropical storm hits Southeast Asia, causing widespread flooding.", "tokens": ["Tropical", "storm", "hits", "Southeast", "Asia", ",", "causing", "widespread", "flooding", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Amazon to acquire popular streaming service for $8 billion.", "tokens": ["Amazon", "to", "acquire", "popular", "streaming", "service", "for", "$", "8", "billion", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Jeff Goldblum to make guest appearance at Johannesburg film festival.", "tokens": ["Jeff", "Goldblum", "to", "make", "guest", "appearance", "at", "Johannesburg", "film", "festival", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Facebook faces lawsuit over data privacy breach.", "tokens": ["Facebook", "faces", "lawsuit", "over", "data", "privacy", "breach", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Johannesburg Mayor renews commitment to solving city's housing crisis.", "tokens": ["Johannesburg", "Mayor", "renews", "commitment", "to", "solving", "city", "'", "s", "housing", "crisis", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "United Parcel Service announces partnership with Amazon for drone delivery.", "tokens": ["United", "Parcel", "Service", "announces", "partnership", "with", "Amazon", "for", "drone", "delivery", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Stockholm, Sweden experienced record high temperatures during the heatwave.", "tokens": ["Stockholm", ",", "Sweden", "experienced", "record", "high", "temperatures", "during", "the", "heatwave", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Mitch McConnell introduces new legislation to address infrastructure issues.", "tokens": ["Mitch", "McConnell", "introduces", "new", "legislation", "to", "address", "infrastructure", "issues", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Protesters gather outside Mitch McConnell's office in downtown Louisville.", "tokens": ["Protesters", "gather", "outside", "Mitch", "McConnell", "'", "s", "office", "in", "downtown", "Louisville", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Senate Majority Leader Mitch McConnell delivers speech on immigration reform.", "tokens": ["Senate", "Majority", "Leader", "Mitch", "McConnell", "delivers", "speech", "on", "immigration", "reform", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Mitch McConnell announces new legislation focused on healthcare reform.", "tokens": ["Mitch", "McConnell", "announces", "new", "legislation", "focused", "on", "healthcare", "reform", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The stock market experienced a sharp decline following Mitch McConnell's speech.", "tokens": ["The", "stock", "market", "experienced", "a", "sharp", "decline", "following", "Mitch", "McConnell", "'", "s", "speech", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Mitch McConnell meets with leaders from various organizations to discuss economic stimulus plans.", "tokens": ["Mitch", "McConnell", "meets", "with", "leaders", "from", "various", "organizations", "to", "discuss", "economic", "stimulus", "plans", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX successfully launches 60 internet satellites.", "tokens": ["Elon", "Musk", "'", "s", "SpaceX", "successfully", "launches", "60", "internet", "satellites", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tokyo Olympics to be held without spectators amid COVID-19 concerns.", "tokens": ["Tokyo", "Olympics", "to", "be", "held", "without", "spectators", "amid", "COVID", "-", "19", "concerns", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Apple unveils new line of iPhone models at annual product launch event.", "tokens": ["Apple", "unveils", "new", "line", "of", "iPhone", "models", "at", "annual", "product", "launch", "event", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Nicole Kidman set to star in new thriller film.", "tokens": ["Nicole", "Kidman", "set", "to", "star", "in", "new", "thriller", "film", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Microsoft Corporation announces plans to acquire artificial intelligence startup.", "tokens": ["Microsoft", "Corporation", "announces", "plans", "to", "acquire", "artificial", "intelligence", "startup", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Local woman wins prestigious science award.", "tokens": ["Local", "woman", "wins", "prestigious", "science", "award", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Oslo city council introduces new recycling program to reduce waste and promote sustainability.", "tokens": ["Oslo", "city", "council", "introduces", "new", "recycling", "program", "to", "reduce", "waste", "and", "promote", "sustainability", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Islamabad police arrest suspected kidnapper in ongoing investigation.", "tokens": ["Islamabad", "police", "arrest", "suspected", "kidnapper", "in", "ongoing", "investigation", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Islamabad-based organization provides relief aid to flood-affected regions in the country.", "tokens": ["Islamabad", "-", "based", "organization", "provides", "relief", "aid", "to", "flood", "-", "affected", "regions", "in", "the", "country", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "LeBron James signs multi-year contract with Los Angeles Lakers.", "tokens": ["LeBron", "James", "signs", "multi", "-", "year", "contract", "with", "Los", "Angeles", "Lakers", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Chevron Corporation to invest $10 billion in renewable energy projects over the next decade.", "tokens": ["Chevron", "Corporation", "to", "invest", "$", "10", "billion", "in", "renewable", "energy", "projects", "over", "the", "next", "decade", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The annual summit in Davos gathers global leaders to discuss economic and environmental issues.", "tokens": ["The", "annual", "summit", "in", "Davos", "gathers", "global", "leaders", "to", "discuss", "economic", "and", "environmental", "issues", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The International Criminal Police Organization issues a global alert for wanted fugitive.", "tokens": ["The", "International", "Criminal", "Police", "Organization", "issues", "a", "global", "alert", "for", "wanted", "fugitive", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The European Central Bank raises interest rates in response to rising inflation.", "tokens": ["The", "European", "Central", "Bank", "raises", "interest", "rates", "in", "response", "to", "rising", "inflation", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Renowned economist Maria Yellen appointed as the new chair of the International Monetary Fund.", "tokens": ["Renowned", "economist", "Maria", "Yellen", "appointed", "as", "the", "new", "chair", "of", "the", "International", "Monetary", "Fund", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Mitt Romney announces bid for Senate.", "tokens": ["Mitt", "Romney", "announces", "bid", "for", "Senate", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "International Criminal Police Organization issues global arrest warrant for notorious drug lord.", "tokens": ["International", "Criminal", "Police", "Organization", "issues", "global", "arrest", "warrant", "for", "notorious", "drug", "lord", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "North Atlantic Treaty Organization responds to increased military activity near Eastern border.", "tokens": ["North", "Atlantic", "Treaty", "Organization", "responds", "to", "increased", "military", "activity", "near", "Eastern", "border", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX launches a new satellite into orbit.", "tokens": ["Elon", "Musk", "'", "s", "SpaceX", "launches", "a", "new", "satellite", "into", "orbit", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "New York City's mayor announces a plan to improve public transportation.", "tokens": ["New", "York", "City", "'", "s", "mayor", "announces", "a", "plan", "to", "improve", "public", "transportation", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The World Health Organization warns of a new strain of flu virus.", "tokens": ["The", "World", "Health", "Organization", "warns", "of", "a", "new", "strain", "of", "flu", "virus", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tesla announces opening of new electric vehicle factory in Canberra.", "tokens": ["Tesla", "announces", "opening", "of", "new", "electric", "vehicle", "factory", "in", "Canberra", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Canberra experiences record-breaking heatwave as temperatures soar above 40 degrees.", "tokens": ["Canberra", "experiences", "record", "-", "breaking", "heatwave", "as", "temperatures", "soar", "above", "40", "degrees", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Investigation reveals that Tesla CEO Elon Musk is under scrutiny for alleged stock manipulation.", "tokens": ["Investigation", "reveals", "that", "Tesla", "CEO", "Elon", "Musk", "is", "under", "scrutiny", "for", "alleged", "stock", "manipulation", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Jennifer Lawrence to star in new Hollywood blockbuster.", "tokens": ["Jennifer", "Lawrence", "to", "star", "in", "new", "Hollywood", "blockbuster", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Wikimedia Foundation announces partnership with major tech company.", "tokens": ["Wikimedia", "Foundation", "announces", "partnership", "with", "major", "tech", "company", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Auckland named top travel destination for 2021.", "tokens": ["Auckland", "named", "top", "travel", "destination", "for", "2021", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Jeffree Star announces new makeup line.", "tokens": ["Jeffree", "Star", "announces", "new", "makeup", "line", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Sergey Brin steps down as president of Alphabet.", "tokens": ["Sergey", "Brin", "steps", "down", "as", "president", "of", "Alphabet", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O"]}
{"sentence": "New York City imposes vaccine mandate for indoor activities.", "tokens": ["New", "York", "City", "imposes", "vaccine", "mandate", "for", "indoor", "activities", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The International Red Cross and Red Crescent Movement distributes aid to victims of natural disasters around the world.", "tokens": ["The", "International", "Red", "Cross", "and", "Red", "Crescent", "Movement", "distributes", "aid", "to", "victims", "of", "natural", "disasters", "around", "the", "world", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
