[
  {
    "sentence": "Protesters gather in downtown Portland to support the Black Lives Matter movement.",
    "span": "Portland",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.01350778600875
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Protesters gather in downtown Portland to support the Black Lives Matter movement.",
    "span": "Black Lives Matter",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0004290717524166666
  },
  {
    "sentence": "New York City mayor announces police reform plan in response to Black Lives Matter demonstrations.",
    "span": "New York City",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -1.3127210116666667e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "New York City mayor announces police reform plan in response to Black Lives Matter demonstrations.",
    "span": "Black Lives Matter",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -9.717282315000001e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Chicago police chief meets with leaders of Black Lives Matter to discuss community policing initiatives.",
    "span": "Chicago",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -6.034591975e-06
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Chicago police chief meets with leaders of Black Lives Matter to discuss community policing initiatives.",
    "span": "Black Lives Matter",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -9.706248336666667e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Steven Spielberg to direct new film about the United Nations Development Programme.",
    "span": "Steven Spielberg",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0004355180972
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX successfully launches 60 Starlink satellites into orbit.",
    "span": "SpaceX",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.026157367138624998
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Paris Climate Agreement participants pledge to reduce carbon emissions by 20% by 2030.",
    "span": "Paris",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.01162959497925
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Apple Inc. announces record-breaking quarterly earnings, surpassing analyst expectations.",
    "span": "Apple Inc.",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0002850186139416667
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Russia and Saudi Arabia agree to cooperate on oil production cuts to stabilize the market.",
    "span": "Russia",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.000187790843
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Russia and Saudi Arabia agree to cooperate on oil production cuts to stabilize the market.",
    "span": "Saudi Arabia",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0007247285123999999
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Oil prices surge as tensions rise between the United States and Iran.",
    "span": "United States",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.000247249298
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Oil prices surge as tensions rise between the United States and Iran.",
    "span": "Iran",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00013845518775
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Pop star Britney Spears announces new Las Vegas residency.",
    "span": "Britney Spears",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0278285198394
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Pop star Britney Spears announces new Las Vegas residency.",
    "span": "Las Vegas",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.005206577235000001
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Britney Spears' new album tops charts in over 20 countries.",
    "span": "Britney Spears",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -5.539805221666667e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Britney Spears' former manager files lawsuit against her estate.",
    "span": "Britney Spears",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0005251179037666666
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Sydney Opera House to host annual music festival.",
    "span": "Sydney",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0029708457666000002
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Sydney Opera House to host annual music festival.",
    "span": "Opera House",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.037728419453600004
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Australian Prime Minister to visit Sydney for climate change summit.",
    "span": "Australian",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.11947332279875
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Australian Prime Minister to visit Sydney for climate change summit.",
    "span": "Prime Minister",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0211895465932
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Australian Prime Minister to visit Sydney for climate change summit.",
    "span": "Sydney",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00177267069275
  },
  {
    "sentence": "New South Wales government announces major infrastructure plan for Sydney.",
    "span": "New South Wales government",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.37629862485764287
  },
  {
    "sentence": "New South Wales government announces major infrastructure plan for Sydney.",
    "span": "Sydney",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -4.3732750349999996e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Supreme Court Justice Ruth Bader Ginsburg hospitalized for treatment of possible infection.",
    "span": "Supreme Court",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.10294193791778111
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Supreme Court Justice Ruth Bader Ginsburg hospitalized for treatment of possible infection.",
    "span": "Ruth Bader Ginsburg",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0008518805698000001
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Ruth Bader Ginsburg, United States Supreme Court Justice, to undergo non-surgical procedure for benign gallbladder condition.",
    "span": "Ruth Bader Ginsburg",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -1.31073431e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Ruth Bader Ginsburg, United States Supreme Court Justice, to undergo non-surgical procedure for benign gallbladder condition.",
    "span": "United States Supreme Court",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.017209187458000003
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Ruth Bader Ginsburg to return to work after treatment for cancer.",
    "span": "Ruth Bader Ginsburg",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -9.864688259999999e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Billie Eilish's new album tops the charts.",
    "span": "Billie Eilish",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0004767178659625
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Billie Eilish announces world tour dates for next year.",
    "span": "Billie Eilish",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -2.615020965e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Angelina Jolie donates $1 million to refugee charity.",
    "span": "Angelina Jolie",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.007113599468742857
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Critics praise Angelina Jolie's performance in new film.",
    "span": "Angelina Jolie",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -2.5753237300000002e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Angelina Jolie partners with UNICEF for new global initiative.",
    "span": "Angelina Jolie",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.00036354011987714286
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Angelina Jolie partners with UNICEF for new global initiative.",
    "span": "UNICEF",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -9.14094805e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Miami Heat signs top free agent from Oslo.",
    "span": "Miami",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.06131279673000001
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Miami Heat signs top free agent from Oslo.",
    "span": "Heat",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.22706658853725
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Miami Heat signs top free agent from Oslo.",
    "span": "Oslo",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.20907234508425004
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Oslo to host international peace summit.",
    "span": "Oslo",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00013264283376
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Miami police department announces new chief of police.",
    "span": "Miami",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0030840236795
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Oxfam International reports a rise in global hunger due to the COVID-19 pandemic.",
    "span": "Oxfam International",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0005289726705714285
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The United Nations calls for urgent action to address the climate crisis.",
    "span": "United Nations",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0010347018094799998
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Professor Johnson's research reveals promising results in the fight against cancer.",
    "span": "Professor Johnson",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0401983770762
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Microsoft acquires cybersecurity firm for $10 billion.",
    "span": "Microsoft",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.6341665903715
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Microsoft acquires cybersecurity firm for $10 billion.",
    "span": "cybersecurity firm",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0102493220852
  },
  {
    "sentence": "President Biden meets with German Chancellor Angela Merkel in Washington.",
    "span": "President Biden",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.007423610237799999
  },
  {
    "sentence": "President Biden meets with German Chancellor Angela Merkel in Washington.",
    "span": "Angela Merkel",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.11191133949710001
  },
  {
    "sentence": "President Biden meets with German Chancellor Angela Merkel in Washington.",
    "span": "Washington",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0036092460385
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tropical storm damages thousands of homes in Philippines.",
    "span": "Philippines",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.029306466006100002
  },
  {
    "sentence": "International Red Cross deploys relief teams to flood-affected areas in Southeast Asia.",
    "span": "International Red Cross",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.46834861359301666
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Renowned scientist from Zurich wins prestigious award for contribution to environmental sustainability.",
    "span": "Zurich",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.008757917747805
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tesla stocks soar after successful launch of new electric vehicle.",
    "span": "Tesla",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00641925166625
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Australian Prime Minister meets with Chinese President to discuss trade agreements.",
    "span": "Australian Prime Minister",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.00023087318333333336
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Australian Prime Minister meets with Chinese President to discuss trade agreements.",
    "span": "Chinese President",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.00017861362692
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Flooding in Midwest causes thousands to evacuate their homes.",
    "span": "Midwest",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -1.60238593e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The new Starbucks Corporation branch in Jakarta is expected to attract a large number of coffee lovers.",
    "span": "Starbucks Corporation",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00024059954259999998
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The new Starbucks Corporation branch in Jakarta is expected to attract a large number of coffee lovers.",
    "span": "Jakarta",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0001262355421
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Jakarta experiences heavy flooding after a week of relentless rain.",
    "span": "Jakarta",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -4.1268261128e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "APPLE ANNOUNCES LAUNCH OF NEW IPHONE MODEL.",
    "span": "APPLE",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.013848172706
  },
  {
    "sentence": "APPLE ANNOUNCES LAUNCH OF NEW IPHONE MODEL.",
    "span": "IPHONE",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.11123436711191999
  },
  {
    "sentence": "TOM CRUISE TO STAR IN UPCOMING ACTION THRILLER FILM.",
    "span": "TOM CRUISE",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.00028117871289125003
  },
  {
    "sentence": "CALIFORNIA GOVERNOR SIGNS BILL TO COMBAT CLIMATE CHANGE.",
    "span": "CALIFORNIA",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.005257792755399999
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Dwayne \"The Rock\" Johnson announces new production company.",
    "span": "Dwayne \"The Rock\" Johnson",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.07769441085852999
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Dwayne \"The Rock\" Johnson announces new production company.",
    "span": "production company",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0012034014632
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Record-breaking heatwave hits Western United States, prompting emergency measures.",
    "span": "Western United States",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.008164573218266668
  },
  {
    "sentence": "New York City Marathon canceled due to extreme weather conditions.",
    "span": "New York City",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.18209894573111665
  },
  {
    "sentence": "New York City Marathon canceled due to extreme weather conditions.",
    "span": "Marathon",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0155652646
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Coca-Cola plans to launch a new line of flavored sparkling water.",
    "span": "Coca-Cola",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0002961687523333333
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Investors speculate on potential merger between PepsiCo and Coca-Cola.",
    "span": "PepsiCo",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -7.5371826e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Investors speculate on potential merger between PepsiCo and Coca-Cola.",
    "span": "Coca-Cola",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0001094351522
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Coca-Cola CEO announced significant expansion in Asian markets.",
    "span": "Coca-Cola",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.004281747905283333
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Queen Elizabeth II celebrates her 95th birthday.",
    "span": "Queen Elizabeth II",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.00111494217
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Walmart announces plans to open 100 new stores nationwide.",
    "span": "Walmart",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00124821285481
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The new documentary features interviews with Walmart employees.",
    "span": "Walmart",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -1.1231871748e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Aung San Suu Kyi calls for release of political prisoners in Myanmar.",
    "span": "Aung San Suu Kyi",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -2.9624997370000004e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Aung San Suu Kyi calls for release of political prisoners in Myanmar.",
    "span": "Myanmar",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00194151736525
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Mumbai police arrest suspects in connection with terrorist plot.",
    "span": "Mumbai",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00047886255892
  },
  {
    "sentence": "New organization in Mumbai aims to provide support for homeless youth.",
    "span": "Mumbai",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00010776190599999999
  },
  {
    "sentence": "UN reports record number of refugees in Vienna.",
    "span": "UN",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0023782052959999997
  },
  {
    "sentence": "UN reports record number of refugees in Vienna.",
    "span": "Vienna",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00098112264325
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Vienna Philharmonic Orchestra cancels upcoming tour due to COVID-19.",
    "span": "Vienna Philharmonic Orchestra",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.007235072568511112
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Vienna Philharmonic Orchestra cancels upcoming tour due to COVID-19.",
    "span": "COVID-19",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.04557449446123333
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Vienna Mayor announces new public transportation initiatives.",
    "span": "Vienna Mayor",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.137999064741605
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Vienna Mayor announces new public transportation initiatives.",
    "span": "public transportation",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.066864168397
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Los Angeles Lakers clinch victory in NBA finals.",
    "span": "Los Angeles",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0010362997654
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Los Angeles Lakers clinch victory in NBA finals.",
    "span": "Lakers",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0019000465486749998
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Elon Omar to lead climate change initiative.",
    "span": "Elon Omar",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0010433771593000001
  },
  {
    "sentence": "United Nations condemns new wave of violence in Middle East.",
    "span": "United Nations",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.000181605467
  },
  {
    "sentence": "United Nations condemns new wave of violence in Middle East.",
    "span": "Middle East",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0001880285413
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Beijing announces new environmental regulations to reduce air pollution.",
    "span": "Beijing",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00420659185908
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Thousands gather in Beijing to celebrate Chinese New Year.",
    "span": "Beijing",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0352953752866
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Beijing Olympics committee selects renowned architect to design main stadium.",
    "span": "Beijing",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.019580274602400003
  },
  {
    "sentence": "National Public Radio reports record-breaking viewership for its latest investigative documentary.",
    "span": "National Public Radio",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00024123720016666668
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Award-winning journalist John Smith announced as the new host of the National Public Radio morning show.",
    "span": "John Smith",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.004653287418399999
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Award-winning journalist John Smith announced as the new host of the National Public Radio morning show.",
    "span": "National Public Radio",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -7.45476678e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "National Public Radio investigates claims of corruption within the local government.",
    "span": "National Public Radio",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0005183569182000001
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The Coca-Cola Company announces new sustainability initiatives in Sydney.",
    "span": "Coca-Cola Company",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.01835204531995
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The Coca-Cola Company announces new sustainability initiatives in Sydney.",
    "span": "Sydney",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00027829990725
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Sydney to host international film festival featuring global directors.",
    "span": "Sydney",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -4.81589677e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Coca-Cola Company reports record sales for the third quarter.",
    "span": "Coca-Cola Company",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -1.8772355564285713e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Martin Scorsese to premiere new film at London Film Festival.",
    "span": "Martin Scorsese",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -7.07372935e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Martin Scorsese to premiere new film at London Film Festival.",
    "span": "London",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.000970804981925
  },
  {
    "sentence": "London mayor announces new initiative to combat air pollution in the city.",
    "span": "London",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.000383992795625
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Martin Scorsese's latest project to be filmed in London.",
    "span": "Martin Scorsese",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -1.0819767557142856e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Martin Scorsese's latest project to be filmed in London.",
    "span": "London",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00017565821055
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The government announced a new transportation infrastructure plan for Jakarta.",
    "span": "government",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.47369997532988
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The government announced a new transportation infrastructure plan for Jakarta.",
    "span": "Jakarta",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.008463964974575
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Local residents in Jakarta protest against the construction of a new shopping mall.",
    "span": "Jakarta",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -5.1638243200000004e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Jakarta Mayor plans to implement a new waste management system in the city.",
    "span": "Jakarta",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00195328139018
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Jakarta Mayor plans to implement a new waste management system in the city.",
    "span": "Mayor",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -6.164034875e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Nancy Pelosi announces plans to address climate change with support from the International Energy Agency.",
    "span": "Nancy Pelosi",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.00017318381555
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Nancy Pelosi announces plans to address climate change with support from the International Energy Agency.",
    "span": "International Energy Agency",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00021051995550000003
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The International Energy Agency predicts a global oil demand surge in the coming months.",
    "span": "International Energy Agency",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -9.4196396e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Nancy Pelosi calls for bipartisan cooperation in Congress to pass new infrastructure legislation.",
    "span": "Nancy Pelosi",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -6.805106658333333e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Greenpeace activists protest outside the Hanoi government building.",
    "span": "Greenpeace",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.10427481031226
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Greenpeace activists protest outside the Hanoi government building.",
    "span": "Hanoi",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00039948383715999997
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The mayor of Hanoi meets with foreign investors to discuss infrastructure projects.",
    "span": "Hanoi",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -4.2819375866e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Greenpeace warns of environmental damage in Hanoi due to excessive air pollution.",
    "span": "Greenpeace",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -4.200805784000001e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Greenpeace warns of environmental damage in Hanoi due to excessive air pollution.",
    "span": "Hanoi",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -9.32461314e-06
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The United States Department of Justice announces new initiatives to combat cybercrime.",
    "span": "United States Department of Justice",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.004968788768562499
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Thousands of migrants are stranded at the border between Mexico and the United States.",
    "span": "Mexico",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0052722089032499996
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Thousands of migrants are stranded at the border between Mexico and the United States.",
    "span": "United States",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0024625032492
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Real Madrid defeats Barcelona in a dramatic overtime victory.",
    "span": "Real Madrid",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0050232980236
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Real Madrid defeats Barcelona in a dramatic overtime victory.",
    "span": "Barcelona",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.054705410586750006
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Protests erupt in Madrid over government decision to raise taxes.",
    "span": "Madrid",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -9.54784186e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Renowned chef from Madrid opens new restaurant in London.",
    "span": "Madrid",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -4.844432077e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Renowned chef from Madrid opens new restaurant in London.",
    "span": "London",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -9.4983903075e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Rosalía wins big at the Latin Grammy Awards.",
    "span": "Rosalía",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.016427242072883336
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Volodymyr Zelensky calls for peace talks in Ukraine.",
    "span": "Volodymyr Zelensky",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.00013259655518181818
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Volodymyr Zelensky calls for peace talks in Ukraine.",
    "span": "Ukraine",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.000150881247575
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Elon Musk announces SpaceX's plan to send humans to Mars by 2026.",
    "span": "Elon Musk",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -3.474158666666667e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Elon Musk announces SpaceX's plan to send humans to Mars by 2026.",
    "span": "SpaceX",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0007789179415000001
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Elon Musk announces SpaceX's plan to send humans to Mars by 2026.",
    "span": "Mars",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00164870194125
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Apple's new iPhone 13 to be released next month.",
    "span": "Apple",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.19829664409075
  },
  {
    "sentence": "President Biden signs $1.2 trillion infrastructure bill into law.",
    "span": "President Biden",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.00172871750792
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The Indian government announces new policies to address air pollution in Delhi.",
    "span": "Indian government",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0663479423094
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The Indian government announces new policies to address air pollution in Delhi.",
    "span": "Delhi",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00026876059405999997
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Protesters gather in Delhi to demand change in government policies.",
    "span": "Delhi",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0001854834338
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Delhi schools to remain closed due to severe air pollution levels.",
    "span": "Delhi",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0003728555418
  },
  {
    "sentence": "United Nations Development Programme allocates $10 million for education projects in Africa.",
    "span": "Africa",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0008862709055
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Renowned economist Joseph Stiglitz joins United Nations Development Programme as senior advisor.",
    "span": "Joseph Stiglitz",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -2.36916349375e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Renowned economist Joseph Stiglitz joins United Nations Development Programme as senior advisor.",
    "span": "United Nations Development Programme",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -9.546485888571428e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "United Nations Development Programme launches initiative to combat climate change in vulnerable island nations.",
    "span": "United Nations Development Programme",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.005219559655
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX successfully launches 60 more Starlink satellites.",
    "span": "Elon Musk",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -3.8716263766666664e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX successfully launches 60 more Starlink satellites.",
    "span": "SpaceX",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.1428529436085
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX successfully launches 60 more Starlink satellites.",
    "span": "Starlink",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0052123329740000005
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The United Nations reports a record number of refugees fleeing conflict in the Middle East.",
    "span": "United Nations",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00360264499688
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The United Nations reports a record number of refugees fleeing conflict in the Middle East.",
    "span": "Middle East",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0001307271348
  },
  {
    "sentence": "President Biden signs executive order to address climate change.",
    "span": "President Biden",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0020337160333
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Kourtney Kardashian launches her new lifestyle brand Poosh.",
    "span": "Kourtney Kardashian",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.11199456449224286
  },
  {
    "sentence": "New York City mayor announces plan to expand affordable housing options.",
    "span": "New York City",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00011159402171666666
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tesla's stock reaches record high after strong quarterly earnings report.",
    "span": "Tesla",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00048610823592500004
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX successfully launches satellite into orbit.",
    "span": "Elon Musk",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0755996771026
  },
  {
    "sentence": "New York City announces plan to invest $100 million in affordable housing.",
    "span": "New York City",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -6.197778743333333e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Apple Inc. reports record-breaking sales for latest iPhone model.",
    "span": "Apple Inc.",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.007558948488908333
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The United Nations calls for a cease-fire in the ongoing conflict in Syria.",
    "span": "United Nations",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -2.312839756e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The United Nations calls for a cease-fire in the ongoing conflict in Syria.",
    "span": "Syria",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00058122959205
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Edinburgh's population reaches over 500,000 for the first time.",
    "span": "Edinburgh",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0033195186459999996
  },
  {
    "sentence": "David Beckham invests in new esports organization.",
    "span": "David Beckham",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0087092088662
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Record number of visitors flock to Edinburgh Festival.",
    "span": "Edinburgh",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0004135021830600001
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The World Trade Organization released a report on global trade tensions.",
    "span": "World Trade Organization",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -1.3048905118463334
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The International Energy Agency predicts a decrease in oil demand for the next quarter.",
    "span": "International Energy Agency",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0019902646169333332
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The United States, China, and the European Union are in talks to address trade imbalances.",
    "span": "United States",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0002185233782
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The United States, China, and the European Union are in talks to address trade imbalances.",
    "span": "China",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -1.6375510375e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The United States, China, and the European Union are in talks to address trade imbalances.",
    "span": "European Union",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -7.44061474e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tesla unveils new electric car with longer battery life.",
    "span": "Tesla",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0038271733352499998
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Angela Merkel elected as Chancellor of Germany for the fourth term.",
    "span": "Angela Merkel",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -1.7299338816666666e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Angela Merkel elected as Chancellor of Germany for the fourth term.",
    "span": "Germany",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00024721342925
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Amazon announces plans to open new headquarters in New York City.",
    "span": "Amazon",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -9.998114025e-06
  },
  {
    "sentence": "George W. Bush delivers keynote speech at Nairobi economic summit.",
    "span": "George W. Bush",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0208292630512
  },
  {
    "sentence": "George W. Bush delivers keynote speech at Nairobi economic summit.",
    "span": "Nairobi",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00024740870347142853
  },
  {
    "sentence": "New business startup in Nairobi sees rapid growth in its first year.",
    "span": "Nairobi",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -3.702607674e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "George W. Bush Foundation for Military Service members announces new scholarship program.",
    "span": "George W. Bush",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.5576513990966286
  },
  {
    "sentence": "George W. Bush Foundation for Military Service members announces new scholarship program.",
    "span": "Military Service",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.46678233793499996
  },
  {
    "sentence": "David Beckham announces his retirement from professional soccer.",
    "span": "David Beckham",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0004740040836
  },
  {
    "sentence": "IBM Corporation reports a 15% increase in quarterly profits.",
    "span": "IBM Corporation",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -4.99462873e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The Democratic National Committee reveals its latest campaign strategy for the upcoming election.",
    "span": "Democratic National Committee",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -2.3040981833333338e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The peace talks in Reykjavik have reached a deadlock.",
    "span": "Reykjavik",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.000563991664057143
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Sony announces the release of their new gaming console next month.",
    "span": "Sony",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -3.39878505e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Taliban insurgents have launched a series of attacks in the region.",
    "span": "Taliban",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -1.7704150248333335e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The Federal Trade Commission investigates allegations of antitrust violations in the tech industry.",
    "span": "Federal Trade Commission",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00202000238145
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Vienna to host international summit on climate change next month.",
    "span": "Vienna",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -3.12580881e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Amal Clooney speaks at United Nations conference on human rights.",
    "span": "Amal Clooney",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0006721121566857143
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Amal Clooney speaks at United Nations conference on human rights.",
    "span": "United Nations",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -4.255639214e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The embassy in Moscow remains closed amid escalating tensions.",
    "span": "Moscow",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0104172071685
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Brasília mayor announces plan to improve public transportation system.",
    "span": "Brasília",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.009079245230350001
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Prominent artist from Moscow to showcase new exhibition in New York.",
    "span": "Moscow",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0009490115571
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tesla announces new electric car model.",
    "span": "Tesla",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.02556895789
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tokyo Olympics officially begin with opening ceremony.",
    "span": "Tokyo",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.2935338242542
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Dr. Johnson appointed as new CEO of pharmaceutical company.",
    "span": "Dr. Johnson",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.009859677551083334
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tom Hanks to star in new sci-fi thriller directed by Christopher Nolan.",
    "span": "Tom Hanks",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -4.3067198e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Local charity organization to host fundraising event with special appearance by Tom Hanks.",
    "span": "Tom Hanks",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.00014641616894166666
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tom Hanks donates $1 million to children's hospital for new research wing.",
    "span": "Tom Hanks",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0030555954254900004
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Brad Pitt signs deal with major film production company.",
    "span": "Brad Pitt",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.09884505183
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Brad Pitt to attend premiere of new movie in New York City.",
    "span": "Brad Pitt",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -3.0423662599999997e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Brad Pitt to attend premiere of new movie in New York City.",
    "span": "New York City",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -8.974857366666668e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Environmental organization led by Brad Pitt launches new conservation initiative.",
    "span": "Brad Pitt",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0813418070436
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Technology company Apple Inc. introduces new line of iPhones.",
    "span": "Apple Inc.",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0037917664909333337
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Jennifer Lopez and Ben Affleck spotted together in Los Angeles.",
    "span": "Jennifer Lopez",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.00027005828032
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Jennifer Lopez and Ben Affleck spotted together in Los Angeles.",
    "span": "Ben Affleck",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -7.860547466666666e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Jennifer Lopez and Ben Affleck spotted together in Los Angeles.",
    "span": "Los Angeles",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.000218013916
  },
  {
    "sentence": "United Nations reports humanitarian crisis in war-torn region.",
    "span": "United Nations",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -9.794612431999999e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX successfully launches new satellite into orbit.",
    "span": "Elon Musk",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -9.34234105e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tropical storm warning issued for Florida coast.",
    "span": "Florida",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.000101153612
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Hollywood actress Angelina Jolie donates $1 million to refugee charity.",
    "span": "Angelina Jolie",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0011650873355571428
  },
  {
    "sentence": "NATO strengthens its military presence in Eastern Europe.",
    "span": "NATO",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00367902268403
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Bank of America announces plans to close several branches in the Midwest.",
    "span": "Bank of America",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -1.2014642716666667e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Bank of America announces plans to close several branches in the Midwest.",
    "span": "Midwest",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.000621009205
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Malala Yousafzai receives the Nobel Peace Prize.",
    "span": "Malala Yousafzai",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.00110536236927
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The United Nations Security Council condemns the recent missile tests by North Korea.",
    "span": "United Nations Security Council",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -8.703727875714286e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The United Nations Security Council condemns the recent missile tests by North Korea.",
    "span": "North Korea",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0006396484339999999
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Famous chef Jamie Oliver opens new restaurant in New York City.",
    "span": "Jamie Oliver",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -1.776423244e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Famous chef Jamie Oliver opens new restaurant in New York City.",
    "span": "New York City",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -3.6928208499999996e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Renowned chef Gordon Ramsay to open new restaurant in Los Angeles.",
    "span": "Gordon Ramsay",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -1.514515762857143e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Renowned chef Gordon Ramsay to open new restaurant in Los Angeles.",
    "span": "Los Angeles",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -8.266934894e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Stocks surge as Apple Inc. announces record-breaking quarterly earnings.",
    "span": "Apple Inc.",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -5.540232988333334e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tesla unveils new electric car model.",
    "span": "Tesla",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.01577366332025
  },
  {
    "sentence": "President Biden to visit European Union headquarters in Brussels next week.",
    "span": "President Biden",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0035492132881999997
  },
  {
    "sentence": "President Biden to visit European Union headquarters in Brussels next week.",
    "span": "European Union",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00912039915492
  },
  {
    "sentence": "President Biden to visit European Union headquarters in Brussels next week.",
    "span": "Brussels",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0002980858725
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Wildfires in California continue to threaten homes and natural habitats.",
    "span": "California",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -7.052010725e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tech giants Apple and Google to release new smartphones next week.",
    "span": "Apple",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00020729164
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tech giants Apple and Google to release new smartphones next week.",
    "span": "Google",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0126531696465
  },
  {
    "sentence": "President Biden announces new infrastructure plan.",
    "span": "President Biden",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0498994567534
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Shakira's charity organization donates $1 million to the earthquake relief efforts in Haiti.",
    "span": "Shakira",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.21414885427061667
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Shakira's charity organization donates $1 million to the earthquake relief efforts in Haiti.",
    "span": "Haiti",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0017073915045
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Justin Trudeau announces new measures to combat climate change at the United Nations summit in New York.",
    "span": "Justin Trudeau",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.00020010551190000002
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Justin Trudeau announces new measures to combat climate change at the United Nations summit in New York.",
    "span": "United Nations",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.000129045072568
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Justin Trudeau announces new measures to combat climate change at the United Nations summit in New York.",
    "span": "New York",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -9.157728379999999e-06
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Hip-hop mogul Jay-Z launches new streaming service.",
    "span": "Jay-Z",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.2794070738469
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Hip-hop mogul Jay-Z launches new streaming service.",
    "span": "streaming service",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00127866356812
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Beyoncé and Jay-Z plan to buy a luxury villa in Italy.",
    "span": "Beyoncé",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -2.0537704521666666e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Beyoncé and Jay-Z plan to buy a luxury villa in Italy.",
    "span": "Jay-Z",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -6.847053559999999e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Beyoncé and Jay-Z plan to buy a luxury villa in Italy.",
    "span": "Italy",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00041826385225
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Jay-Z's music label signs new up-and-coming artist.",
    "span": "Jay-Z",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.9040876417526
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Singapore reports record number of new COVID-19 cases.",
    "span": "Singapore",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00202540715
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Meghan Markle launches new charitable foundation.",
    "span": "Meghan Markle",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.00037875842714285714
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Singapore Airlines announces partnership with international hotel chain.",
    "span": "Singapore Airlines",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.030663799505599998
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Charlize Theron wins Best Actress award at the Oscars.",
    "span": "Charlize Theron",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0018099930716125
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Panama City announces new plans for public transportation system.",
    "span": "Panama City",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0016059066358166667
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Beirut explosion leaves hundreds dead and injured.",
    "span": "Beirut",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0015994749942000001
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Rome mayor announces new COVID-19 restrictions for city residents.",
    "span": "Rome",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00183856942292
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Celebrity chef opens new restaurant in Beirut.",
    "span": "Beirut",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.17147174849732
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Academy Award-winner George Clooney to direct and star in new political thriller.",
    "span": "George Clooney",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.004898381658
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Ocean conservation organization, founded by George Clooney, raises $1 million in charity auction.",
    "span": "George Clooney",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.006772024948166667
  },
  {
    "sentence": "George Clooney's new film tops box office in opening weekend.",
    "span": "George Clooney",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -2.8166739233333334e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "NATO to increase presence in Eastern Europe to deter Russian aggression.",
    "span": "NATO",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00041863782953
  },
  {
    "sentence": "NATO to increase presence in Eastern Europe to deter Russian aggression.",
    "span": "Eastern Europe",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.000502803379
  },
  {
    "sentence": "NATO to increase presence in Eastern Europe to deter Russian aggression.",
    "span": "Russian",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.81318671279375
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Cybersecurity concerns prompt NATO to hold emergency meeting.",
    "span": "NATO",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00011841431432
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Member nations of NATO commit to increase defense spending.",
    "span": "NATO",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -2.325656118e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tesla CEO Elon Musk announces plans to build new gigafactory in Texas.",
    "span": "Tesla",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0155017208825
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tesla CEO Elon Musk announces plans to build new gigafactory in Texas.",
    "span": "Elon Musk",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.000118061823
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tesla CEO Elon Musk announces plans to build new gigafactory in Texas.",
    "span": "Texas",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0025793281135
  },
  {
    "sentence": "China inaugurates the world's longest sea bridge connecting Hong Kong, Macau, and Zhuhai.",
    "span": "China",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00032224207125
  },
  {
    "sentence": "China inaugurates the world's longest sea bridge connecting Hong Kong, Macau, and Zhuhai.",
    "span": "Hong Kong",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -2.560783386e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "China inaugurates the world's longest sea bridge connecting Hong Kong, Macau, and Zhuhai.",
    "span": "Macau",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -5.96762416e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "China inaugurates the world's longest sea bridge connecting Hong Kong, Macau, and Zhuhai.",
    "span": "Zhuhai",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00013317325605000002
  },
  {
    "sentence": "UNICEF launches vaccination campaign in war-torn Syrian city.",
    "span": "UNICEF",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -8.478267016666667e-06
  },
  {
    "sentence": "UNICEF launches vaccination campaign in war-torn Syrian city.",
    "span": "Syrian",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.29986582300000003
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Michelle Obama to release new memoir next year.",
    "span": "Michelle Obama",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0014483564718
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Robert Downey Jr. to star in new superhero movie.",
    "span": "Robert Downey Jr.",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -3.4060978400000004e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Zlatan Ibrahimovic signs new contract with LA Galaxy.",
    "span": "Zlatan Ibrahimovic",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0012869975384499999
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Zlatan Ibrahimovic signs new contract with LA Galaxy.",
    "span": "LA Galaxy",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -1.8908588e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The Federal Aviation Administration issued an emergency order to fix Boeing 737 MAX planes.",
    "span": "Federal Aviation Administration",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0002916090168333333
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The Federal Aviation Administration issued an emergency order to fix Boeing 737 MAX planes.",
    "span": "Boeing",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.01112603467
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Condoleezza Rice met with world leaders in Singapore to discuss international security.",
    "span": "Condoleezza Rice",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0001566702328125
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Condoleezza Rice met with world leaders in Singapore to discuss international security.",
    "span": "Singapore",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0008970453195
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Singapore announced a new initiative to promote renewable energy.",
    "span": "Singapore",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00049021709375
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Ford Motor Company announces plans to invest $22 billion in electric vehicles.",
    "span": "Ford Motor Company",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0007961900423333334
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The CEO of Ford Motor Company predicts a surge in demand for electric cars in the next decade.",
    "span": "CEO",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.5351184399052666
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The CEO of Ford Motor Company predicts a surge in demand for electric cars in the next decade.",
    "span": "Ford Motor Company",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.1041119167165
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Ford Motor Company to open a new manufacturing plant in Mexico.",
    "span": "Ford Motor Company",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -7.047823366666667e-06
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Ford Motor Company to open a new manufacturing plant in Mexico.",
    "span": "Mexico",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.000185607113125
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The United Nations has issued a warning about the humanitarian crisis in Yemen.",
    "span": "United Nations",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0009744843242000001
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The United Nations has issued a warning about the humanitarian crisis in Yemen.",
    "span": "Yemen",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00187658907075
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tesla announces plans to build a new Gigafactory in Germany.",
    "span": "Tesla",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -1.527287565e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tesla announces plans to build a new Gigafactory in Germany.",
    "span": "Germany",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0005385816225
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Jennifer Lopez and Alex Rodriguez call off their engagement.",
    "span": "Jennifer Lopez",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -5.18781202e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Jennifer Lopez and Alex Rodriguez call off their engagement.",
    "span": "Alex Rodriguez",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -5.3333139e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Ariana Grande's new single breaks record on Twitter.",
    "span": "Ariana Grande",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.03296273724411429
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Ariana Grande's new single breaks record on Twitter.",
    "span": "Twitter",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00033984295199999997
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Twitter announces new policy on hate speech.",
    "span": "Twitter",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0001837970687
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Ariana Grande surprises fans with impromptu performance in New York City.",
    "span": "Ariana Grande",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -2.2757163185714283e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Ariana Grande surprises fans with impromptu performance in New York City.",
    "span": "New York City",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -3.865543883333333e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Marco Rubio visits Riyadh for diplomatic talks.",
    "span": "Marco Rubio",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0002464280586
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Marco Rubio visits Riyadh for diplomatic talks.",
    "span": "Riyadh",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00047177623774999995
  },
  {
    "sentence": "San Francisco's Bay Area Rapid Transit system faces criticism for delays.",
    "span": "San Francisco",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0582210422264
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Breaking news: Riyadh-based organization announces partnership with major tech company.",
    "span": "Riyadh",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0007621755
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Quentin Tarantino announces his upcoming film project at a press conference in Los Angeles.",
    "span": "Quentin Tarantino",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -3.7315992142857146e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Quentin Tarantino announces his upcoming film project at a press conference in Los Angeles.",
    "span": "Los Angeles",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0013331289231999998
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Planned Parenthood to open a new health clinic in downtown Portland next month.",
    "span": "Planned Parenthood",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -6.789549016666666e-06
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Planned Parenthood to open a new health clinic in downtown Portland next month.",
    "span": "Portland",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00064686867975
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Actress Emma Stone praises Quentin Tarantino's latest movie at the premiere in New York City.",
    "span": "Emma Stone",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -7.151628454000001e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Actress Emma Stone praises Quentin Tarantino's latest movie at the premiere in New York City.",
    "span": "Quentin Tarantino",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -7.325965000000001e-06
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Actress Emma Stone praises Quentin Tarantino's latest movie at the premiere in New York City.",
    "span": "New York City",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -6.585007374999999e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Al Jazeera Media Network reports record viewership for its latest documentary series on wildlife conservation.",
    "span": "Al Jazeera Media Network",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0003669872959142857
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The United Nations condemns the ongoing violence in Myanmar and calls for immediate action to protect civilians.",
    "span": "United Nations",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0012892149812
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The United Nations condemns the ongoing violence in Myanmar and calls for immediate action to protect civilians.",
    "span": "Myanmar",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.000203077801075
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Environmental activist Greta Thunberg meets with European Union leaders to discuss climate change policy.",
    "span": "Greta Thunberg",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -1.1503060425e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Environmental activist Greta Thunberg meets with European Union leaders to discuss climate change policy.",
    "span": "European Union",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -9.06236528e-06
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The OPEC members met in Wellington to discuss oil production cuts.",
    "span": "OPEC",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.11428520728040004
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The OPEC members met in Wellington to discuss oil production cuts.",
    "span": "Wellington",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00029630838280000004
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Rio de Janeiro to host the 2024 Summer Olympics.",
    "span": "Rio de Janeiro",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00017126433061666669
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Iran, Iraq, and Kuwait are key members of OPEC.",
    "span": "Iran",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0011230105075749998
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Iran, Iraq, and Kuwait are key members of OPEC.",
    "span": "Iraq",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -7.621208075000001e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Iran, Iraq, and Kuwait are key members of OPEC.",
    "span": "Kuwait",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.000200179767575
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Iran, Iraq, and Kuwait are key members of OPEC.",
    "span": "OPEC",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -2.184099706e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Xi Jinping calls for increased international cooperation in addressing climate change",
    "span": "Xi Jinping",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0020574536762000004
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Global leaders gather in New York for United Nations General Assembly",
    "span": "New York",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0002600616588
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Government announces new measures to boost economy and tackle inflation, says Xi Jinping",
    "span": "Xi Jinping",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.00319966374492
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Instagram introduces new feature to help users combat cyberbullying.",
    "span": "Instagram",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.000948398826
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The European Space Agency plans to launch a new mission to study exoplanets.",
    "span": "European Space Agency",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0005947133425333334
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Washington D.C. mayor announces new initiative to improve public transportation system.",
    "span": "Washington D.C.",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -8.284183571857143e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Cairo to implement new public transportation system.",
    "span": "Cairo",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0013194991818
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Former New York City Mayor David Dinkins passes away at 93.",
    "span": "New York City",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.02000288340385714
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Former New York City Mayor David Dinkins passes away at 93.",
    "span": "David Dinkins",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0042394100715
  },
  {
    "sentence": "UNESCO and WHO collaborate on global health and education initiative.",
    "span": "UNESCO",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -5.0541570739999996e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "UNESCO and WHO collaborate on global health and education initiative.",
    "span": "WHO",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -8.875184825e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Greenpeace activists protest in Caracas over environmental issues.",
    "span": "Greenpeace",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.25496311951239997
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Greenpeace activists protest in Caracas over environmental issues.",
    "span": "Caracas",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0003388538571
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Caracas mayor announces new public transportation initiative.",
    "span": "Caracas",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -2.770581886e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Greenpeace launches campaign against air pollution in major cities.",
    "span": "Greenpeace",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -1.3615945e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Cairo experiences record-breaking heat wave in July.",
    "span": "Cairo",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0011299190143
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Dallas-based company announces merger with international firm.",
    "span": "Dallas",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00077300185365
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Violent protests erupt in downtown Cairo over economic reforms.",
    "span": "Cairo",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -1.943308356e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "New York Times reveals investigation into government corruption.",
    "span": "New York Times",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.005952925198666667
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Economist John Smith predicts global recession in coming months.",
    "span": "John Smith",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0028412672012
  },
  {
    "sentence": "New York Times investigation uncovers environmental violations by major oil company.",
    "span": "New York Times",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.004406932186266667
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Google LLC announces new headquarters in Brussels.",
    "span": "Google LLC",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -8.291288759999999e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Google LLC announces new headquarters in Brussels.",
    "span": "Brussels",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00063280031325
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Brussels to host international climate summit.",
    "span": "Brussels",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -3.921869084e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Google LLC unveils plans for renewable energy investment.",
    "span": "Google LLC",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -6.48907604e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The American Cancer Society is funding a new research study on potential cancer treatments.",
    "span": "American Cancer Society",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0004982321711666666
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The New York Times reported on the increase in cyber attacks targeting government agencies.",
    "span": "New York Times",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00038945630566666667
  },
  {
    "sentence": "An American Cancer Society fundraiser in Chicago raised over $100,000 for cancer research.",
    "span": "American Cancer Society",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.13436533970863332
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Oxfam International launches emergency appeal for humanitarian aid in war-torn region.",
    "span": "Oxfam International",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0010558811441
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Renowned economist Dr. Angela Li appointed as the new director of Oxfam International's economic research division.",
    "span": "Dr. Angela Li",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.004674634535385713
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Renowned economist Dr. Angela Li appointed as the new director of Oxfam International's economic research division.",
    "span": "Oxfam International",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -8.444099777857142e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The annual report from Oxfam International highlights the growing income inequality in developing countries.",
    "span": "Oxfam International",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -7.9588798e-06
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Israel announces new security measures in response to recent attacks in Tel Aviv.",
    "span": "Israel",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.008017758292500001
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Israel announces new security measures in response to recent attacks in Tel Aviv.",
    "span": "Tel Aviv",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0016769299291199999
  },
  {
    "sentence": "New study shows increasing air pollution levels in Tel Aviv.",
    "span": "Tel Aviv",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -5.743227606e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tel Aviv University receives $10 million donation for new research center.",
    "span": "Tel Aviv University",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.029417693147583333
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Montreal Canadiens defeat Toronto Maple Leafs in overtime thriller.",
    "span": "Montreal",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.307484937589
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Montreal Canadiens defeat Toronto Maple Leafs in overtime thriller.",
    "span": "Canadiens",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.1252965105875
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Montreal Canadiens defeat Toronto Maple Leafs in overtime thriller.",
    "span": "Toronto",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.005164168007175
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Montreal Canadiens defeat Toronto Maple Leafs in overtime thriller.",
    "span": "Maple Leafs",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0008687932314
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Prince William visits wildfire-ravaged communities in Western Canada.",
    "span": "Prince William",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -3.080511209999999e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Prince William visits wildfire-ravaged communities in Western Canada.",
    "span": "Western Canada",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.01601597627664
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Lisbon hosts international climate change conference.",
    "span": "Lisbon",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0029986492037949995
  },
  {
    "sentence": "South Korea reports record high temperatures as heatwave hits Seoul.",
    "span": "South Korea",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0011861862002
  },
  {
    "sentence": "South Korea reports record high temperatures as heatwave hits Seoul.",
    "span": "Seoul",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00106914129425
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Seoul Mayor announces new initiative to reduce air pollution in the city.",
    "span": "Seoul",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.08952830204248
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Major electronics company headquartered in Seoul sees 15% increase in profits.",
    "span": "company",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.068506162101626
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Major electronics company headquartered in Seoul sees 15% increase in profits.",
    "span": "Seoul",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.13292185120725
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Justice Stephen Breyer announces retirement from the Supreme Court.",
    "span": "Stephen Breyer",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0013264613518142855
  },
  {
    "sentence": "New York City declares state of emergency due to rising COVID-19 cases.",
    "span": "New York City",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.06643370891
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX launches another batch of Starlink satellites into orbit.",
    "span": "Elon Musk",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -6.272999466666666e-06
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX launches another batch of Starlink satellites into orbit.",
    "span": "SpaceX",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.050866712824075
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Cairo, Egypt's capital, experiences record high temperatures.",
    "span": "Cairo",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0003034382324
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Cairo, Egypt's capital, experiences record high temperatures.",
    "span": "Egypt",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0020282254071000002
  },
  {
    "sentence": "International Monetary Fund approves $12 billion loan to Egypt to support economic reform efforts.",
    "span": "International Monetary Fund",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -1.7637081766666663e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "International Monetary Fund approves $12 billion loan to Egypt to support economic reform efforts.",
    "span": "Egypt",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.000108234312575
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Cairo University professor wins prestigious award for research in environmental science.",
    "span": "Cairo University",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0025438368730216665
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The United Nations releases report on global poverty and inequality.",
    "span": "United Nations",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.021447720369
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX plans to launch new satellite into orbit next month.",
    "span": "Elon Musk",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -1.6484780166666665e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX plans to launch new satellite into orbit next month.",
    "span": "SpaceX",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00012789099655000002
  },
  {
    "sentence": "New York City to invest $10 million in affordable housing initiative.",
    "span": "New York City",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -3.3550770933333335e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX launches new satellite into orbit.",
    "span": "Elon Musk",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0001337231122
  },
  {
    "sentence": "China's President Xi Jinping visits Russia for trade talks.",
    "span": "China",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00118278150025
  },
  {
    "sentence": "China's President Xi Jinping visits Russia for trade talks.",
    "span": "President Xi Jinping",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.008083177333416666
  },
  {
    "sentence": "China's President Xi Jinping visits Russia for trade talks.",
    "span": "Russia",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.000244392425575
  },
  {
    "sentence": "New York City implements new regulations on food delivery services.",
    "span": "New York City",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -1.741854205e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Queen Elizabeth attends opening ceremony of new hospital.",
    "span": "Queen Elizabeth",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0484418980428
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Annual meeting of World Health Organization attended by representatives from 194 countries",
    "span": "World Health Organization",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0001753945835
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Protests in front of Parliament demand resignation of Prime Minister following corruption scandal.",
    "span": "Parliament",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0003658037394
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Protests in front of Parliament demand resignation of Prime Minister following corruption scandal.",
    "span": "Prime Minister",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0006109915054
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Beauty YouTuber Jeffree Star launches new makeup line.",
    "span": "Jeffree Star",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0016328186115999999
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Angela Davis gives powerful speech at civil rights event.",
    "span": "Angela Davis",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0007789612071666666
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Jeffree Star's cosmetics company experiences rapid growth in sales.",
    "span": "Jeffree Star",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0016245140328833335
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The American Red Cross provides humanitarian aid to flood victims in the Midwest.",
    "span": "American Red Cross",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0007228362091833332
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The American Red Cross provides humanitarian aid to flood victims in the Midwest.",
    "span": "Midwest",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0005500421114999999
  },
  {
    "sentence": "American Red Cross mobilizes volunteers to help with disaster relief efforts in hurricane-affected areas.",
    "span": "American Red Cross",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0010338839297666666
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Shakira to headline concert in Atlanta this weekend.",
    "span": "Shakira",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -9.520779300000001e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Shakira to headline concert in Atlanta this weekend.",
    "span": "Atlanta",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0005956812025000001
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The Democratic National Committee releases statement on healthcare legislation.",
    "span": "Democratic National Committee",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0003680143072333333
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Atlanta Mayor announces new initiative to improve public transportation.",
    "span": "Atlanta",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0006249452852500001
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tesla CEO Elon Musk unveils new electric vehicle model.",
    "span": "Tesla",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0058628474835000005
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tesla CEO Elon Musk unveils new electric vehicle model.",
    "span": "Elon Musk",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0048155259852
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tropical storm hits Southeast Asia, causing widespread flooding.",
    "span": "Southeast Asia",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00010369417833333333
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Amazon to acquire popular streaming service for $8 billion.",
    "span": "Amazon",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.000152497402925
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Jeff Goldblum to make guest appearance at Johannesburg film festival.",
    "span": "Jeff Goldblum",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.00020000647385714286
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Jeff Goldblum to make guest appearance at Johannesburg film festival.",
    "span": "Johannesburg",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00372076949275
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Facebook faces lawsuit over data privacy breach.",
    "span": "Facebook",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.000274341906575
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Johannesburg Mayor renews commitment to solving city's housing crisis.",
    "span": "Johannesburg",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00021982312777857143
  },
  {
    "sentence": "United Parcel Service announces partnership with Amazon for drone delivery.",
    "span": "United Parcel Service",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00010957244566666666
  },
  {
    "sentence": "United Parcel Service announces partnership with Amazon for drone delivery.",
    "span": "Amazon",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.000848545938
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Stockholm, Sweden experienced record high temperatures during the heatwave.",
    "span": "Stockholm",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -8.715360520000002e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Stockholm, Sweden experienced record high temperatures during the heatwave.",
    "span": "Sweden",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00078206322525
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Mitch McConnell introduces new legislation to address infrastructure issues.",
    "span": "Mitch McConnell",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0034240390467999995
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Protesters gather outside Mitch McConnell's office in downtown Louisville.",
    "span": "Mitch McConnell",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.008184309165600001
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Protesters gather outside Mitch McConnell's office in downtown Louisville.",
    "span": "Louisville",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00023137582449999998
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Senate Majority Leader Mitch McConnell delivers speech on immigration reform.",
    "span": "Mitch McConnell",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0349359401586
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Mitch McConnell announces new legislation focused on healthcare reform.",
    "span": "Mitch McConnell",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0050245141826
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The stock market experienced a sharp decline following Mitch McConnell's speech.",
    "span": "Mitch McConnell",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -3.972154691999999e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Mitch McConnell meets with leaders from various organizations to discuss economic stimulus plans.",
    "span": "Mitch McConnell",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.000720174631128
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX successfully launches 60 internet satellites.",
    "span": "Elon Musk",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.00020176823924999998
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX successfully launches 60 internet satellites.",
    "span": "SpaceX",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.017890751137925
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tokyo Olympics to be held without spectators amid COVID-19 concerns.",
    "span": "Tokyo",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.009190516716128
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Apple unveils new line of iPhone models at annual product launch event.",
    "span": "Apple",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.1522543557981625
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Nicole Kidman set to star in new thriller film.",
    "span": "Nicole Kidman",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0008588646051285714
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Microsoft Corporation announces plans to acquire artificial intelligence startup.",
    "span": "Microsoft Corporation",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00270372038966
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Oslo city council introduces new recycling program to reduce waste and promote sustainability.",
    "span": "Oslo",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0033524697588
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Islamabad police arrest suspected kidnapper in ongoing investigation.",
    "span": "Islamabad",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -6.441393956e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Islamabad-based organization provides relief aid to flood-affected regions in the country.",
    "span": "Islamabad",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00494490326568
  },
  {
    "sentence": "LeBron James signs multi-year contract with Los Angeles Lakers.",
    "span": "LeBron James",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.00025313220233333334
  },
  {
    "sentence": "LeBron James signs multi-year contract with Los Angeles Lakers.",
    "span": "Los Angeles Lakers",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00036624401733333334
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Chevron Corporation to invest $10 billion in renewable energy projects over the next decade.",
    "span": "Chevron Corporation",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00064498556925
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The annual summit in Davos gathers global leaders to discuss economic and environmental issues.",
    "span": "Davos",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -2.3684200066666666e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The European Central Bank raises interest rates in response to rising inflation.",
    "span": "European Central Bank",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00041011802573333333
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Renowned economist Maria Yellen appointed as the new chair of the International Monetary Fund.",
    "span": "Maria Yellen",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.00013341716520666667
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Mitt Romney announces bid for Senate.",
    "span": "Mitt Romney",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0013421522676666667
  },
  {
    "sentence": "North Atlantic Treaty Organization responds to increased military activity near Eastern border.",
    "span": "North Atlantic Treaty Organization",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.000154719308
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX launches a new satellite into orbit.",
    "span": "Elon Musk",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -6.3926616e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "New York City's mayor announces a plan to improve public transportation.",
    "span": "New York City",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -7.496732306666667e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The World Health Organization warns of a new strain of flu virus.",
    "span": "World Health Organization",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0001156270795
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tesla announces opening of new electric vehicle factory in Canberra.",
    "span": "Tesla",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0329088838895
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tesla announces opening of new electric vehicle factory in Canberra.",
    "span": "Canberra",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00057737790775
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Canberra experiences record-breaking heatwave as temperatures soar above 40 degrees.",
    "span": "Canberra",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -5.36408665e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Investigation reveals that Tesla CEO Elon Musk is under scrutiny for alleged stock manipulation.",
    "span": "Tesla",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -5.6484790250000003e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Investigation reveals that Tesla CEO Elon Musk is under scrutiny for alleged stock manipulation.",
    "span": "Elon Musk",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -4.055597308e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Jennifer Lawrence to star in new Hollywood blockbuster.",
    "span": "Jennifer Lawrence",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0046956885162
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Wikimedia Foundation announces partnership with major tech company.",
    "span": "Wikimedia Foundation",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -2.7789261333333335e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Auckland named top travel destination for 2021.",
    "span": "Auckland",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -1.9838376399999997e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Jeffree Star announces new makeup line.",
    "span": "Jeffree Star",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.007825074637166666
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Sergey Brin steps down as president of Alphabet.",
    "span": "Sergey Brin",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.00018174083512875
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Sergey Brin steps down as president of Alphabet.",
    "span": "Alphabet",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00078332532975
  },
  {
    "sentence": "New York City imposes vaccine mandate for indoor activities.",
    "span": "New York City",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -8.429882675e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Martin Luther King Jr.'s legacy continues to inspire civil rights activists today.",
    "span": "Martin Luther King Jr.",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.00745077963620625
  },
  {
    "sentence": "United Nations condemns attack on aid convoy in Syria.",
    "span": "United Nations",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0018080371905799995
  },
  {
    "sentence": "United Nations condemns attack on aid convoy in Syria.",
    "span": "Syria",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0007032152895
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Singapore announces new trade agreement with Japan.",
    "span": "Singapore",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00031013644825
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Singapore announces new trade agreement with Japan.",
    "span": "Japan",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0055881389615
  },
  {
    "sentence": "PM Lee Hsien Loong addresses the United Nations General Assembly.",
    "span": "PM Lee Hsien Loong",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.011470865554390001
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Singapore Airlines wins 'Best Airline' award for the fifth consecutive year.",
    "span": "Singapore Airlines",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.013728172292488
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Recep Tayyip Erdoğan meets with EU officials in Brussels to discuss migration policy.",
    "span": "Recep Tayyip Erdoğan",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -1.8733515391666667e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Recep Tayyip Erdoğan meets with EU officials in Brussels to discuss migration policy.",
    "span": "EU",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.017814392654000002
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Recep Tayyip Erdoğan meets with EU officials in Brussels to discuss migration policy.",
    "span": "Brussels",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00044099370825
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Brussels issues new guidelines for vaccine distribution in the region.",
    "span": "Brussels",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -5.8429918400000003e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Turkish President Recep Tayyip Erdoğan addresses NATO leaders in Brussels regarding security in the region.",
    "span": "Recep Tayyip Erdoğan",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.00035567521048333336
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Turkish President Recep Tayyip Erdoğan addresses NATO leaders in Brussels regarding security in the region.",
    "span": "NATO",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.000388660559725
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Turkish President Recep Tayyip Erdoğan addresses NATO leaders in Brussels regarding security in the region.",
    "span": "Brussels",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -1.4915265475e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The flooding in Jakarta has displaced thousands of residents.",
    "span": "Jakarta",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0013709942769
  },
  {
    "sentence": "President Jokowi announces new economic policies to boost growth in Jakarta.",
    "span": "President Jokowi",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.3294409143933286
  },
  {
    "sentence": "President Jokowi announces new economic policies to boost growth in Jakarta.",
    "span": "Jakarta",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -8.5682356375e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "KFC plans to open 50 new stores in Jakarta by the end of the year.",
    "span": "KFC",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -5.438573908e-06
  },
  {
