{"sentence": "NASA's new rover successfully lands on Mars, sending back stunning images of the red planet.", "tokens": ["NASA", "'", "s", "new", "rover", "successfully", "lands", "on", "Mars", ",", "sending", "back", "stunning", "images", "of", "the", "red", "planet", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX announces plans for a manned mission to Mars by 2026.", "tokens": ["Elon", "Musk", "'", "s", "SpaceX", "announces", "plans", "for", "a", "manned", "mission", "to", "Mars", "by", "2026", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The United Nations reports a spike in violence in the Democratic Republic of the Congo, leading to a humanitarian crisis.", "tokens": ["The", "United", "Nations", "reports", "a", "spike", "in", "violence", "in", "the", "Democratic", "Republic", "of", "the", "Congo", ",", "leading", "to", "a", "humanitarian", "crisis", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX successfully launches communication satellite.", "tokens": ["Elon", "Musk", "'", "s", "SpaceX", "successfully", "launches", "communication", "satellite", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "United Nations peacekeeping mission in Mali extended for another year.", "tokens": ["United", "Nations", "peacekeeping", "mission", "in", "Mali", "extended", "for", "another", "year", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "German Chancellor Angela Merkel meets with French President Emmanuel Macron to discuss EU immigration policy.", "tokens": ["German", "Chancellor", "Angela", "Merkel", "meets", "with", "French", "President", "Emmanuel", "Macron", "to", "discuss", "EU", "immigration", "policy", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX successfully launches 60 new Starlink satellites into orbit.", "tokens": ["Elon", "Musk", "'", "s", "SpaceX", "successfully", "launches", "60", "new", "Starlink", "satellites", "into", "orbit", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The United Nations reports record-high temperatures in the Arctic region.", "tokens": ["The", "United", "Nations", "reports", "record", "-", "high", "temperatures", "in", "the", "Arctic", "region", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Mayor Johnson announces new infrastructure plan for the city.", "tokens": ["Mayor", "Johnson", "announces", "new", "infrastructure", "plan", "for", "the", "city", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "High school students protest climate change in front of the White House.", "tokens": ["High", "school", "students", "protest", "climate", "change", "in", "front", "of", "the", "White", "House", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "CHINA TO IMPOSE TARIFFS ON U.S. GOODS IN RETALIATION.", "tokens": ["CHINA", "TO", "IMPOSE", "TARIFFS", "ON", "U", ".", "S", ".", "GOODS", "IN", "RETALIATION", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "ELON MUSK JOINS TWITTER BOARD OF DIRECTORS.", "tokens": ["ELON", "MUSK", "JOINS", "TWITTER", "BOARD", "OF", "DIRECTORS", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tesla CEO Elon Musk announces plans for new electric car model.", "tokens": ["Tesla", "CEO", "Elon", "Musk", "announces", "plans", "for", "new", "electric", "car", "model", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Japan welcomes tourists back as international travel restrictions ease.", "tokens": ["Japan", "welcomes", "tourists", "back", "as", "international", "travel", "restrictions", "ease", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "UNICEF provides humanitarian aid to refugees in war-torn region.", "tokens": ["UNICEF", "provides", "humanitarian", "aid", "to", "refugees", "in", "war", "-", "torn", "region", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The United Nations reports a surge in humanitarian aid to war-torn regions.", "tokens": ["The", "United", "Nations", "reports", "a", "surge", "in", "humanitarian", "aid", "to", "war", "-", "torn", "regions", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Amelia Earhart's long-lost plane believed to have been found in the Pacific Ocean.", "tokens": ["Amelia", "Earhart", "'", "s", "long", "-", "lost", "plane", "believed", "to", "have", "been", "found", "in", "the", "Pacific", "Ocean", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "NASA's Mars rover sends back stunning images of the planet's surface.", "tokens": ["NASA", "'", "s", "Mars", "rover", "sends", "back", "stunning", "images", "of", "the", "planet", "'", "s", "surface", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tesla announces new electric vehicle model.", "tokens": ["Tesla", "announces", "new", "electric", "vehicle", "model", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "London mayor introduces new public transportation initiative.", "tokens": ["London", "mayor", "introduces", "new", "public", "transportation", "initiative", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Actress Emma Stone to star in upcoming blockbuster film.", "tokens": ["Actress", "Emma", "Stone", "to", "star", "in", "upcoming", "blockbuster", "film", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX successfully launches rocket into orbit.", "tokens": ["Elon", "Musk", "'", "s", "SpaceX", "successfully", "launches", "rocket", "into", "orbit", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "New York City to implement new public transportation system by 2025.", "tokens": ["New", "York", "City", "to", "implement", "new", "public", "transportation", "system", "by", "2025", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Apple Inc. announces record-breaking iPhone sales for the quarter.", "tokens": ["Apple", "Inc", ".", "announces", "record", "-", "breaking", "iPhone", "sales", "for", "the", "quarter", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tesla's CEO, Elon Musk, announces plans for new electric car model.", "tokens": ["Tesla", "'", "s", "CEO", ",", "Elon", "Musk", ",", "announces", "plans", "for", "new", "electric", "car", "model", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "China imposes new restrictions on tech industry.", "tokens": ["China", "imposes", "new", "restrictions", "on", "tech", "industry", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Apple launches new iPhone with upgraded features.", "tokens": ["Apple", "launches", "new", "iPhone", "with", "upgraded", "features", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tesla's CEO Elon Musk unveils the company's latest electric car model.", "tokens": ["Tesla", "'", "s", "CEO", "Elon", "Musk", "unveils", "the", "company", "'", "s", "latest", "electric", "car", "model", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The United Nations report warns of a looming humanitarian crisis in Yemen as the conflict continues.", "tokens": ["The", "United", "Nations", "report", "warns", "of", "a", "looming", "humanitarian", "crisis", "in", "Yemen", "as", "the", "conflict", "continues", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Celebrity chef Gordon Ramsay opens a new restaurant in Las Vegas.", "tokens": ["Celebrity", "chef", "Gordon", "Ramsay", "opens", "a", "new", "restaurant", "in", "Las", "Vegas", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "President Biden visits London to discuss trade agreements with Prime Minister Johnson.", "tokens": ["President", "Biden", "visits", "London", "to", "discuss", "trade", "agreements", "with", "Prime", "Minister", "Johnson", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "I-person", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Earthquake hits southern California, causing damage to several buildings.", "tokens": ["Earthquake", "hits", "southern", "California", ",", "causing", "damage", "to", "several", "buildings", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX successfully launches satellite into orbit.", "tokens": ["Elon", "Musk", "'", "s", "SpaceX", "successfully", "launches", "satellite", "into", "orbit", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "New York City implements new traffic control measures to reduce congestion.", "tokens": ["New", "York", "City", "implements", "new", "traffic", "control", "measures", "to", "reduce", "congestion", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "World Health Organization reports vaccine distribution progress in Africa.", "tokens": ["World", "Health", "Organization", "reports", "vaccine", "distribution", "progress", "in", "Africa", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tesla's CEO, Elon Musk, unveils the company's latest electric vehicle model.", "tokens": ["Tesla", "'", "s", "CEO", ",", "Elon", "Musk", ",", "unveils", "the", "company", "'", "s", "latest", "electric", "vehicle", "model", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Violent clashes erupt between police and protesters in Hong Kong.", "tokens": ["Violent", "clashes", "erupt", "between", "police", "and", "protesters", "in", "Hong", "Kong", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "NASA announces plans for a manned mission to Mars by 2030.", "tokens": ["NASA", "announces", "plans", "for", "a", "manned", "mission", "to", "Mars", "by", "2030", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tesla's stock price reaches all-time high.", "tokens": ["Tesla", "'", "s", "stock", "price", "reaches", "all", "-", "time", "high", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Jennifer Aniston to star in new Netflix series.", "tokens": ["Jennifer", "Aniston", "to", "star", "in", "new", "Netflix", "series", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Japan pledges $10 million in humanitarian aid to Afghanistan.", "tokens": ["Japan", "pledges", "$", "10", "million", "in", "humanitarian", "aid", "to", "Afghanistan", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "COVID-19 cases surge in India, overwhelming hospitals and healthcare workers.", "tokens": ["COVID", "-", "19", "cases", "surge", "in", "India", ",", "overwhelming", "hospitals", "and", "healthcare", "workers", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Apple announces new iPhone launch event, expected to unveil the latest technology and features.", "tokens": ["Apple", "announces", "new", "iPhone", "launch", "event", ",", "expected", "to", "unveil", "the", "latest", "technology", "and", "features", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Apple unveils new line of iPhones.", "tokens": ["Apple", "unveils", "new", "line", "of", "iPhones", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Earthquake hits southern California, causing minor damage.", "tokens": ["Earthquake", "hits", "southern", "California", ",", "causing", "minor", "damage", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "UNICEF reports increase in child malnutrition rates in developing countries.", "tokens": ["UNICEF", "reports", "increase", "in", "child", "malnutrition", "rates", "in", "developing", "countries", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tech giant Apple announces new iPhone release.", "tokens": ["Tech", "giant", "Apple", "announces", "new", "iPhone", "release", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Los Angeles Lakers acquire top draft pick for upcoming season.", "tokens": ["Los", "Angeles", "Lakers", "acquire", "top", "draft", "pick", "for", "upcoming", "season", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Famous actress Jennifer Lawrence spotted dining in New York City.", "tokens": ["Famous", "actress", "Jennifer", "Lawrence", "spotted", "dining", "in", "New", "York", "City", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tesla CEO Elon Musk predicts record-breaking sales for the next quarter.", "tokens": ["Tesla", "CEO", "Elon", "Musk", "predicts", "record", "-", "breaking", "sales", "for", "the", "next", "quarter", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The European Union drafts new regulations on carbon emissions for member countries.", "tokens": ["The", "European", "Union", "drafts", "new", "regulations", "on", "carbon", "emissions", "for", "member", "countries", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Los Angeles Dodgers pitcher Clayton Kershaw throws a no-hitter against the San Francisco Giants.", "tokens": ["Los", "Angeles", "Dodgers", "pitcher", "Clayton", "Kershaw", "throws", "a", "no", "-", "hitter", "against", "the", "San", "Francisco", "Giants", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX to launch new satellite into orbit.", "tokens": ["Elon", "Musk", "'", "s", "SpaceX", "to", "launch", "new", "satellite", "into", "orbit", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "New York City Mayor announces new plan to address homelessness crisis.", "tokens": ["New", "York", "City", "Mayor", "announces", "new", "plan", "to", "address", "homelessness", "crisis", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Apple Inc. unveils latest iPhone with 5G capability.", "tokens": ["Apple", "Inc", ".", "unveils", "latest", "iPhone", "with", "5G", "capability", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX plans to launch satellite internet service in India.", "tokens": ["Elon", "Musk", "'", "s", "SpaceX", "plans", "to", "launch", "satellite", "internet", "service", "in", "India", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Unemployment rate in New York City drops to 5.1 percent, the lowest in a decade.", "tokens": ["Unemployment", "rate", "in", "New", "York", "City", "drops", "to", "5", ".", "1", "percent", ",", "the", "lowest", "in", "a", "decade", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Apple announces new iPhone model with advanced camera features.", "tokens": ["Apple", "announces", "new", "iPhone", "model", "with", "advanced", "camera", "features", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX launches new satellite into orbit.", "tokens": ["Elon", "Musk", "'", "s", "SpaceX", "launches", "new", "satellite", "into", "orbit", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Hurricane Maria devastates Puerto Rico, leaving millions without power.", "tokens": ["Hurricane", "Maria", "devastates", "Puerto", "Rico", ",", "leaving", "millions", "without", "power", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "I-location", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Apple unveils new iPhone with advanced facial recognition technology.", "tokens": ["Apple", "unveils", "new", "iPhone", "with", "advanced", "facial", "recognition", "technology", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "NASA's Perseverance rover makes historic landing on Mars.", "tokens": ["NASA", "'", "s", "Perseverance", "rover", "makes", "historic", "landing", "on", "Mars", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX plans to launch another set of Starlink satellites.", "tokens": ["Elon", "Musk", "'", "s", "SpaceX", "plans", "to", "launch", "another", "set", "of", "Starlink", "satellites", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "European Union imposes sanctions on Russia over Navalny case.", "tokens": ["European", "Union", "imposes", "sanctions", "on", "Russia", "over", "Navalny", "case", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "B-person", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Wuhan reports zero new COVID-19 cases for the third consecutive day.", "tokens": ["Wuhan", "reports", "zero", "new", "COVID", "-", "19", "cases", "for", "the", "third", "consecutive", "day", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Apple unveils new lineup of iPhone models with improved camera and processing capabilities.", "tokens": ["Apple", "unveils", "new", "lineup", "of", "iPhone", "models", "with", "improved", "camera", "and", "processing", "capabilities", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Stock prices soar as tech giant Apple announces record-breaking quarterly earnings.", "tokens": ["Stock", "prices", "soar", "as", "tech", "giant", "Apple", "announces", "record", "-", "breaking", "quarterly", "earnings", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Prime Minister Johnson plans to visit European Union headquarters to discuss Brexit negotiations.", "tokens": ["Prime", "Minister", "Johnson", "plans", "to", "visit", "European", "Union", "headquarters", "to", "discuss", "Brexit", "negotiations", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Wildfires continue to spread across California, prompting evacuations in several communities.", "tokens": ["Wildfires", "continue", "to", "spread", "across", "California", ",", "prompting", "evacuations", "in", "several", "communities", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tesla unveils new electric car model.", "tokens": ["Tesla", "unveils", "new", "electric", "car", "model", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Hurricane Irma devastates Florida coast.", "tokens": ["Hurricane", "Irma", "devastates", "Florida", "coast", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Elon Musk announces plans for SpaceX Mars mission.", "tokens": ["Elon", "Musk", "announces", "plans", "for", "SpaceX", "Mars", "mission", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "B-location", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "President Biden promotes infrastructure plan during visit to Ohio.", "tokens": ["President", "Biden", "promotes", "infrastructure", "plan", "during", "visit", "to", "Ohio", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Apple announces new product launch event next month.", "tokens": ["Apple", "announces", "new", "product", "launch", "event", "next", "month", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "World Health Organization issues new guidelines for COVID-19 testing.", "tokens": ["World", "Health", "Organization", "issues", "new", "guidelines", "for", "COVID", "-", "19", "testing", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tesla unveils new model electric car at tech conference.", "tokens": ["Tesla", "unveils", "new", "model", "electric", "car", "at", "tech", "conference", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "California governor announces plan to combat wildfires.", "tokens": ["California", "governor", "announces", "plan", "to", "combat", "wildfires", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "CEO of Apple Inc. steps down after successful product launch.", "tokens": ["CEO", "of", "Apple", "Inc", ".", "steps", "down", "after", "successful", "product", "launch", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tesla CEO Elon Musk announces plan for new electric vehicle model.", "tokens": ["Tesla", "CEO", "Elon", "Musk", "announces", "plan", "for", "new", "electric", "vehicle", "model", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tokyo Olympics postponed due to COVID-19 pandemic.", "tokens": ["Tokyo", "Olympics", "postponed", "due", "to", "COVID", "-", "19", "pandemic", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Apple Inc. unveils latest iPhone with advanced features.", "tokens": ["Apple", "Inc", ".", "unveils", "latest", "iPhone", "with", "advanced", "features", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX to launch new satellite into orbit next month.", "tokens": ["Elon", "Musk", "'", "s", "SpaceX", "to", "launch", "new", "satellite", "into", "orbit", "next", "month", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Heavy rain causes flooding in downtown New York City.", "tokens": ["Heavy", "rain", "causes", "flooding", "in", "downtown", "New", "York", "City", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Apple Inc. announces partnership with international tech company for new product release.", "tokens": ["Apple", "Inc", ".", "announces", "partnership", "with", "international", "tech", "company", "for", "new", "product", "release", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tesla surpasses expectations with record-breaking quarterly revenue.", "tokens": ["Tesla", "surpasses", "expectations", "with", "record", "-", "breaking", "quarterly", "revenue", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "In a historic move, Paris Agreement enters into force with overwhelming global support.", "tokens": ["In", "a", "historic", "move", ",", "Paris", "Agreement", "enters", "into", "force", "with", "overwhelming", "global", "support", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Famous chef Gordon Ramsay opens new restaurant in New York City.", "tokens": ["Famous", "chef", "Gordon", "Ramsay", "opens", "new", "restaurant", "in", "New", "York", "City", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Japan's Prime Minister visits United States for trade talks.", "tokens": ["Japan", "'", "s", "Prime", "Minister", "visits", "United", "States", "for", "trade", "talks", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Apple Inc. surpasses $3 trillion market cap.", "tokens": ["Apple", "Inc", ".", "surpasses", "$", "3", "trillion", "market", "cap", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tesla's CEO Elon Musk predicts record-breaking sales for the next quarter.", "tokens": ["Tesla", "'", "s", "CEO", "Elon", "Musk", "predicts", "record", "-", "breaking", "sales", "for", "the", "next", "quarter", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "New York City declares state of emergency due to extreme weather conditions.", "tokens": ["New", "York", "City", "declares", "state", "of", "emergency", "due", "to", "extreme", "weather", "conditions", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The World Health Organization announces global vaccination initiative for COVID-19.", "tokens": ["The", "World", "Health", "Organization", "announces", "global", "vaccination", "initiative", "for", "COVID", "-", "19", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "President Biden's infrastructure plan faces opposition from Republican lawmakers.", "tokens": ["President", "Biden", "'", "s", "infrastructure", "plan", "faces", "opposition", "from", "Republican", "lawmakers", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Wildfires continue to devastate the forests in California.", "tokens": ["Wildfires", "continue", "to", "devastate", "the", "forests", "in", "California", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Apple Inc. announces a new lineup of products at their annual event.", "tokens": ["Apple", "Inc", ".", "announces", "a", "new", "lineup", "of", "products", "at", "their", "annual", "event", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Fire breaks out in downtown Los Angeles, causing traffic delays.", "tokens": ["Fire", "breaks", "out", "in", "downtown", "Los", "Angeles", ",", "causing", "traffic", "delays", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "U.S. Senate passes new bill to increase funding for public schools.", "tokens": ["U", ".", "S", ".", "Senate", "passes", "new", "bill", "to", "increase", "funding", "for", "public", "schools", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "NASA's Perseverance Rover discovers evidence of ancient life on Mars.", "tokens": ["NASA", "'", "s", "Perseverance", "Rover", "discovers", "evidence", "of", "ancient", "life", "on", "Mars", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "New York City declares state of emergency due to severe weather.", "tokens": ["New", "York", "City", "declares", "state", "of", "emergency", "due", "to", "severe", "weather", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "NASA successfully launches new communication satellite into orbit.", "tokens": ["NASA", "successfully", "launches", "new", "communication", "satellite", "into", "orbit", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Michelle Obama to speak at United Nations summit on education.", "tokens": ["Michelle", "Obama", "to", "speak", "at", "United", "Nations", "summit", "on", "education", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tensions rise as Russia sends more troops to Ukraine border.", "tokens": ["Tensions", "rise", "as", "Russia", "sends", "more", "troops", "to", "Ukraine", "border", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX launches another set of Starlink satellites into orbit.", "tokens": ["Elon", "Musk", "'", "s", "SpaceX", "launches", "another", "set", "of", "Starlink", "satellites", "into", "orbit", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Wildfires continue to ravage parts of California, forcing thousands to evacuate their homes.", "tokens": ["Wildfires", "continue", "to", "ravage", "parts", "of", "California", ",", "forcing", "thousands", "to", "evacuate", "their", "homes", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Microsoft's acquisition of LinkedIn shakes up the tech industry.", "tokens": ["Microsoft", "'", "s", "acquisition", "of", "LinkedIn", "shakes", "up", "the", "tech", "industry", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tech giant Apple unveils new iPhone 13.", "tokens": ["Tech", "giant", "Apple", "unveils", "new", "iPhone", "13", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Chancellor Angela Merkel wins fourth term in Germany.", "tokens": ["Chancellor", "Angela", "Merkel", "wins", "fourth", "term", "in", "Germany", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Wildfires continue to ravage California, forcing thousands to evacuate.", "tokens": ["Wildfires", "continue", "to", "ravage", "California", ",", "forcing", "thousands", "to", "evacuate", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tesla announces plans to build new factory in Germany.", "tokens": ["Tesla", "announces", "plans", "to", "build", "new", "factory", "in", "Germany", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "CEO of Google to step down after 10 years at the company.", "tokens": ["CEO", "of", "Google", "to", "step", "down", "after", "10", "years", "at", "the", "company", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Firefighters battle massive blaze in downtown Sydney.", "tokens": ["Firefighters", "battle", "massive", "blaze", "in", "downtown", "Sydney", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The CEO of Apple, Tim Cook, announces the release of a new line of iPhones.", "tokens": ["The", "CEO", "of", "Apple", ",", "Tim", "Cook", ",", "announces", "the", "release", "of", "a", "new", "line", "of", "iPhones", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "A fire broke out in a residential building in downtown Los Angeles, forcing the evacuation of hundreds of residents.", "tokens": ["A", "fire", "broke", "out", "in", "a", "residential", "building", "in", "downtown", "Los", "Angeles", ",", "forcing", "the", "evacuation", "of", "hundreds", "of", "residents", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The United Nations issued a statement condemning the recent acts of aggression by North Korea.", "tokens": ["The", "United", "Nations", "issued", "a", "statement", "condemning", "the", "recent", "acts", "of", "aggression", "by", "North", "Korea", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The famous actress will be hosting a charity event to raise funds for a children's hospital.", "tokens": ["The", "famous", "actress", "will", "be", "hosting", "a", "charity", "event", "to", "raise", "funds", "for", "a", "children", "'", "s", "hospital", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The United Nations reported a sharp increase in humanitarian aid to the war-torn region.", "tokens": ["The", "United", "Nations", "reported", "a", "sharp", "increase", "in", "humanitarian", "aid", "to", "the", "war", "-", "torn", "region", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX successfully lands Starship prototype.", "tokens": ["Elon", "Musk", "'", "s", "SpaceX", "successfully", "lands", "Starship", "prototype", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Stocks rally as Apple surpasses revenue expectations.", "tokens": ["Stocks", "rally", "as", "Apple", "surpasses", "revenue", "expectations", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tesla announces plans to build new gigafactory in Texas.", "tokens": ["Tesla", "announces", "plans", "to", "build", "new", "gigafactory", "in", "Texas", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Los Angeles Lakers trade star player to New York Knicks.", "tokens": ["Los", "Angeles", "Lakers", "trade", "star", "player", "to", "New", "York", "Knicks", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tennis champion Serena Williams advances to the finals of Wimbledon.", "tokens": ["Tennis", "champion", "Serena", "Williams", "advances", "to", "the", "finals", "of", "Wimbledon", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "President Biden announces infrastructure plan to address aging roads and bridges.", "tokens": ["President", "Biden", "announces", "infrastructure", "plan", "to", "address", "aging", "roads", "and", "bridges", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The CEO of Google announced a new initiative to combat online misinformation.", "tokens": ["The", "CEO", "of", "Google", "announced", "a", "new", "initiative", "to", "combat", "online", "misinformation", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Pop star Taylor Swift is set to release her highly anticipated new album next month.", "tokens": ["Pop", "star", "Taylor", "Swift", "is", "set", "to", "release", "her", "highly", "anticipated", "new", "album", "next", "month", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "United Nations report warns of potential food crisis in Africa.", "tokens": ["United", "Nations", "report", "warns", "of", "potential", "food", "crisis", "in", "Africa", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "California governor signs new climate change legislation.", "tokens": ["California", "governor", "signs", "new", "climate", "change", "legislation", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Famous actress Jennifer Lawrence to star in upcoming thriller film.", "tokens": ["Famous", "actress", "Jennifer", "Lawrence", "to", "star", "in", "upcoming", "thriller", "film", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "New York City braces for potential subway strike.", "tokens": ["New", "York", "City", "braces", "for", "potential", "subway", "strike", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Apple Inc. announces the release of their new iPhone model.", "tokens": ["Apple", "Inc", ".", "announces", "the", "release", "of", "their", "new", "iPhone", "model", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX company successfully launches another batch of Starlink satellites.", "tokens": ["Elon", "Musk", "'", "s", "SpaceX", "company", "successfully", "launches", "another", "batch", "of", "Starlink", "satellites", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tesla surpasses $1 trillion market value.", "tokens": ["Tesla", "surpasses", "$", "1", "trillion", "market", "value", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "President Biden delivers speech on economy and infrastructure in New York City.", "tokens": ["President", "Biden", "delivers", "speech", "on", "economy", "and", "infrastructure", "in", "New", "York", "City", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Hurricane Elsa makes landfall in Florida, causing widespread power outages.", "tokens": ["Hurricane", "Elsa", "makes", "landfall", "in", "Florida", ",", "causing", "widespread", "power", "outages", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-person", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Japan experiences record-breaking heatwave.", "tokens": ["Japan", "experiences", "record", "-", "breaking", "heatwave", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Paris Hilton announces engagement to Carter Reum.", "tokens": ["Paris", "Hilton", "announces", "engagement", "to", "Carter", "Reum", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The United Nations condemns human rights abuses in Myanmar.", "tokens": ["The", "United", "Nations", "condemns", "human", "rights", "abuses", "in", "Myanmar", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "JFK Airport in New York City to undergo major renovation.", "tokens": ["JFK", "Airport", "in", "New", "York", "City", "to", "undergo", "major", "renovation", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "I-location", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Amazon announces plans to open new fulfillment center in Texas.", "tokens": ["Amazon", "announces", "plans", "to", "open", "new", "fulfillment", "center", "in", "Texas", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Thousands gather in Times Square to ring in the New Year.", "tokens": ["Thousands", "gather", "in", "Times", "Square", "to", "ring", "in", "the", "New", "Year", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX successfully launches crewed mission to International Space Station.", "tokens": ["Elon", "Musk", "'", "s", "SpaceX", "successfully", "launches", "crewed", "mission", "to", "International", "Space", "Station", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "China imposes new tariffs on imported American goods.", "tokens": ["China", "imposes", "new", "tariffs", "on", "imported", "American", "goods", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Serena Williams advances to the quarterfinals of the French Open.", "tokens": ["Serena", "Williams", "advances", "to", "the", "quarterfinals", "of", "the", "French", "Open", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX successfully launches new batch of Starlink satellites.", "tokens": ["Elon", "Musk", "'", "s", "SpaceX", "successfully", "launches", "new", "batch", "of", "Starlink", "satellites", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "New York City Mayor announces plan to address homelessness crisis.", "tokens": ["New", "York", "City", "Mayor", "announces", "plan", "to", "address", "homelessness", "crisis", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "B-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "NASA announces plans for new mission to Mars.", "tokens": ["NASA", "announces", "plans", "for", "new", "mission", "to", "Mars", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tech giant Apple unveils new iPhone with 5G capability.", "tokens": ["Tech", "giant", "Apple", "unveils", "new", "iPhone", "with", "5G", "capability", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Former president Barack Obama to release new memoir.", "tokens": ["Former", "president", "Barack", "Obama", "to", "release", "new", "memoir", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The United Nations releases new report on global poverty rate.", "tokens": ["The", "United", "Nations", "releases", "new", "report", "on", "global", "poverty", "rate", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX launches satellite into orbit.", "tokens": ["Elon", "Musk", "'", "s", "SpaceX", "launches", "satellite", "into", "orbit", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Paris fashion week kicks off with dazzling runway shows.", "tokens": ["Paris", "fashion", "week", "kicks", "off", "with", "dazzling", "runway", "shows", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The CEO of Apple announces the launch of a new iPhone.", "tokens": ["The", "CEO", "of", "Apple", "announces", "the", "launch", "of", "a", "new", "iPhone", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-person", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The United Nations report highlights the growing concerns over climate change.", "tokens": ["The", "United", "Nations", "report", "highlights", "the", "growing", "concerns", "over", "climate", "change", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The mayor of London introduces new measures to tackle air pollution.", "tokens": ["The", "mayor", "of", "London", "introduces", "new", "measures", "to", "tackle", "air", "pollution", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-person", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "CALIFORNIA WILDFIRES LEAD TO EVACUATIONS IN NAPA VALLEY.", "tokens": ["CALIFORNIA", "WILDFIRES", "LEAD", "TO", "EVACUATIONS", "IN", "NAPA", "VALLEY", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "GOOGLE CEO MAKES ANNOUNCEMENT ABOUT COMPANY'S NEW TECHNOLOGY.", "tokens": ["GOOGLE", "CEO", "MAKES", "ANNOUNCEMENT", "ABOUT", "COMPANY", "'", "S", "NEW", "TECHNOLOGY", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "B-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tesla announces plans to build new factory in Texas.", "tokens": ["Tesla", "announces", "plans", "to", "build", "new", "factory", "in", "Texas", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The Prime Minister of Japan's visit to the United States will focus on trade and security discussions.", "tokens": ["The", "Prime", "Minister", "of", "Japan", "'", "s", "visit", "to", "the", "United", "States", "will", "focus", "on", "trade", "and", "security", "discussions", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-person", "I-person", "I-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Apple Inc. reports record-breaking profits for the third quarter.", "tokens": ["Apple", "Inc", ".", "reports", "record", "-", "breaking", "profits", "for", "the", "third", "quarter", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Apple Inc. announces new iPhone release date.", "tokens": ["Apple", "Inc", ".", "announces", "new", "iPhone", "release", "date", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "London mayor unveils new public transportation plan.", "tokens": ["London", "mayor", "unveils", "new", "public", "transportation", "plan", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Taylor Swift wins Grammy for Album of the Year.", "tokens": ["Taylor", "Swift", "wins", "Grammy", "for", "Album", "of", "the", "Year", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "President Biden visits European Union headquarters in Brussels to discuss climate change initiatives.", "tokens": ["President", "Biden", "visits", "European", "Union", "headquarters", "in", "Brussels", "to", "discuss", "climate", "change", "initiatives", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "SpaceX launches satellite into orbit to expand global internet coverage.", "tokens": ["SpaceX", "launches", "satellite", "into", "orbit", "to", "expand", "global", "internet", "coverage", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX launches new batch of Starlink satellites.", "tokens": ["Elon", "Musk", "'", "s", "SpaceX", "launches", "new", "batch", "of", "Starlink", "satellites", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "United States imposes new sanctions on North Korea.", "tokens": ["United", "States", "imposes", "new", "sanctions", "on", "North", "Korea", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Taylor Swift's new album breaks streaming records.", "tokens": ["Taylor", "Swift", "'", "s", "new", "album", "breaks", "streaming", "records", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tesla's CEO, Elon Musk, unveils plans for new electric car model.", "tokens": ["Tesla", "'", "s", "CEO", ",", "Elon", "Musk", ",", "unveils", "plans", "for", "new", "electric", "car", "model", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The United Nations issues a statement condemning the recent human rights abuses in Myanmar.", "tokens": ["The", "United", "Nations", "issues", "a", "statement", "condemning", "the", "recent", "human", "rights", "abuses", "in", "Myanmar", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Apple announces the launch of its new iPhone 13 series.", "tokens": ["Apple", "announces", "the", "launch", "of", "its", "new", "iPhone", "13", "series", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Apple announces record-breaking sales for the latest iPhone model.", "tokens": ["Apple", "announces", "record", "-", "breaking", "sales", "for", "the", "latest", "iPhone", "model", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The hurricane caused extensive damage to the coastal town of Wilmington, North Carolina.", "tokens": ["The", "hurricane", "caused", "extensive", "damage", "to", "the", "coastal", "town", "of", "Wilmington", ",", "North", "Carolina", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "NASA's Mars rover discovers evidence of ancient life on the red planet.", "tokens": ["NASA", "'", "s", "Mars", "rover", "discovers", "evidence", "of", "ancient", "life", "on", "the", "red", "planet", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tesla CEO Elon Musk unveils new electric car model.", "tokens": ["Tesla", "CEO", "Elon", "Musk", "unveils", "new", "electric", "car", "model", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "China launches new satellite into space.", "tokens": ["China", "launches", "new", "satellite", "into", "space", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Microsoft announces acquisition of cybersecurity company.", "tokens": ["Microsoft", "announces", "acquisition", "of", "cybersecurity", "company", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "COVID-19 cases surge in New York City, prompting new restrictions.", "tokens": ["COVID", "-", "19", "cases", "surge", "in", "New", "York", "City", ",", "prompting", "new", "restrictions", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Apple announces plan to open new headquarters in Austin, Texas.", "tokens": ["Apple", "announces", "plan", "to", "open", "new", "headquarters", "in", "Austin", ",", "Texas", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Apple Inc. announces record-breaking sales for the new iPhone model.", "tokens": ["Apple", "Inc", ".", "announces", "record", "-", "breaking", "sales", "for", "the", "new", "iPhone", "model", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Jessica Smith appointed as the new CEO of the technology company.", "tokens": ["Jessica", "Smith", "appointed", "as", "the", "new", "CEO", "of", "the", "technology", "company", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Wildfires continue to devastate the state of California, prompting mass evacuations.", "tokens": ["Wildfires", "continue", "to", "devastate", "the", "state", "of", "California", ",", "prompting", "mass", "evacuations", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tesla announces plans to open a new manufacturing facility in Austin, Texas.", "tokens": ["Tesla", "announces", "plans", "to", "open", "a", "new", "manufacturing", "facility", "in", "Austin", ",", "Texas", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Greta Thunberg delivers impassioned speech at climate change rally in New York City.", "tokens": ["Greta", "Thunberg", "delivers", "impassioned", "speech", "at", "climate", "change", "rally", "in", "New", "York", "City", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "World Health Organization issues new guidelines for vaccination distribution in developing countries.", "tokens": ["World", "Health", "Organization", "issues", "new", "guidelines", "for", "vaccination", "distribution", "in", "developing", "countries", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Apple announces new iPhone launch event.", "tokens": ["Apple", "announces", "new", "iPhone", "launch", "event", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Los Angeles Lakers sign new head coach.", "tokens": ["Los", "Angeles", "Lakers", "sign", "new", "head", "coach", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "I-location", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Renowned scientist Dr. Jane Smith wins Nobel Prize in Physics.", "tokens": ["Renowned", "scientist", "Dr", ".", "Jane", "Smith", "wins", "Nobel", "Prize", "in", "Physics", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "I-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "New York City imposes new restrictions on large gatherings.", "tokens": ["New", "York", "City", "imposes", "new", "restrictions", "on", "large", "gatherings", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Amazon CEO Jeff Bezos steps down from role.", "tokens": ["Amazon", "CEO", "Jeff", "Bezos", "steps", "down", "from", "role", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "New York City mayor announces plan to increase funding for public schools.", "tokens": ["New", "York", "City", "mayor", "announces", "plan", "to", "increase", "funding", "for", "public", "schools", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Apple announces new iPhone with 5G capability.", "tokens": ["Apple", "announces", "new", "iPhone", "with", "5G", "capability", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tesla's CEO Elon Musk unveils new electric car model.", "tokens": ["Tesla", "'", "s", "CEO", "Elon", "Musk", "unveils", "new", "electric", "car", "model", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Strong earthquake hits Tokyo, causing widespread damage.", "tokens": ["Strong", "earthquake", "hits", "Tokyo", ",", "causing", "widespread", "damage", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Apple Inc. announces plans to open new headquarters in Austin, Texas.", "tokens": ["Apple", "Inc", ".", "announces", "plans", "to", "open", "new", "headquarters", "in", "Austin", ",", "Texas", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tech giant Apple announces the release of the new iPhone 13.", "tokens": ["Tech", "giant", "Apple", "announces", "the", "release", "of", "the", "new", "iPhone", "13", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Prime Minister Trudeau unveils new climate policy.", "tokens": ["Prime", "Minister", "Trudeau", "unveils", "new", "climate", "policy", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Hurricane Ida hit Louisiana with devastating force.", "tokens": ["Hurricane", "Ida", "hit", "Louisiana", "with", "devastating", "force", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tesla reports record-breaking quarterly profits.", "tokens": ["Tesla", "reports", "record", "-", "breaking", "quarterly", "profits", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "New York City Mayor announces plan to invest in public transportation.", "tokens": ["New", "York", "City", "Mayor", "announces", "plan", "to", "invest", "in", "public", "transportation", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "B-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "World Health Organization warns of new COVID-19 variant.", "tokens": ["World", "Health", "Organization", "warns", "of", "new", "COVID", "-", "19", "variant", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Apple announces new iPhone 12 release date.", "tokens": ["Apple", "announces", "new", "iPhone", "12", "release", "date", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "President Biden unveils $2 trillion infrastructure plan.", "tokens": ["President", "Biden", "unveils", "$", "2", "trillion", "infrastructure", "plan", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Wildfire threatens homes in Los Angeles.", "tokens": ["Wildfire", "threatens", "homes", "in", "Los", "Angeles", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tesla announces record-breaking quarterly earnings.", "tokens": ["Tesla", "announces", "record", "-", "breaking", "quarterly", "earnings", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The CEO of Amazon plans to step down next year.", "tokens": ["The", "CEO", "of", "Amazon", "plans", "to", "step", "down", "next", "year", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-person", "I-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tokyo Olympics organizers unveil COVID-19 guidelines for athletes and officials.", "tokens": ["Tokyo", "Olympics", "organizers", "unveil", "COVID", "-", "19", "guidelines", "for", "athletes", "and", "officials", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tensions rise as China announces new military exercises in the South China Sea.", "tokens": ["Tensions", "rise", "as", "China", "announces", "new", "military", "exercises", "in", "the", "South", "China", "Sea", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Amazon revamps its Prime Day strategy to boost sales amid increasing competition from other e-commerce giants.", "tokens": ["Amazon", "revamps", "its", "Prime", "Day", "strategy", "to", "boost", "sales", "amid", "increasing", "competition", "from", "other", "e", "-", "commerce", "giants", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tesla announces plans to build new Gigafactory in Texas.", "tokens": ["Tesla", "announces", "plans", "to", "build", "new", "Gigafactory", "in", "Texas", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Prime Minister Johnson meets with President Macron to discuss trade agreement.", "tokens": ["Prime", "Minister", "Johnson", "meets", "with", "President", "Macron", "to", "discuss", "trade", "agreement", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Apple unveils new iPhone with innovative features.", "tokens": ["Apple", "unveils", "new", "iPhone", "with", "innovative", "features", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "President Biden signs new infrastructure bill into law.", "tokens": ["President", "Biden", "signs", "new", "infrastructure", "bill", "into", "law", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Apple Inc. unveils new iPhone model at tech conference.", "tokens": ["Apple", "Inc", ".", "unveils", "new", "iPhone", "model", "at", "tech", "conference", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Wildfires continue to devastate California.", "tokens": ["Wildfires", "continue", "to", "devastate", "California", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX successfully launches new batch of Starlink satellites into orbit.", "tokens": ["Elon", "Musk", "'", "s", "SpaceX", "successfully", "launches", "new", "batch", "of", "Starlink", "satellites", "into", "orbit", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tensions rise between Russia and Ukraine over disputed territory in the Black Sea.", "tokens": ["Tensions", "rise", "between", "Russia", "and", "Ukraine", "over", "disputed", "territory", "in", "the", "Black", "Sea", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Apple unveils new iPhone model with enhanced camera features at annual product launch event.", "tokens": ["Apple", "unveils", "new", "iPhone", "model", "with", "enhanced", "camera", "features", "at", "annual", "product", "launch", "event", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Dr. Anthony Fauci warns of potential fourth COVID-19 wave in the US.", "tokens": ["Dr", ".", "Anthony", "Fauci", "warns", "of", "potential", "fourth", "COVID", "-", "19", "wave", "in", "the", "US", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "I-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "European Union announces plans to increase renewable energy targets by 2030.", "tokens": ["European", "Union", "announces", "plans", "to", "increase", "renewable", "energy", "targets", "by", "2030", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tropical storm hits Florida coast.", "tokens": ["Tropical", "storm", "hits", "Florida", "coast", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Apple launches new iPhone with advanced camera features.", "tokens": ["Apple", "launches", "new", "iPhone", "with", "advanced", "camera", "features", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Earthquake strikes near Tokyo, Japan.", "tokens": ["Earthquake", "strikes", "near", "Tokyo", ",", "Japan", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "LeBron James signs $154 million contract with Lakers.", "tokens": ["LeBron", "James", "signs", "$", "154", "million", "contract", "with", "Lakers", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Heavy rains expected to hit Florida this weekend.", "tokens": ["Heavy", "rains", "expected", "to", "hit", "Florida", "this", "weekend", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "APPLE ANNOUNCES NEW IPHONE RELEASE DATE.", "tokens": ["APPLE", "ANNOUNCES", "NEW", "IPHONE", "RELEASE", "DATE", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "TEXAS GOVERNOR SIGNS BILL TO RESTRICT VOTING RIGHTS.", "tokens": ["TEXAS", "GOVERNOR", "SIGNS", "BILL", "TO", "RESTRICT", "VOTING", "RIGHTS", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "EUROPEAN UNION IMPOSES SANCTIONS ON RUSSIA OVER UKRAINE CRISIS.", "tokens": ["EUROPEAN", "UNION", "IMPOSES", "SANCTIONS", "ON", "RUSSIA", "OVER", "UKRAINE", "CRISIS", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "B-location", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tesla CEO Elon Musk invests in new space exploration technology.", "tokens": ["Tesla", "CEO", "Elon", "Musk", "invests", "in", "new", "space", "exploration", "technology", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "World Health Organization warns of potential outbreak in Africa.", "tokens": ["World", "Health", "Organization", "warns", "of", "potential", "outbreak", "in", "Africa", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "United Nations peacekeeping forces patrol the border between Rwanda and Congo.", "tokens": ["United", "Nations", "peacekeeping", "forces", "patrol", "the", "border", "between", "Rwanda", "and", "Congo", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Apple Inc. announces new iPhone with advanced camera technology.", "tokens": ["Apple", "Inc", ".", "announces", "new", "iPhone", "with", "advanced", "camera", "technology", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The United States imposes new tariffs on Chinese imports, sparking trade tensions.", "tokens": ["The", "United", "States", "imposes", "new", "tariffs", "on", "Chinese", "imports", ",", "sparking", "trade", "tensions", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Entrepreneur Elizabeth Holmes faces criminal charges for her role in fraud scandal at Theranos.", "tokens": ["Entrepreneur", "Elizabeth", "Holmes", "faces", "criminal", "charges", "for", "her", "role", "in", "fraud", "scandal", "at", "Theranos", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Wildfires continue to ravage large parts of Australia, forcing mass evacuations.", "tokens": ["Wildfires", "continue", "to", "ravage", "large", "parts", "of", "Australia", ",", "forcing", "mass", "evacuations", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "California wildfires force thousands to evacuate.", "tokens": ["California", "wildfires", "force", "thousands", "to", "evacuate", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tesla announces plans for new electric vehicle factory.", "tokens": ["Tesla", "announces", "plans", "for", "new", "electric", "vehicle", "factory", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "California Governor Newsom announces new COVID-19 restrictions.", "tokens": ["California", "Governor", "Newsom", "announces", "new", "COVID", "-", "19", "restrictions", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "B-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "New York City announces plans to build affordable housing developments in Brooklyn and Queens.", "tokens": ["New", "York", "City", "announces", "plans", "to", "build", "affordable", "housing", "developments", "in", "Brooklyn", "and", "Queens", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "New York City plans to implement a congestion pricing program to reduce traffic in the city center.", "tokens": ["New", "York", "City", "plans", "to", "implement", "a", "congestion", "pricing", "program", "to", "reduce", "traffic", "in", "the", "city", "center", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The World Health Organization warns of a new strain of flu virus spreading rapidly in Asia.", "tokens": ["The", "World", "Health", "Organization", "warns", "of", "a", "new", "strain", "of", "flu", "virus", "spreading", "rapidly", "in", "Asia", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tesla's CEO, Elon Musk, announces plans to build a new Gigafactory in Texas.", "tokens": ["Tesla", "'", "s", "CEO", ",", "Elon", "Musk", ",", "announces", "plans", "to", "build", "a", "new", "Gigafactory", "in", "Texas", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The United Nations urges all parties involved in the conflict to seek a peaceful resolution.", "tokens": ["The", "United", "Nations", "urges", "all", "parties", "involved", "in", "the", "conflict", "to", "seek", "a", "peaceful", "resolution", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Pop superstar Taylor Swift to release new album next month.", "tokens": ["Pop", "superstar", "Taylor", "Swift", "to", "release", "new", "album", "next", "month", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tesla announces plans to build a new gigafactory in Texas.", "tokens": ["Tesla", "announces", "plans", "to", "build", "a", "new", "gigafactory", "in", "Texas", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Angela Merkel elected as new President of European Commission.", "tokens": ["Angela", "Merkel", "elected", "as", "new", "President", "of", "European", "Commission", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Stocks soar as Apple reports record-breaking quarterly earnings.", "tokens": ["Stocks", "soar", "as", "Apple", "reports", "record", "-", "breaking", "quarterly", "earnings", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "New York City's mayor announces plans to increase affordable housing options.", "tokens": ["New", "York", "City", "'", "s", "mayor", "announces", "plans", "to", "increase", "affordable", "housing", "options", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Apple Inc. reports record-breaking sales for the latest iPhone model.", "tokens": ["Apple", "Inc", ".", "reports", "record", "-", "breaking", "sales", "for", "the", "latest", "iPhone", "model", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Renowned actress Emma Watson to star in upcoming thriller film.", "tokens": ["Renowned", "actress", "Emma", "Watson", "to", "star", "in", "upcoming", "thriller", "film", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tesla announces plans to open new Gigafactory in Texas.", "tokens": ["Tesla", "announces", "plans", "to", "open", "new", "Gigafactory", "in", "Texas", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "NASA launches new mission to explore Mars.", "tokens": ["NASA", "launches", "new", "mission", "to", "explore", "Mars", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tesla Inc. announces plans to open a new factory in Texas next year.", "tokens": ["Tesla", "Inc", ".", "announces", "plans", "to", "open", "a", "new", "factory", "in", "Texas", "next", "year", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Taylor Swift releases a new album titled 'Red (Taylor's Version).'", "tokens": ["Taylor", "Swift", "releases", "a", "new", "album", "titled", "'", "Red", "(", "Taylor", "'", "s", "Version", ")", ".", "'"], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Researchers discover ancient ruins in Greece dating back to the Mycenaean civilization.", "tokens": ["Researchers", "discover", "ancient", "ruins", "in", "Greece", "dating", "back", "to", "the", "Mycenaean", "civilization", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O"]}
{"sentence": "President Biden visits Texas to survey storm damage.", "tokens": ["President", "Biden", "visits", "Texas", "to", "survey", "storm", "damage", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "NASA announces upcoming Mars mission.", "tokens": ["NASA", "announces", "upcoming", "Mars", "mission", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Hollywood actors protest against the construction of a new oil pipeline.", "tokens": ["Hollywood", "actors", "protest", "against", "the", "construction", "of", "a", "new", "oil", "pipeline", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Amazon announces new delivery drone technology.", "tokens": ["Amazon", "announces", "new", "delivery", "drone", "technology", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "John Smith elected as the new chairman of the board.", "tokens": ["John", "Smith", "elected", "as", "the", "new", "chairman", "of", "the", "board", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Prime Minister Trudeau visits United Nations headquarters.", "tokens": ["Prime", "Minister", "Trudeau", "visits", "United", "Nations", "headquarters", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-person", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Hurricane Maria hits Puerto Rico.", "tokens": ["Hurricane", "Maria", "hits", "Puerto", "Rico", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "I-location", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tech giant Apple announces record-breaking quarterly profits.", "tokens": ["Tech", "giant", "Apple", "announces", "record", "-", "breaking", "quarterly", "profits", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "New York City Mayor declares state of emergency following severe weather.", "tokens": ["New", "York", "City", "Mayor", "declares", "state", "of", "emergency", "following", "severe", "weather", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "B-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Global environmental organization Greenpeace launches new campaign to protect endangered species.", "tokens": ["Global", "environmental", "organization", "Greenpeace", "launches", "new", "campaign", "to", "protect", "endangered", "species", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tech giant Apple unveils new product line.", "tokens": ["Tech", "giant", "Apple", "unveils", "new", "product", "line", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "New York City Mayor announces public transportation improvements.", "tokens": ["New", "York", "City", "Mayor", "announces", "public", "transportation", "improvements", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "B-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Environmental organization Greenpeace protests outside oil company headquarters.", "tokens": ["Environmental", "organization", "Greenpeace", "protests", "outside", "oil", "company", "headquarters", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Apple to release new iPhone model next month.", "tokens": ["Apple", "to", "release", "new", "iPhone", "model", "next", "month", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "CEO of Google, Sundar Pichai, speaks at tech conference.", "tokens": ["CEO", "of", "Google", ",", "Sundar", "Pichai", ",", "speaks", "at", "tech", "conference", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Hurricane Maria devastates Puerto Rico, leaving thousands without power or water.", "tokens": ["Hurricane", "Maria", "devastates", "Puerto", "Rico", ",", "leaving", "thousands", "without", "power", "or", "water", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "I-location", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX launches new batch of Starlink satellites", "tokens": ["Elon", "Musk", "'", "s", "SpaceX", "launches", "new", "batch", "of", "Starlink", "satellites"], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O"]}
{"sentence": "New York City mayoral candidate proposes affordable housing plan", "tokens": ["New", "York", "City", "mayoral", "candidate", "proposes", "affordable", "housing", "plan"], "labels": ["B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Pfizer and Moderna announce plans for COVID-19 vaccine booster shots", "tokens": ["Pfizer", "and", "Moderna", "announce", "plans", "for", "COVID", "-", "19", "vaccine", "booster", "shots"], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Dr. Anthony Fauci warns of potential COVID-19 surge in the fall.", "tokens": ["Dr", ".", "Anthony", "Fauci", "warns", "of", "potential", "COVID", "-", "19", "surge", "in", "the", "fall", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "I-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tesla announces plans to open new gigafactory in Germany.", "tokens": ["Tesla", "announces", "plans", "to", "open", "new", "gigafactory", "in", "Germany", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Famous actor to star in upcoming Marvel movie.", "tokens": ["Famous", "actor", "to", "star", "in", "upcoming", "Marvel", "movie", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "United Nations to discuss climate change at upcoming summit in Paris.", "tokens": ["United", "Nations", "to", "discuss", "climate", "change", "at", "upcoming", "summit", "in", "Paris", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Apple reaches $2 trillion market cap.", "tokens": ["Apple", "reaches", "$", "2", "trillion", "market", "cap", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Paris prepares for the annual Bastille Day celebrations.", "tokens": ["Paris", "prepares", "for", "the", "annual", "Bastille", "Day", "celebrations", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Doctors Without Borders provides aid to refugees in war-torn region.", "tokens": ["Doctors", "Without", "Borders", "provides", "aid", "to", "refugees", "in", "war", "-", "torn", "region", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Elon Musk plans to send humans to Mars by 2026.", "tokens": ["Elon", "Musk", "plans", "to", "send", "humans", "to", "Mars", "by", "2026", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Google opens new artificial intelligence research lab in London.", "tokens": ["Google", "opens", "new", "artificial", "intelligence", "research", "lab", "in", "London", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Angela Merkel reelected as Chancellor of Germany for fourth term.", "tokens": ["Angela", "Merkel", "reelected", "as", "Chancellor", "of", "Germany", "for", "fourth", "term", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX launches communication satellite into space.", "tokens": ["Elon", "Musk", "'", "s", "SpaceX", "launches", "communication", "satellite", "into", "space", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "New York City Mayor announces new affordable housing initiative.", "tokens": ["New", "York", "City", "Mayor", "announces", "new", "affordable", "housing", "initiative", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "B-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Apple Inc. unveils latest iPhone model with advanced camera technology.", "tokens": ["Apple", "Inc", ".", "unveils", "latest", "iPhone", "model", "with", "advanced", "camera", "technology", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "China imposes new restrictions on tech giant Alibaba's financial affiliate Ant Group.", "tokens": ["China", "imposes", "new", "restrictions", "on", "tech", "giant", "Alibaba", "'", "s", "financial", "affiliate", "Ant", "Group", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Associated Press journalist Kim Ng becomes first female general manager in MLB history.", "tokens": ["Associated", "Press", "journalist", "Kim", "Ng", "becomes", "first", "female", "general", "manager", "in", "MLB", "history", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Explosion in downtown New York injures several people.", "tokens": ["Explosion", "in", "downtown", "New", "York", "injures", "several", "people", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Apple's CEO Tim Cook unveils new iPhone model.", "tokens": ["Apple", "'", "s", "CEO", "Tim", "Cook", "unveils", "new", "iPhone", "model", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "APPLE UNVEILS NEW iPHONE WITH 5G CAPABILITIES.", "tokens": ["APPLE", "UNVEILS", "NEW", "iPHONE", "WITH", "5G", "CAPABILITIES", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "TOKYO OLYMPICS TO ALLOW LIMITED SPECTATORS AMID COVID-19 CONCERNS.", "tokens": ["TOKYO", "OLYMPICS", "TO", "ALLOW", "LIMITED", "SPECTATORS", "AMID", "COVID", "-", "19", "CONCERNS", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "President Biden meets with South Korean leader to discuss trade agreements.", "tokens": ["President", "Biden", "meets", "with", "South", "Korean", "leader", "to", "discuss", "trade", "agreements", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Wildfires continue to ravage California, prompting mass evacuations.", "tokens": ["Wildfires", "continue", "to", "ravage", "California", ",", "prompting", "mass", "evacuations", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Earthquake hits southern California, causing power outages and minor damage.", "tokens": ["Earthquake", "hits", "southern", "California", ",", "causing", "power", "outages", "and", "minor", "damage", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Amazon employees plan to unionize for better working conditions.", "tokens": ["Amazon", "employees", "plan", "to", "unionize", "for", "better", "working", "conditions", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tesla announces plans to open new manufacturing plant in Berlin.", "tokens": ["Tesla", "announces", "plans", "to", "open", "new", "manufacturing", "plant", "in", "Berlin", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Prime Minister Johnson delivers address on climate change at summit.", "tokens": ["Prime", "Minister", "Johnson", "delivers", "address", "on", "climate", "change", "at", "summit", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "New York Mets pitcher Jacob deGrom wins Cy Young Award.", "tokens": ["New", "York", "Mets", "pitcher", "Jacob", "deGrom", "wins", "Cy", "Young", "Award", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX plans to send civilians on a mission to the moon.", "tokens": ["Elon", "Musk", "'", "s", "SpaceX", "plans", "to", "send", "civilians", "on", "a", "mission", "to", "the", "moon", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Foreign investors pour billions into tech startups in Silicon Valley.", "tokens": ["Foreign", "investors", "pour", "billions", "into", "tech", "startups", "in", "Silicon", "Valley", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Former President Barack Obama to deliver keynote address at climate change conference.", "tokens": ["Former", "President", "Barack", "Obama", "to", "deliver", "keynote", "address", "at", "climate", "change", "conference", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX launches a Falcon 9 rocket into orbit.", "tokens": ["Elon", "Musk", "'", "s", "SpaceX", "launches", "a", "Falcon", "9", "rocket", "into", "orbit", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Paris, France, announces new measures to combat air pollution.", "tokens": ["Paris", ",", "France", ",", "announces", "new", "measures", "to", "combat", "air", "pollution", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Apple unveils the latest iPhone model at its annual product launch event.", "tokens": ["Apple", "unveils", "the", "latest", "iPhone", "model", "at", "its", "annual", "product", "launch", "event", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Severe weather advisory for residents of New York City.", "tokens": ["Severe", "weather", "advisory", "for", "residents", "of", "New", "York", "City", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Apple announces new product launch event.", "tokens": ["Apple", "announces", "new", "product", "launch", "event", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tesla's CEO, Elon Musk, announces plans for new electric vehicle.", "tokens": ["Tesla", "'", "s", "CEO", ",", "Elon", "Musk", ",", "announces", "plans", "for", "new", "electric", "vehicle", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Pfizer's COVID-19 vaccine found to be 95% effective in final analysis.", "tokens": ["Pfizer", "'", "s", "COVID", "-", "19", "vaccine", "found", "to", "be", "95", "%", "effective", "in", "final", "analysis", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Biden visits European Union headquarters to discuss climate change policies.", "tokens": ["Biden", "visits", "European", "Union", "headquarters", "to", "discuss", "climate", "change", "policies", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tesla stock surges after announcing record production numbers.", "tokens": ["Tesla", "stock", "surges", "after", "announcing", "record", "production", "numbers", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "London Mayor announces plan to reduce air pollution in the city center.", "tokens": ["London", "Mayor", "announces", "plan", "to", "reduce", "air", "pollution", "in", "the", "city", "center", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "B-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "World Health Organization warns of potential new strain of flu virus.", "tokens": ["World", "Health", "Organization", "warns", "of", "potential", "new", "strain", "of", "flu", "virus", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Apple Inc. announces the launch of its new iPhone 13 series.", "tokens": ["Apple", "Inc", ".", "announces", "the", "launch", "of", "its", "new", "iPhone", "13", "series", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The president of France, Emmanuel Macron, visits the United States for trade discussions.", "tokens": ["The", "president", "of", "France", ",", "Emmanuel", "Macron", ",", "visits", "the", "United", "States", "for", "trade", "discussions", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The United Nations reports a significant increase in humanitarian aid for refugees in war-torn regions.", "tokens": ["The", "United", "Nations", "reports", "a", "significant", "increase", "in", "humanitarian", "aid", "for", "refugees", "in", "war", "-", "torn", "regions", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Apple Inc. announces new product lineup at virtual event.", "tokens": ["Apple", "Inc", ".", "announces", "new", "product", "lineup", "at", "virtual", "event", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "President Biden travels to Europe to meet with NATO leaders.", "tokens": ["President", "Biden", "travels", "to", "Europe", "to", "meet", "with", "NATO", "leaders", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "New York City launches new program to address homelessness crisis.", "tokens": ["New", "York", "City", "launches", "new", "program", "to", "address", "homelessness", "crisis", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tokyo experiences record-breaking heatwave.", "tokens": ["Tokyo", "experiences", "record", "-", "breaking", "heatwave", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Famous chef Gordon Ramsay to open new restaurant in New York City.", "tokens": ["Famous", "chef", "Gordon", "Ramsay", "to", "open", "new", "restaurant", "in", "New", "York", "City", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "World Health Organization declares new strain of flu a global health emergency.", "tokens": ["World", "Health", "Organization", "declares", "new", "strain", "of", "flu", "a", "global", "health", "emergency", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Japan's Prime Minister meets with South Korea's President ahead of the upcoming trade talks.", "tokens": ["Japan", "'", "s", "Prime", "Minister", "meets", "with", "South", "Korea", "'", "s", "President", "ahead", "of", "the", "upcoming", "trade", "talks", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "B-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tesla's CEO unveils new electric truck model at company's annual event.", "tokens": ["Tesla", "'", "s", "CEO", "unveils", "new", "electric", "truck", "model", "at", "company", "'", "s", "annual", "event", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "B-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The United Nations releases report on the impact of climate change in the Arctic region.", "tokens": ["The", "United", "Nations", "releases", "report", "on", "the", "impact", "of", "climate", "change", "in", "the", "Arctic", "region", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Elon Musk becomes the world's richest person, surpassing Jeff Bezos.", "tokens": ["Elon", "Musk", "becomes", "the", "world", "'", "s", "richest", "person", ",", "surpassing", "Jeff", "Bezos", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O"]}
{"sentence": "New York City Mayor announces plan to invest in affordable housing.", "tokens": ["New", "York", "City", "Mayor", "announces", "plan", "to", "invest", "in", "affordable", "housing", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The CEO of Apple Inc. unveils the latest iPhone model at the tech conference.", "tokens": ["The", "CEO", "of", "Apple", "Inc", ".", "unveils", "the", "latest", "iPhone", "model", "at", "the", "tech", "conference", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-person", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Hurricane Katrina devastates New Orleans, leaving thousands homeless.", "tokens": ["Hurricane", "Katrina", "devastates", "New", "Orleans", ",", "leaving", "thousands", "homeless", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The United Nations issues a global warning about climate change.", "tokens": ["The", "United", "Nations", "issues", "a", "global", "warning", "about", "climate", "change", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tesla announces plans to open new manufacturing plant in Texas.", "tokens": ["Tesla", "announces", "plans", "to", "open", "new", "manufacturing", "plant", "in", "Texas", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Former President Obama delivers speech at climate change conference.", "tokens": ["Former", "President", "Obama", "delivers", "speech", "at", "climate", "change", "conference", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Wildfires in California continue to threaten residential areas.", "tokens": ["Wildfires", "in", "California", "continue", "to", "threaten", "residential", "areas", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Apple's new iPhone release date confirmed for September.", "tokens": ["Apple", "'", "s", "new", "iPhone", "release", "date", "confirmed", "for", "September", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tesla announces plans to build a new factory in Europe.", "tokens": ["Tesla", "announces", "plans", "to", "build", "a", "new", "factory", "in", "Europe", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Beyoncé's new album breaks streaming records.", "tokens": ["Beyoncé", "'", "s", "new", "album", "breaks", "streaming", "records", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
