[
  {
    "sentence": "NASA's new rover successfully lands on Mars, sending back stunning images of the red planet.",
    "span": "NASA",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00011735981624999999
  },
  {
    "sentence": "NASA's new rover successfully lands on Mars, sending back stunning images of the red planet.",
    "span": "Mars",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.004021162757375
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX announces plans for a manned mission to Mars by 2026.",
    "span": "Elon Musk",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -2.1431732166666666e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX announces plans for a manned mission to Mars by 2026.",
    "span": "SpaceX",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -8.2228193e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX announces plans for a manned mission to Mars by 2026.",
    "span": "Mars",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.000199014777075
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The United Nations reports a spike in violence in the Democratic Republic of the Congo, leading to a humanitarian crisis.",
    "span": "The United Nations",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.9342808444772003
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The United Nations reports a spike in violence in the Democratic Republic of the Congo, leading to a humanitarian crisis.",
    "span": "Democratic Republic of the Congo",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0016567082386
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX successfully launches communication satellite.",
    "span": "Elon Musk",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -7.292526876666668e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX successfully launches communication satellite.",
    "span": "SpaceX",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.02760409102775
  },
  {
    "sentence": "United Nations peacekeeping mission in Mali extended for another year.",
    "span": "United Nations",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -3.7337473999999995e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "United Nations peacekeeping mission in Mali extended for another year.",
    "span": "Mali",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.000271343913675
  },
  {
    "sentence": "German Chancellor Angela Merkel meets with French President Emmanuel Macron to discuss EU immigration policy.",
    "span": "Angela Merkel",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.003546750193533333
  },
  {
    "sentence": "German Chancellor Angela Merkel meets with French President Emmanuel Macron to discuss EU immigration policy.",
    "span": "Emmanuel Macron",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.028424894280399998
  },
  {
    "sentence": "German Chancellor Angela Merkel meets with French President Emmanuel Macron to discuss EU immigration policy.",
    "span": "EU",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.000437726124
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX successfully launches 60 new Starlink satellites into orbit.",
    "span": "Elon Musk",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -9.733909683333334e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX successfully launches 60 new Starlink satellites into orbit.",
    "span": "SpaceX",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.14396408518375
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The United Nations reports record-high temperatures in the Arctic region.",
    "span": "United Nations",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0008141826070999999
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The United Nations reports record-high temperatures in the Arctic region.",
    "span": "Arctic",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.034739377426500004
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Mayor Johnson announces new infrastructure plan for the city.",
    "span": "Mayor Johnson",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.18395325009479999
  },
  {
    "sentence": "High school students protest climate change in front of the White House.",
    "span": "White House",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0007598868572
  },
  {
    "sentence": "CHINA TO IMPOSE TARIFFS ON U.S. GOODS IN RETALIATION.",
    "span": "CHINA",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00060413566
  },
  {
    "sentence": "CHINA TO IMPOSE TARIFFS ON U.S. GOODS IN RETALIATION.",
    "span": "U.S.",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.01487684209555
  },
  {
    "sentence": "ELON MUSK JOINS TWITTER BOARD OF DIRECTORS.",
    "span": "ELON MUSK",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -2.6150209375e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "ELON MUSK JOINS TWITTER BOARD OF DIRECTORS.",
    "span": "TWITTER",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0034978960070000003
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tesla CEO Elon Musk announces plans for new electric car model.",
    "span": "Tesla",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00173309486825
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tesla CEO Elon Musk announces plans for new electric car model.",
    "span": "Elon Musk",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.00717431606646
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Japan welcomes tourists back as international travel restrictions ease.",
    "span": "Japan",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00013872432200000002
  },
  {
    "sentence": "UNICEF provides humanitarian aid to refugees in war-torn region.",
    "span": "UNICEF",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -6.79336956e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The United Nations reports a surge in humanitarian aid to war-torn regions.",
    "span": "United Nations",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.007215623209999999
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Amelia Earhart's long-lost plane believed to have been found in the Pacific Ocean.",
    "span": "Amelia Earhart",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.00042647866071428574
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Amelia Earhart's long-lost plane believed to have been found in the Pacific Ocean.",
    "span": "Pacific Ocean",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00030395026166
  },
  {
    "sentence": "NASA's Mars rover sends back stunning images of the planet's surface.",
    "span": "NASA",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0001405366755
  },
  {
    "sentence": "NASA's Mars rover sends back stunning images of the planet's surface.",
    "span": "Mars",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -8.6963798375e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tesla announces new electric vehicle model.",
    "span": "Tesla",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.94615974429075
  },
  {
    "sentence": "London mayor introduces new public transportation initiative.",
    "span": "London",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.008204490310749999
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Actress Emma Stone to star in upcoming blockbuster film.",
    "span": "Emma Stone",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.00040741430159999995
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX successfully launches rocket into orbit.",
    "span": "Elon Musk",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.00028127558728333334
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX successfully launches rocket into orbit.",
    "span": "SpaceX",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00828825069425
  },
  {
    "sentence": "New York City to implement new public transportation system by 2025.",
    "span": "New York City",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -8.847584178333333e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Apple Inc. announces record-breaking iPhone sales for the quarter.",
    "span": "Apple Inc.",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0202615683035
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tesla's CEO, Elon Musk, announces plans for new electric car model.",
    "span": "Tesla",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0065192535736
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tesla's CEO, Elon Musk, announces plans for new electric car model.",
    "span": "Elon Musk",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0026222224616
  },
  {
    "sentence": "China imposes new restrictions on tech industry.",
    "span": "China",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00017870247649999998
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Apple launches new iPhone with upgraded features.",
    "span": "Apple",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0055607677899
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tesla's CEO Elon Musk unveils the company's latest electric car model.",
    "span": "Tesla",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0015180514975
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tesla's CEO Elon Musk unveils the company's latest electric car model.",
    "span": "Elon Musk",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0024470009012
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The United Nations report warns of a looming humanitarian crisis in Yemen as the conflict continues.",
    "span": "United Nations",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00010521534229999999
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The United Nations report warns of a looming humanitarian crisis in Yemen as the conflict continues.",
    "span": "Yemen",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -1.93420253089015
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Celebrity chef Gordon Ramsay opens a new restaurant in Las Vegas.",
    "span": "Gordon Ramsay",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -7.571450385714284e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Celebrity chef Gordon Ramsay opens a new restaurant in Las Vegas.",
    "span": "Las Vegas",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.005775226496400001
  },
  {
    "sentence": "President Biden visits London to discuss trade agreements with Prime Minister Johnson.",
    "span": "President Biden",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.030608347524999996
  },
  {
    "sentence": "President Biden visits London to discuss trade agreements with Prime Minister Johnson.",
    "span": "London",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -5.672411825e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "President Biden visits London to discuss trade agreements with Prime Minister Johnson.",
    "span": "Prime Minister Johnson",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.00024472130705
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Earthquake hits southern California, causing damage to several buildings.",
    "span": "California",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.06690498012575
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX successfully launches satellite into orbit.",
    "span": "Elon Musk",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -1.972314576666667e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "New York City implements new traffic control measures to reduce congestion.",
    "span": "New York City",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -8.0492256e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "World Health Organization reports vaccine distribution progress in Africa.",
    "span": "World Health Organization",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -3.855732566666667e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "World Health Organization reports vaccine distribution progress in Africa.",
    "span": "Africa",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0003554352615
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tesla's CEO, Elon Musk, unveils the company's latest electric vehicle model.",
    "span": "Tesla",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0018390305993750001
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tesla's CEO, Elon Musk, unveils the company's latest electric vehicle model.",
    "span": "Elon Musk",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0030255767822
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Violent clashes erupt between police and protesters in Hong Kong.",
    "span": "Hong Kong",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0005699652148
  },
  {
    "sentence": "NASA announces plans for a manned mission to Mars by 2030.",
    "span": "NASA",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.000162304641
  },
  {
    "sentence": "NASA announces plans for a manned mission to Mars by 2030.",
    "span": "Mars",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0002568180296
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tesla's stock price reaches all-time high.",
    "span": "Tesla",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0069249350785
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Jennifer Aniston to star in new Netflix series.",
    "span": "Jennifer Aniston",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0001316997115
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Jennifer Aniston to star in new Netflix series.",
    "span": "Netflix",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -9.545522107500001e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Japan pledges $10 million in humanitarian aid to Afghanistan.",
    "span": "Japan",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00011089667575
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Japan pledges $10 million in humanitarian aid to Afghanistan.",
    "span": "Afghanistan",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00012862730625
  },
  {
    "sentence": "COVID-19 cases surge in India, overwhelming hospitals and healthcare workers.",
    "span": "India",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0006330570807499999
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Apple announces new iPhone launch event, expected to unveil the latest technology and features.",
    "span": "Apple",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.07437525313775001
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Apple unveils new line of iPhones.",
    "span": "Apple",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.022732370025
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Earthquake hits southern California, causing minor damage.",
    "span": "California",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.100081230735
  },
  {
    "sentence": "UNICEF reports increase in child malnutrition rates in developing countries.",
    "span": "UNICEF",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0019714417216333334
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tech giant Apple announces new iPhone release.",
    "span": "Apple",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.1182615146225
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Los Angeles Lakers acquire top draft pick for upcoming season.",
    "span": "Los Angeles Lakers",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.09114729641404999
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Famous actress Jennifer Lawrence spotted dining in New York City.",
    "span": "Jennifer Lawrence",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0007249518895999999
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Famous actress Jennifer Lawrence spotted dining in New York City.",
    "span": "New York City",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00017996559183333332
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tesla CEO Elon Musk predicts record-breaking sales for the next quarter.",
    "span": "Tesla",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0018619759275
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tesla CEO Elon Musk predicts record-breaking sales for the next quarter.",
    "span": "Elon Musk",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.00331219361
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The European Union drafts new regulations on carbon emissions for member countries.",
    "span": "European Union",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00016178134068
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Los Angeles Dodgers pitcher Clayton Kershaw throws a no-hitter against the San Francisco Giants.",
    "span": "Los Angeles Dodgers",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -9.417286778333336e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Los Angeles Dodgers pitcher Clayton Kershaw throws a no-hitter against the San Francisco Giants.",
    "span": "Clayton Kershaw",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -5.083394717142856e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX to launch new satellite into orbit.",
    "span": "Elon Musk",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0001815192086666667
  },
  {
    "sentence": "New York City Mayor announces new plan to address homelessness crisis.",
    "span": "New York City",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.14250218924616667
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Apple Inc. unveils latest iPhone with 5G capability.",
    "span": "Apple Inc.",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0025876633600000003
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX plans to launch satellite internet service in India.",
    "span": "Elon Musk",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.00012904941050000002
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX plans to launch satellite internet service in India.",
    "span": "SpaceX",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00018132817575
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX plans to launch satellite internet service in India.",
    "span": "India",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0015086525611
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Unemployment rate in New York City drops to 5.1 percent, the lowest in a decade.",
    "span": "New York City",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -3.6489906216666665e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Apple announces new iPhone model with advanced camera features.",
    "span": "Apple",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.02293377311375
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX launches new satellite into orbit.",
    "span": "Elon Musk",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -8.269874671666666e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Hurricane Maria devastates Puerto Rico, leaving millions without power.",
    "span": "Hurricane Maria",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.019169038814333333
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Hurricane Maria devastates Puerto Rico, leaving millions without power.",
    "span": "Puerto Rico",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0002541487696
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Apple unveils new iPhone with advanced facial recognition technology.",
    "span": "Apple",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.049776158872500004
  },
  {
    "sentence": "NASA's Perseverance rover makes historic landing on Mars.",
    "span": "NASA",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00047910493125
  },
  {
    "sentence": "NASA's Perseverance rover makes historic landing on Mars.",
    "span": "Perseverance rover",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.1709661630170875
  },
  {
    "sentence": "NASA's Perseverance rover makes historic landing on Mars.",
    "span": "Mars",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0038491709369249997
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX plans to launch another set of Starlink satellites.",
    "span": "Elon Musk",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -1.67430545e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX plans to launch another set of Starlink satellites.",
    "span": "SpaceX",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00470566673025
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX plans to launch another set of Starlink satellites.",
    "span": "Starlink",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0728387524772
  },
  {
    "sentence": "European Union imposes sanctions on Russia over Navalny case.",
    "span": "European Union",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -3.016141302e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "European Union imposes sanctions on Russia over Navalny case.",
    "span": "Russia",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -5.356705375e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "European Union imposes sanctions on Russia over Navalny case.",
    "span": "Navalny",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -2.8087269599999996e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Wuhan reports zero new COVID-19 cases for the third consecutive day.",
    "span": "Wuhan",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0366755387145
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Apple unveils new lineup of iPhone models with improved camera and processing capabilities.",
    "span": "Apple",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.037278581456825
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Apple unveils new lineup of iPhone models with improved camera and processing capabilities.",
    "span": "iPhone",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.01591274577575
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Stock prices soar as tech giant Apple announces record-breaking quarterly earnings.",
    "span": "Apple",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00574019904425
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Prime Minister Johnson plans to visit European Union headquarters to discuss Brexit negotiations.",
    "span": "Prime Minister Johnson",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.034997616168333336
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Prime Minister Johnson plans to visit European Union headquarters to discuss Brexit negotiations.",
    "span": "European Union",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0003924243277
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Wildfires continue to spread across California, prompting evacuations in several communities.",
    "span": "California",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.000115899568
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tesla unveils new electric car model.",
    "span": "Tesla",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.72245024819475
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Hurricane Irma devastates Florida coast.",
    "span": "Florida",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -1.11719578913125
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Elon Musk announces plans for SpaceX Mars mission.",
    "span": "Elon Musk",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0007763188736666667
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Elon Musk announces plans for SpaceX Mars mission.",
    "span": "SpaceX",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.06699983567375
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Elon Musk announces plans for SpaceX Mars mission.",
    "span": "Mars",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.000206225252075
  },
  {
    "sentence": "President Biden promotes infrastructure plan during visit to Ohio.",
    "span": "President Biden",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0051576466788
  },
  {
    "sentence": "President Biden promotes infrastructure plan during visit to Ohio.",
    "span": "Ohio",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0156764771735
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Apple announces new product launch event next month.",
    "span": "Apple",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00014773657872499998
  },
  {
    "sentence": "World Health Organization issues new guidelines for COVID-19 testing.",
    "span": "World Health Organization",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0023391947540666665
  },
  {
    "sentence": "World Health Organization issues new guidelines for COVID-19 testing.",
    "span": "COVID-19",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.03769437405091667
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tesla unveils new model electric car at tech conference.",
    "span": "Tesla",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.010033289977
  },
  {
    "sentence": "California governor announces plan to combat wildfires.",
    "span": "California",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0039537012085
  },
  {
    "sentence": "CEO of Apple Inc. steps down after successful product launch.",
    "span": "CEO",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.017911613460166672
  },
  {
    "sentence": "CEO of Apple Inc. steps down after successful product launch.",
    "span": "Apple Inc.",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.01406098500875
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tesla CEO Elon Musk announces plan for new electric vehicle model.",
    "span": "Tesla",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0018158851925
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tesla CEO Elon Musk announces plan for new electric vehicle model.",
    "span": "Elon Musk",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0073618694852
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tokyo Olympics postponed due to COVID-19 pandemic.",
    "span": "Tokyo",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.010956287932480002
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Apple Inc. unveils latest iPhone with advanced features.",
    "span": "Apple Inc.",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0010578463333333332
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX to launch new satellite into orbit next month.",
    "span": "Elon Musk",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.00012730842733333335
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX to launch new satellite into orbit next month.",
    "span": "SpaceX",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.017122774006
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Heavy rain causes flooding in downtown New York City.",
    "span": "New York City",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00015050545816666668
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Apple Inc. announces partnership with international tech company for new product release.",
    "span": "Apple Inc.",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0001368013253333333
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tesla surpasses expectations with record-breaking quarterly revenue.",
    "span": "Tesla",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0053887059725
  },
  {
    "sentence": "In a historic move, Paris Agreement enters into force with overwhelming global support.",
    "span": "Paris Agreement",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.089726759861
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Famous chef Gordon Ramsay opens new restaurant in New York City.",
    "span": "Gordon Ramsay",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -7.089107917142856e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Famous chef Gordon Ramsay opens new restaurant in New York City.",
    "span": "New York City",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0010457694840500002
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Japan's Prime Minister visits United States for trade talks.",
    "span": "Japan",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -5.5980925500000004e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Japan's Prime Minister visits United States for trade talks.",
    "span": "United States",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.3168532206608
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Apple Inc. surpasses $3 trillion market cap.",
    "span": "Apple Inc.",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00018723976454999998
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tesla's CEO Elon Musk predicts record-breaking sales for the next quarter.",
    "span": "Tesla",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00037718029175
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tesla's CEO Elon Musk predicts record-breaking sales for the next quarter.",
    "span": "Elon Musk",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0004938986567599999
  },
  {
    "sentence": "New York City declares state of emergency due to extreme weather conditions.",
    "span": "New York City",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00013474154121666666
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The World Health Organization announces global vaccination initiative for COVID-19.",
    "span": "World Health Organization",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.31419466007525004
  },
  {
    "sentence": "President Biden's infrastructure plan faces opposition from Republican lawmakers.",
    "span": "President Biden",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0046207708448
  },
  {
    "sentence": "President Biden's infrastructure plan faces opposition from Republican lawmakers.",
    "span": "Republican lawmakers",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.052338693390300006
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Wildfires continue to devastate the forests in California.",
    "span": "California",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00012439649399999998
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Apple Inc. announces a new lineup of products at their annual event.",
    "span": "Apple Inc.",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0002277008546083333
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Fire breaks out in downtown Los Angeles, causing traffic delays.",
    "span": "Los Angeles",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0008092024445999999
  },
  {
    "sentence": "U.S. Senate passes new bill to increase funding for public schools.",
    "span": "U.S. Senate",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.001098135063857143
  },
  {
    "sentence": "NASA's Perseverance Rover discovers evidence of ancient life on Mars.",
    "span": "NASA",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0006200385400000001
  },
  {
    "sentence": "NASA's Perseverance Rover discovers evidence of ancient life on Mars.",
    "span": "Perseverance Rover",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00046926790391250007
  },
  {
    "sentence": "NASA's Perseverance Rover discovers evidence of ancient life on Mars.",
    "span": "Mars",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.004350436520899999
  },
  {
    "sentence": "New York City declares state of emergency due to severe weather.",
    "span": "New York City",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -4.050431688333334e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "NASA successfully launches new communication satellite into orbit.",
    "span": "NASA",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.013698282841749999
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Michelle Obama to speak at United Nations summit on education.",
    "span": "Michelle Obama",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -6.129741060000001e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Michelle Obama to speak at United Nations summit on education.",
    "span": "United Nations",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.000194654058
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tensions rise as Russia sends more troops to Ukraine border.",
    "span": "Russia",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -7.13581985e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tensions rise as Russia sends more troops to Ukraine border.",
    "span": "Ukraine",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -5.317964125e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX launches another set of Starlink satellites into orbit.",
    "span": "Elon Musk",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.00015464734021666666
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX launches another set of Starlink satellites into orbit.",
    "span": "SpaceX",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.11801041071674999
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Wildfires continue to ravage parts of California, forcing thousands to evacuate their homes.",
    "span": "California",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.000135536532
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Microsoft's acquisition of LinkedIn shakes up the tech industry.",
    "span": "Microsoft",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -5.9314961125e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Microsoft's acquisition of LinkedIn shakes up the tech industry.",
    "span": "LinkedIn",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0002930949385
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tech giant Apple unveils new iPhone 13.",
    "span": "Apple",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0738711004825
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Chancellor Angela Merkel wins fourth term in Germany.",
    "span": "Angela Merkel",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.003418488495716667
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Chancellor Angela Merkel wins fourth term in Germany.",
    "span": "Germany",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.000272753738
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Wildfires continue to ravage California, forcing thousands to evacuate.",
    "span": "California",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00020167073425
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tesla announces plans to build new factory in Germany.",
    "span": "Tesla",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -6.3816736e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tesla announces plans to build new factory in Germany.",
    "span": "Germany",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0077257087430000005
  },
  {
    "sentence": "CEO of Google to step down after 10 years at the company.",
    "span": "Google",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.03701715831249999
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Firefighters battle massive blaze in downtown Sydney.",
    "span": "Sydney",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0006232133604999999
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The CEO of Apple, Tim Cook, announces the release of a new line of iPhones.",
    "span": "Apple",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.15239010389500002
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The CEO of Apple, Tim Cook, announces the release of a new line of iPhones.",
    "span": "Tim Cook",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0019939280791000003
  },
  {
    "sentence": "A fire broke out in a residential building in downtown Los Angeles, forcing the evacuation of hundreds of residents.",
    "span": "Los Angeles",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -7.87466244e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The United Nations issued a statement condemning the recent acts of aggression by North Korea.",
    "span": "United Nations",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -8.693463904000001e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The United Nations issued a statement condemning the recent acts of aggression by North Korea.",
    "span": "North Korea",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -9.077299706e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The famous actress will be hosting a charity event to raise funds for a children's hospital.",
    "span": "actress",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.05374226224999999
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The United Nations reported a sharp increase in humanitarian aid to the war-torn region.",
    "span": "United Nations",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0002035583746
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX successfully lands Starship prototype.",
    "span": "Elon Musk",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.00011233644571666665
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX successfully lands Starship prototype.",
    "span": "SpaceX",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.10658966950175
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX successfully lands Starship prototype.",
    "span": "Starship",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.017744977633
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Stocks rally as Apple surpasses revenue expectations.",
    "span": "Apple",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00281737815275
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tesla announces plans to build new gigafactory in Texas.",
    "span": "Tesla",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00017888311675
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tesla announces plans to build new gigafactory in Texas.",
    "span": "Texas",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.008102012264
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Los Angeles Lakers trade star player to New York Knicks.",
    "span": "Los Angeles Lakers",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0009237219721333335
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Los Angeles Lakers trade star player to New York Knicks.",
    "span": "New York Knicks",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.004264808250333333
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tennis champion Serena Williams advances to the finals of Wimbledon.",
    "span": "Serena Williams",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.00010943337991666667
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tennis champion Serena Williams advances to the finals of Wimbledon.",
    "span": "Wimbledon",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00016842896365
  },
  {
    "sentence": "President Biden announces infrastructure plan to address aging roads and bridges.",
    "span": "President Biden",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0018480781016
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The CEO of Google announced a new initiative to combat online misinformation.",
    "span": "Google",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0329075813775
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The United Nations Security Council held an emergency meeting to discuss the crisis in Syria.",
    "span": "United Nations",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0006129681842
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Pop star Taylor Swift is set to release her highly anticipated new album next month.",
    "span": "Taylor Swift",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -3.707522620000001e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "United Nations report warns of potential food crisis in Africa.",
    "span": "United Nations",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -1.020672044e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "United Nations report warns of potential food crisis in Africa.",
    "span": "Africa",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.000536984836725
  },
  {
    "sentence": "California governor signs new climate change legislation.",
    "span": "California",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.010875929211749999
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Famous actress Jennifer Lawrence to star in upcoming thriller film.",
    "span": "Jennifer Lawrence",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.00039676627226000003
  },
  {
    "sentence": "New York City braces for potential subway strike.",
    "span": "New York City",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.016716069977166667
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Apple Inc. announces the release of their new iPhone model.",
    "span": "Apple Inc.",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0034471425036666664
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX company successfully launches another batch of Starlink satellites.",
    "span": "Elon Musk",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -2.1034386599999998e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX company successfully launches another batch of Starlink satellites.",
    "span": "SpaceX",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.051775820334375
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tesla surpasses $1 trillion market value.",
    "span": "Tesla",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00832238516075
  },
  {
    "sentence": "President Biden delivers speech on economy and infrastructure in New York City.",
    "span": "Biden",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.3350553624932
  },
  {
    "sentence": "President Biden delivers speech on economy and infrastructure in New York City.",
    "span": "New York City",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00017835388750000002
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Hurricane Elsa makes landfall in Florida, causing widespread power outages.",
    "span": "Elsa",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.022263997790800003
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Hurricane Elsa makes landfall in Florida, causing widespread power outages.",
    "span": "Florida",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -6.1074134625e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Japan experiences record-breaking heatwave.",
    "span": "Japan",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.000582102425
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Paris Hilton announces engagement to Carter Reum.",
    "span": "Paris Hilton",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -2.11734581e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Paris Hilton announces engagement to Carter Reum.",
    "span": "Carter Reum",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0001225528185
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The United Nations condemns human rights abuses in Myanmar.",
    "span": "United Nations",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.004438123866220001
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The United Nations condemns human rights abuses in Myanmar.",
    "span": "Myanmar",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -8.589554640000001e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "JFK Airport in New York City to undergo major renovation.",
    "span": "JFK Airport",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -8.211893166666667e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "JFK Airport in New York City to undergo major renovation.",
    "span": "New York City",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00013053884699999998
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Amazon announces plans to open new fulfillment center in Texas.",
    "span": "Amazon",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -7.70185395e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Amazon announces plans to open new fulfillment center in Texas.",
    "span": "Texas",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00415090802
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Thousands gather in Times Square to ring in the New Year.",
    "span": "Times Square",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0006047988089999999
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX successfully launches crewed mission to International Space Station.",
    "span": "Elon Musk",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0008917521409333335
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX successfully launches crewed mission to International Space Station.",
    "span": "SpaceX",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -2.7550853499999997e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "China imposes new tariffs on imported American goods.",
    "span": "China",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.02370331134575
  },
  {
    "sentence": "China imposes new tariffs on imported American goods.",
    "span": "American",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.003610087675
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Serena Williams advances to the quarterfinals of the French Open.",
    "span": "Serena Williams",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -2.5087310483333334e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX successfully launches new batch of Starlink satellites.",
    "span": "Elon Musk",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.00042702384116666666
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX successfully launches new batch of Starlink satellites.",
    "span": "SpaceX",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.1408311412105
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX successfully launches new batch of Starlink satellites.",
    "span": "Starlink",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.760957274521
  },
  {
    "sentence": "New York City Mayor announces plan to address homelessness crisis.",
    "span": "New York City",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.02257667041733333
  },
  {
    "sentence": "New York City Mayor announces plan to address homelessness crisis.",
    "span": "Mayor",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.321998755211
  },
  {
    "sentence": "NASA announces plans for new mission to Mars.",
    "span": "NASA",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00035737000499999996
  },
  {
    "sentence": "NASA announces plans for new mission to Mars.",
    "span": "Mars",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.011861976372250001
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tech giant Apple unveils new iPhone with 5G capability.",
    "span": "Apple",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.244606089338575
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Former president Barack Obama to release new memoir.",
    "span": "Barack Obama",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -8.452226038333335e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The United Nations releases new report on global poverty rate.",
    "span": "United Nations",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.036882494092
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX launches satellite into orbit.",
    "span": "Elon Musk",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -4.0542831133333325e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Paris fashion week kicks off with dazzling runway shows.",
    "span": "Paris",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -4.0037437e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The CEO of Apple announces the launch of a new iPhone.",
    "span": "CEO",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0412862891075
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The CEO of Apple announces the launch of a new iPhone.",
    "span": "Apple",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.22270738935
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The United Nations report highlights the growing concerns over climate change.",
    "span": "United Nations",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0004496241921
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The mayor of London introduces new measures to tackle air pollution.",
    "span": "mayor",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.00069257582825
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The mayor of London introduces new measures to tackle air pollution.",
    "span": "London",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0015521492382999998
  },
  {
    "sentence": "CALIFORNIA WILDFIRES LEAD TO EVACUATIONS IN NAPA VALLEY.",
    "span": "CALIFORNIA",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -9.121439222857144e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "CALIFORNIA WILDFIRES LEAD TO EVACUATIONS IN NAPA VALLEY.",
    "span": "NAPA VALLEY",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00013758593395714287
  },
  {
    "sentence": "GOOGLE CEO MAKES ANNOUNCEMENT ABOUT COMPANY'S NEW TECHNOLOGY.",
    "span": "GOOGLE",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.006182407919799999
  },
  {
    "sentence": "GOOGLE CEO MAKES ANNOUNCEMENT ABOUT COMPANY'S NEW TECHNOLOGY.",
    "span": "CEO",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0031359746025
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tesla announces plans to build new factory in Texas.",
    "span": "Tesla",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.000116319525
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tesla announces plans to build new factory in Texas.",
    "span": "Texas",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00895930773925
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The Prime Minister of Japan's visit to the United States will focus on trade and security discussions.",
    "span": "Prime Minister of Japan",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0011762587984714284
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The Prime Minister of Japan's visit to the United States will focus on trade and security discussions.",
    "span": "United States",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0001782097994
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Apple Inc. reports record-breaking profits for the third quarter.",
    "span": "Apple Inc.",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0011448048509916668
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Apple Inc. announces new iPhone release date.",
    "span": "Apple Inc.",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.044377517129716666
  },
  {
    "sentence": "London mayor unveils new public transportation plan.",
    "span": "London",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0007132592245
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Taylor Swift wins Grammy for Album of the Year.",
    "span": "Taylor Swift",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0393753835828
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Taylor Swift wins Grammy for Album of the Year.",
    "span": "Grammy",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.000543385935
  },
  {
    "sentence": "President Biden visits European Union headquarters in Brussels to discuss climate change initiatives.",
    "span": "President Biden",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0018626606064
  },
  {
    "sentence": "President Biden visits European Union headquarters in Brussels to discuss climate change initiatives.",
    "span": "European Union",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00061629521902
  },
  {
    "sentence": "President Biden visits European Union headquarters in Brussels to discuss climate change initiatives.",
    "span": "Brussels",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.046474250960625
  },
  {
    "sentence": "SpaceX launches satellite into orbit to expand global internet coverage.",
    "span": "SpaceX",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00057105250682
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX launches new batch of Starlink satellites.",
    "span": "Elon Musk",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0006941674676666667
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX launches new batch of Starlink satellites.",
    "span": "SpaceX",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.048811141199499995
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX launches new batch of Starlink satellites.",
    "span": "Starlink",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.008479407653199999
  },
  {
    "sentence": "United States imposes new sanctions on North Korea.",
    "span": "United States",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0041014708626
  },
  {
    "sentence": "United States imposes new sanctions on North Korea.",
    "span": "North Korea",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0001552713496
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Taylor Swift's new album breaks streaming records.",
    "span": "Taylor Swift",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -5.6694684e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tesla's CEO, Elon Musk, unveils plans for new electric car model.",
    "span": "Tesla",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0031296697244999998
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tesla's CEO, Elon Musk, unveils plans for new electric car model.",
    "span": "Elon Musk",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0059456731421999994
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The United Nations issues a statement condemning the recent human rights abuses in Myanmar.",
    "span": "United Nations",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0026581168579199997
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The United Nations issues a statement condemning the recent human rights abuses in Myanmar.",
    "span": "Myanmar",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00023699353874999997
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Apple announces the launch of its new iPhone 13 series.",
    "span": "Apple",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.1210451678085
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Apple announces record-breaking sales for the latest iPhone model.",
    "span": "Apple",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.217176239455
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The hurricane caused extensive damage to the coastal town of Wilmington, North Carolina.",
    "span": "Wilmington",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0009803432674
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The hurricane caused extensive damage to the coastal town of Wilmington, North Carolina.",
    "span": "North Carolina",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0002882641472
  },
  {
    "sentence": "NASA's Mars rover discovers evidence of ancient life on the red planet.",
    "span": "NASA",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.03395655794215
  },
  {
    "sentence": "NASA's Mars rover discovers evidence of ancient life on the red planet.",
    "span": "Mars",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -4.6263994574999995e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tesla CEO Elon Musk unveils new electric car model.",
    "span": "Tesla",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0012549681275000001
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tesla CEO Elon Musk unveils new electric car model.",
    "span": "Elon Musk",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0062395094402000004
  },
  {
    "sentence": "China launches new satellite into space.",
    "span": "China",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.000108872050125
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Microsoft announces acquisition of cybersecurity company.",
    "span": "Microsoft",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0003070936005
  },
  {
    "sentence": "COVID-19 cases surge in New York City, prompting new restrictions.",
    "span": "New York City",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.004652804773716666
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Apple announces plan to open new headquarters in Austin, Texas.",
    "span": "Apple",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -1.1696765575e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Apple announces plan to open new headquarters in Austin, Texas.",
    "span": "Austin",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.010328360714875
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Apple announces plan to open new headquarters in Austin, Texas.",
    "span": "Texas",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0003580774759
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Apple Inc. announces record-breaking sales for the new iPhone model.",
    "span": "Apple Inc.",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.037773534325666665
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Jessica Smith appointed as the new CEO of the technology company.",
    "span": "Jessica Smith",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0015867565667
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Wildfires continue to devastate the state of California, prompting mass evacuations.",
    "span": "California",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -7.969970475e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tesla announces plans to open a new manufacturing facility in Austin, Texas.",
    "span": "Tesla",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -8.05034125e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tesla announces plans to open a new manufacturing facility in Austin, Texas.",
    "span": "Austin, Texas",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00023023834
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Greta Thunberg delivers impassioned speech at climate change rally in New York City.",
    "span": "Greta Thunberg",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -1.6360609737499998e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Greta Thunberg delivers impassioned speech at climate change rally in New York City.",
    "span": "New York City",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0001088083265
  },
  {
    "sentence": "World Health Organization issues new guidelines for vaccination distribution in developing countries.",
    "span": "World Health Organization",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00098224503175
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Apple announces new iPhone launch event.",
    "span": "Apple",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.22954574691675
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Los Angeles Lakers sign new head coach.",
    "span": "Los Angeles",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.3277690777372
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Los Angeles Lakers sign new head coach.",
    "span": "Lakers",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00033985763099999997
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Renowned scientist Dr. Jane Smith wins Nobel Prize in Physics.",
    "span": "Dr. Jane Smith",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.04402811813232858
  },
  {
    "sentence": "New York City imposes new restrictions on large gatherings.",
    "span": "New York City",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -7.643688783333333e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Amazon CEO Jeff Bezos steps down from role.",
    "span": "Amazon",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00024360064329999998
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Amazon CEO Jeff Bezos steps down from role.",
    "span": "Jeff Bezos",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -4.296602743333333e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "New York City mayor announces plan to increase funding for public schools.",
    "span": "New York City",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -7.29359727e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Apple announces new iPhone with 5G capability.",
    "span": "Apple",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.07266422236775001
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Apple announces new iPhone with 5G capability.",
    "span": "iPhone",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0735959164865
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tesla's CEO Elon Musk unveils new electric car model.",
    "span": "Tesla",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00335939720625
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tesla's CEO Elon Musk unveils new electric car model.",
    "span": "Elon Musk",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0069026475462
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Strong earthquake hits Tokyo, causing widespread damage.",
    "span": "Tokyo",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -9.144713814e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Apple Inc. announces plans to open new headquarters in Austin, Texas.",
    "span": "Apple Inc.",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -5.843774743999999e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Apple Inc. announces plans to open new headquarters in Austin, Texas.",
    "span": "Austin",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0010917463093249999
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Apple Inc. announces plans to open new headquarters in Austin, Texas.",
    "span": "Texas",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00024237605550000003
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tech giant Apple announces the release of the new iPhone 13.",
    "span": "Apple",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.4819321482215
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Prime Minister Trudeau unveils new climate policy.",
    "span": "Trudeau",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0057561243216
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Hurricane Ida hit Louisiana with devastating force.",
    "span": "Hurricane Ida",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.42317066718680013
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Hurricane Ida hit Louisiana with devastating force.",
    "span": "Louisiana",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.2225284238519
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tesla reports record-breaking quarterly profits.",
    "span": "Tesla",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.014366245284
  },
  {
    "sentence": "New York City Mayor announces plan to invest in public transportation.",
    "span": "New York City",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0071387481696666664
  },
  {
    "sentence": "New York City Mayor announces plan to invest in public transportation.",
    "span": "Mayor",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0003609108025
  },
  {
    "sentence": "World Health Organization warns of new COVID-19 variant.",
    "span": "World Health Organization",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.004336639691333333
  },
  {
    "sentence": "World Health Organization warns of new COVID-19 variant.",
    "span": "COVID-19",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.009918782810333333
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Apple announces new iPhone 12 release date.",
    "span": "Apple",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.16735594617424998
  },
  {
    "sentence": "President Biden unveils $2 trillion infrastructure plan.",
    "span": "President Biden",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0164499531876
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Wildfire threatens homes in Los Angeles.",
    "span": "Los Angeles",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0011947251364
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tesla announces record-breaking quarterly earnings.",
    "span": "Tesla",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.008161179565
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The CEO of Amazon plans to step down next year.",
    "span": "CEO of Amazon",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.1673793127745
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tokyo Olympics organizers unveil COVID-19 guidelines for athletes and officials.",
    "span": "Tokyo",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.05720845528388001
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tokyo Olympics organizers unveil COVID-19 guidelines for athletes and officials.",
    "span": "Olympics organizers",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.01075185715002
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tensions rise as China announces new military exercises in the South China Sea.",
    "span": "China",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.15452382954825
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tensions rise as China announces new military exercises in the South China Sea.",
    "span": "South China Sea",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0012833888340833333
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Amazon revamps its Prime Day strategy to boost sales amid increasing competition from other e-commerce giants.",
    "span": "Amazon",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.051242715768075
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Amazon revamps its Prime Day strategy to boost sales amid increasing competition from other e-commerce giants.",
    "span": "Prime Day",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0036619853936000002
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tesla announces plans to build new Gigafactory in Texas.",
    "span": "Tesla",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -4.1289077e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tesla announces plans to build new Gigafactory in Texas.",
    "span": "Texas",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.009901369285
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Prime Minister Johnson meets with President Macron to discuss trade agreement.",
    "span": "Prime Minister Johnson",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0018960615265666669
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Prime Minister Johnson meets with President Macron to discuss trade agreement.",
    "span": "President Macron",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.00015817551706
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Apple unveils new iPhone with innovative features.",
    "span": "Apple",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.13289761399935
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Apple unveils new iPhone with innovative features.",
    "span": "iPhone",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -1.987148154774
  },
  {
    "sentence": "President Biden signs new infrastructure bill into law.",
    "span": "President Biden",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.07212350740519999
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Apple Inc. unveils new iPhone model at tech conference.",
    "span": "Apple Inc.",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0005480326965
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Wildfires continue to devastate California.",
    "span": "California",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.000174686687
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX successfully launches new batch of Starlink satellites into orbit.",
    "span": "Elon Musk",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0004029471533333333
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX successfully launches new batch of Starlink satellites into orbit.",
    "span": "SpaceX",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.072927090843
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX successfully launches new batch of Starlink satellites into orbit.",
    "span": "Starlink",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0049188591939999995
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tensions rise between Russia and Ukraine over disputed territory in the Black Sea.",
    "span": "Russia",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -5.34180495e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tensions rise between Russia and Ukraine over disputed territory in the Black Sea.",
    "span": "Ukraine",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -3.5448095575e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tensions rise between Russia and Ukraine over disputed territory in the Black Sea.",
    "span": "Black Sea",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0001352106574
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Apple unveils new iPhone model with enhanced camera features at annual product launch event.",
    "span": "Apple",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0049356683545
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Apple unveils new iPhone model with enhanced camera features at annual product launch event.",
    "span": "iPhone",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00458598089775
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Dr. Anthony Fauci warns of potential fourth COVID-19 wave in the US.",
    "span": "Dr. Anthony Fauci",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.009013325168
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Dr. Anthony Fauci warns of potential fourth COVID-19 wave in the US.",
    "span": "US",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00034272585385000003
  },
  {
    "sentence": "European Union announces plans to increase renewable energy targets by 2030.",
    "span": "European Union",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -4.9803974520000006e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tropical storm hits Florida coast.",
    "span": "Florida",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.001670172337
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Apple launches new iPhone with advanced camera features.",
    "span": "Apple",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.176119099665
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Earthquake strikes near Tokyo, Japan.",
    "span": "Tokyo",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00066990267652
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Earthquake strikes near Tokyo, Japan.",
    "span": "Japan",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.000126530241425
  },
  {
    "sentence": "LeBron James signs $154 million contract with Lakers.",
    "span": "LeBron James",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -7.318354421666668e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "LeBron James signs $154 million contract with Lakers.",
    "span": "Lakers",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00266234566025
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Heavy rains expected to hit Florida this weekend.",
    "span": "Florida",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0005750419945
  },
  {
    "sentence": "APPLE ANNOUNCES NEW IPHONE RELEASE DATE.",
    "span": "APPLE",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.048826595614999996
  },
  {
    "sentence": "APPLE ANNOUNCES NEW IPHONE RELEASE DATE.",
    "span": "IPHONE",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.07319739376066
  },
  {
    "sentence": "TEXAS GOVERNOR SIGNS BILL TO RESTRICT VOTING RIGHTS.",
    "span": "TEXAS",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.010409115478
  },
  {
    "sentence": "EUROPEAN UNION IMPOSES SANCTIONS ON RUSSIA OVER UKRAINE CRISIS.",
    "span": "EUROPEAN UNION",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -4.8662969375e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "EUROPEAN UNION IMPOSES SANCTIONS ON RUSSIA OVER UKRAINE CRISIS.",
    "span": "RUSSIA",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -7.33605165e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "EUROPEAN UNION IMPOSES SANCTIONS ON RUSSIA OVER UKRAINE CRISIS.",
    "span": "UKRAINE",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0001531300811
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tesla CEO Elon Musk invests in new space exploration technology.",
    "span": "Tesla",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.012280126990000001
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tesla CEO Elon Musk invests in new space exploration technology.",
    "span": "Elon Musk",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0286369678555
  },
  {
    "sentence": "World Health Organization warns of potential outbreak in Africa.",
    "span": "World Health Organization",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -3.2219663333333334e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "World Health Organization warns of potential outbreak in Africa.",
    "span": "Africa",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.000127245457
  },
  {
    "sentence": "United Nations peacekeeping forces patrol the border between Rwanda and Congo.",
    "span": "United Nations",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -1.30437677e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "United Nations peacekeeping forces patrol the border between Rwanda and Congo.",
    "span": "Rwanda",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -4.2481111749999996e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "United Nations peacekeeping forces patrol the border between Rwanda and Congo.",
    "span": "Congo",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00017999447312499998
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Apple Inc. announces new iPhone with advanced camera technology.",
    "span": "Apple Inc.",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.08249563236560833
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The United States imposes new tariffs on Chinese imports, sparking trade tensions.",
    "span": "United States",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0402482351532
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The United States imposes new tariffs on Chinese imports, sparking trade tensions.",
    "span": "Chinese",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0177347185875
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Entrepreneur Elizabeth Holmes faces criminal charges for her role in fraud scandal at Theranos.",
    "span": "Elizabeth Holmes",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.00023058606370000005
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Entrepreneur Elizabeth Holmes faces criminal charges for her role in fraud scandal at Theranos.",
    "span": "Theranos",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00016466496374
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Wildfires continue to ravage large parts of Australia, forcing mass evacuations.",
    "span": "Australia",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.000121533773
  },
  {
    "sentence": "California wildfires force thousands to evacuate.",
    "span": "California",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00021619019175000002
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tesla announces plans for new electric vehicle factory.",
    "span": "Tesla",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00174652806191
  },
  {
    "sentence": "California Governor Newsom announces new COVID-19 restrictions.",
    "span": "California",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0004980500575
  },
  {
    "sentence": "California Governor Newsom announces new COVID-19 restrictions.",
    "span": "Newsom",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.032573458117000006
  },
  {
    "sentence": "New York City announces plans to build affordable housing developments in Brooklyn and Queens.",
    "span": "New York City",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -3.65693746e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "New York City announces plans to build affordable housing developments in Brooklyn and Queens.",
    "span": "Brooklyn",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -7.9120497e-06
  },
  {
    "sentence": "New York City announces plans to build affordable housing developments in Brooklyn and Queens.",
    "span": "Queens",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0001075553115
  },
  {
    "sentence": "New York City plans to implement a congestion pricing program to reduce traffic in the city center.",
    "span": "New York City",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -6.14016371e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The World Health Organization warns of a new strain of flu virus spreading rapidly in Asia.",
    "span": "World Health Organization",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0002586929285
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The World Health Organization warns of a new strain of flu virus spreading rapidly in Asia.",
    "span": "Asia",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.000215994894
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tesla's CEO, Elon Musk, announces plans to build a new Gigafactory in Texas.",
    "span": "Tesla",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.027811948384499997
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tesla's CEO, Elon Musk, announces plans to build a new Gigafactory in Texas.",
    "span": "Elon Musk",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.00010586638506
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tesla's CEO, Elon Musk, announces plans to build a new Gigafactory in Texas.",
    "span": "Texas",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0011262574825
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The United Nations urges all parties involved in the conflict to seek a peaceful resolution.",
    "span": "United Nations",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0049840918903199995
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Pop superstar Taylor Swift to release new album next month.",
    "span": "Taylor Swift",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -2.973228066e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tesla announces plans to build a new gigafactory in Texas.",
    "span": "Tesla",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00011000264887499999
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tesla announces plans to build a new gigafactory in Texas.",
    "span": "Texas",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0049985626945
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Angela Merkel elected as new President of European Commission.",
    "span": "Angela Merkel",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.00029380451628333335
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Angela Merkel elected as new President of European Commission.",
    "span": "European Commission",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0014762280375400002
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Stocks soar as Apple reports record-breaking quarterly earnings.",
    "span": "Apple",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00055426158575
  },
  {
    "sentence": "New York City's mayor announces plans to increase affordable housing options.",
    "span": "New York City",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.046831792558999996
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Apple Inc. reports record-breaking sales for the latest iPhone model.",
    "span": "Apple Inc.",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.13076133802423334
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Renowned actress Emma Watson to star in upcoming thriller film.",
    "span": "Emma Watson",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.00021838330273999998
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tesla announces plans to open new Gigafactory in Texas.",
    "span": "Tesla",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.000201434165
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tesla announces plans to open new Gigafactory in Texas.",
    "span": "Texas",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.011831853595
  },
  {
    "sentence": "NASA launches new mission to explore Mars.",
    "span": "NASA",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -8.92528105e-06
  },
  {
    "sentence": "NASA launches new mission to explore Mars.",
    "span": "Mars",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -5.4219923050000005e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tesla Inc. announces plans to open a new factory in Texas next year.",
    "span": "Tesla Inc.",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0003315413360666667
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tesla Inc. announces plans to open a new factory in Texas next year.",
    "span": "Texas",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00358156979175
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Taylor Swift releases a new album titled 'Red (Taylor's Version).'",
    "span": "Taylor Swift",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0007740532486
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Researchers discover ancient ruins in Greece dating back to the Mycenaean civilization.",
    "span": "Greece",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00024196872791999998
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Researchers discover ancient ruins in Greece dating back to the Mycenaean civilization.",
    "span": "Mycenaean civilization",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0023397170784112504
  },
  {
    "sentence": "President Biden visits Texas to survey storm damage.",
    "span": "President Biden",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0016638296737999994
  },
  {
    "sentence": "President Biden visits Texas to survey storm damage.",
    "span": "Texas",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00042320940500000003
  },
  {
    "sentence": "NASA announces upcoming Mars mission.",
    "span": "NASA",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -2.7610455750000003e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "NASA announces upcoming Mars mission.",
    "span": "Mars",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -2.0726444499999997e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Hollywood actors protest against the construction of a new oil pipeline.",
    "span": "Hollywood",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0421489715784
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Amazon announces new delivery drone technology.",
    "span": "Amazon",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.000110771058425
  },
  {
    "sentence": "John Smith elected as the new chairman of the board.",
    "span": "John Smith",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0015283072787999998
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Prime Minister Trudeau visits United Nations headquarters.",
    "span": "Trudeau",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.41407677132133003
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Prime Minister Trudeau visits United Nations headquarters.",
    "span": "United Nations",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0031255972912
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Hurricane Maria hits Puerto Rico.",
    "span": "Hurricane Maria",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.06210444849650001
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Hurricane Maria hits Puerto Rico.",
    "span": "Puerto Rico",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0001971206486
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tech giant Apple announces record-breaking quarterly profits.",
    "span": "Apple",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0023416543027500003
  },
  {
    "sentence": "New York City Mayor declares state of emergency following severe weather.",
    "span": "New York City",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0006922770084166666
  },
  {
    "sentence": "New York City Mayor declares state of emergency following severe weather.",
    "span": "Mayor",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.00046134544099999997
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Global environmental organization Greenpeace launches new campaign to protect endangered species.",
    "span": "Greenpeace",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0028244263693200005
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tech giant Apple unveils new product line.",
    "span": "Apple",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.72476963409325
  },
  {
    "sentence": "New York City Mayor announces public transportation improvements.",
    "span": "New York City",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0090553710655
  },
  {
    "sentence": "New York City Mayor announces public transportation improvements.",
    "span": "Mayor",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0004201101125
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Environmental organization Greenpeace protests outside oil company headquarters.",
    "span": "Greenpeace",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.021855528907720002
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Apple to release new iPhone model next month.",
    "span": "Apple",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.21214941426199999
  },
  {
    "sentence": "CEO of Google, Sundar Pichai, speaks at tech conference.",
    "span": "Google",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.006478747729
  },
  {
    "sentence": "CEO of Google, Sundar Pichai, speaks at tech conference.",
    "span": "Sundar Pichai",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -7.90800774125e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Hurricane Maria devastates Puerto Rico, leaving thousands without power or water.",
    "span": "Hurricane Maria",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.008936893040833335
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Hurricane Maria devastates Puerto Rico, leaving thousands without power or water.",
    "span": "Puerto Rico",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00011496326840000001
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX launches new batch of Starlink satellites",
    "span": "Elon Musk",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.00015914650216666666
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX launches new batch of Starlink satellites",
    "span": "SpaceX",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.01360184033725
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX launches new batch of Starlink satellites",
    "span": "Starlink",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.004393867614000001
  },
  {
    "sentence": "New York City mayoral candidate proposes affordable housing plan",
    "span": "New York City",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -9.859960243333332e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Pfizer and Moderna announce plans for COVID-19 vaccine booster shots",
    "span": "Pfizer",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -5.239901133333333e-06
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Pfizer and Moderna announce plans for COVID-19 vaccine booster shots",
    "span": "Moderna",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.014436889717999998
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Pfizer and Moderna announce plans for COVID-19 vaccine booster shots",
    "span": "COVID-19",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0018492094508666668
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Dr. Anthony Fauci warns of potential COVID-19 surge in the fall.",
    "span": "Dr. Anthony Fauci",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.028844773074250003
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tesla announces plans to open new gigafactory in Germany.",
    "span": "Tesla",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -6.941838975e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tesla announces plans to open new gigafactory in Germany.",
    "span": "Germany",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.007102088313
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Famous actor to star in upcoming Marvel movie.",
    "span": "Marvel",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00613034083185
  },
  {
    "sentence": "United Nations to discuss climate change at upcoming summit in Paris.",
    "span": "United Nations",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -1.3902034100000003e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "United Nations to discuss climate change at upcoming summit in Paris.",
    "span": "Paris",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.000134943266
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Apple reaches $2 trillion market cap.",
    "span": "Apple",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0001169334291625
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Paris prepares for the annual Bastille Day celebrations.",
    "span": "Paris",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0030117542605
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Paris prepares for the annual Bastille Day celebrations.",
    "span": "Bastille Day",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.059273022842000006
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Doctors Without Borders provides aid to refugees in war-torn region.",
    "span": "Doctors Without Borders",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -7.987026254999999e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Elon Musk plans to send humans to Mars by 2026.",
    "span": "Elon Musk",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0024965251646666665
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Elon Musk plans to send humans to Mars by 2026.",
    "span": "Mars",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0184372006515
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Google opens new artificial intelligence research lab in London.",
    "span": "Google",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -2.03986342e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Google opens new artificial intelligence research lab in London.",
    "span": "London",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00023587439375
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Angela Merkel reelected as Chancellor of Germany for fourth term.",
    "span": "Angela Merkel",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -8.696807183333333e-06
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Angela Merkel reelected as Chancellor of Germany for fourth term.",
    "span": "Germany",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00019744588075
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX launches communication satellite into space.",
    "span": "Elon Musk",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.00010902044150000001
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX launches communication satellite into space.",
    "span": "SpaceX",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.01249615994075
  },
  {
    "sentence": "New York City Mayor announces new affordable housing initiative.",
    "span": "New York City",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.4683530834308334
  },
  {
    "sentence": "New York City Mayor announces new affordable housing initiative.",
    "span": "Mayor",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.045135431427500004
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Apple Inc. unveils latest iPhone model with advanced camera technology.",
    "span": "Apple Inc.",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.012796652740941666
  },
  {
    "sentence": "China imposes new restrictions on tech giant Alibaba's financial affiliate Ant Group.",
    "span": "China",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -6.906169725e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "China imposes new restrictions on tech giant Alibaba's financial affiliate Ant Group.",
    "span": "Alibaba",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -5.1628161e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "China imposes new restrictions on tech giant Alibaba's financial affiliate Ant Group.",
    "span": "Ant Group",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00012649558239999999
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Associated Press journalist Kim Ng becomes first female general manager in MLB history.",
    "span": "Associated Press",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00017888321568
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Associated Press journalist Kim Ng becomes first female general manager in MLB history.",
    "span": "Kim Ng",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -9.783131779999999e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Associated Press journalist Kim Ng becomes first female general manager in MLB history.",
    "span": "MLB",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -3.5835507575e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Explosion in downtown New York injures several people.",
    "span": "New York",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00012958423654
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Apple's CEO Tim Cook unveils new iPhone model.",
    "span": "Apple",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -8.5982195675e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Apple's CEO Tim Cook unveils new iPhone model.",
    "span": "Tim Cook",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.00537635040804
  },
  {
    "sentence": "APPLE UNVEILS NEW iPHONE WITH 5G CAPABILITIES.",
    "span": "APPLE",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.07822437605499999
  },
  {
    "sentence": "TOKYO OLYMPICS TO ALLOW LIMITED SPECTATORS AMID COVID-19 CONCERNS.",
    "span": "TOKYO",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.5687169329378333
  },
  {
    "sentence": "President Biden meets with South Korean leader to discuss trade agreements.",
    "span": "President Biden",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.014179399407800001
  },
  {
    "sentence": "President Biden meets with South Korean leader to discuss trade agreements.",
    "span": "South Korean",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.34107752413299997
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Wildfires continue to ravage California, prompting mass evacuations.",
    "span": "California",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00019407517375
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Earthquake hits southern California, causing power outages and minor damage.",
    "span": "southern California",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0796586191496143
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Amazon employees plan to unionize for better working conditions.",
    "span": "Amazon",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.005528136290825
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tesla announces plans to open new manufacturing plant in Berlin.",
    "span": "Tesla",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -8.339410224999999e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tesla announces plans to open new manufacturing plant in Berlin.",
    "span": "Berlin",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.006275593506499999
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Prime Minister Johnson delivers address on climate change at summit.",
    "span": "Prime Minister Johnson",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.04214820781016665
  },
  {
    "sentence": "New York Mets pitcher Jacob deGrom wins Cy Young Award.",
    "span": "New York Mets",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0002214121153333334
  },
  {
    "sentence": "New York Mets pitcher Jacob deGrom wins Cy Young Award.",
    "span": "Jacob deGrom",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.02932404750924286
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX plans to send civilians on a mission to the moon.",
    "span": "Elon Musk",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -5.425125166666667e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX plans to send civilians on a mission to the moon.",
    "span": "SpaceX",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.009337779920249999
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX plans to send civilians on a mission to the moon.",
    "span": "moon",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00897516961
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Foreign investors pour billions into tech startups in Silicon Valley.",
    "span": "Silicon Valley",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0031969986024999995
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Former President Barack Obama to deliver keynote address at climate change conference.",
    "span": "Barack Obama",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0017690823952000003
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX launches a Falcon 9 rocket into orbit.",
    "span": "Elon Musk",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -3.7663297283333335e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX launches a Falcon 9 rocket into orbit.",
    "span": "SpaceX",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.025793033773875
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Paris, France, announces new measures to combat air pollution.",
    "span": "Paris",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00911977505775
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Paris, France, announces new measures to combat air pollution.",
    "span": "France",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0001648179945
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Apple unveils the latest iPhone model at its annual product launch event.",
    "span": "Apple",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.01286926995625
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Severe weather advisory for residents of New York City.",
    "span": "New York City",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00010831775633333334
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Apple announces new product launch event.",
    "span": "Apple",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -6.44109185e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tesla's CEO, Elon Musk, announces plans for new electric vehicle.",
    "span": "Tesla",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0028218276575
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tesla's CEO, Elon Musk, announces plans for new electric vehicle.",
    "span": "Elon Musk",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.004619131216
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Pfizer's COVID-19 vaccine found to be 95% effective in final analysis.",
    "span": "Pfizer",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0004431640842
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Biden visits European Union headquarters to discuss climate change policies.",
    "span": "Biden",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -9.208936980000001e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Biden visits European Union headquarters to discuss climate change policies.",
    "span": "European Union",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0006428009212
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tesla stock surges after announcing record production numbers.",
    "span": "Tesla",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.010347963441
  },
  {
    "sentence": "London Mayor announces plan to reduce air pollution in the city center.",
    "span": "London",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.394884625798
  },
  {
    "sentence": "London Mayor announces plan to reduce air pollution in the city center.",
    "span": "Mayor",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.00087416434
  },
  {
    "sentence": "World Health Organization warns of potential new strain of flu virus.",
    "span": "World Health Organization",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0003313151799166667
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Apple Inc. announces the launch of its new iPhone 13 series.",
    "span": "Apple Inc.",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.15822248018898336
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The president of France, Emmanuel Macron, visits the United States for trade discussions.",
    "span": "Emmanuel Macron",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.2935914238121067
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The president of France, Emmanuel Macron, visits the United States for trade discussions.",
    "span": "United States",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.10277825492099998
  },
  {
