{"sentence": "The European Union is considering imposing tariffs on American products.", "tokens": ["The", "European", "Union", "is", "considering", "imposing", "tariffs", "on", "American", "products", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX successfully launches another batch of Starlink satellites.", "tokens": ["Elon", "Musk", "'", "s", "SpaceX", "successfully", "launches", "another", "batch", "of", "Starlink", "satellites", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The protests in Hong Kong continue to escalate as tensions rise between the government and demonstrators.", "tokens": ["The", "protests", "in", "Hong", "Kong", "continue", "to", "escalate", "as", "tensions", "rise", "between", "the", "government", "and", "demonstrators", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The World Health Organization warns of a potential Ebola outbreak in the Democratic Republic of Congo.", "tokens": ["The", "World", "Health", "Organization", "warns", "of", "a", "potential", "Ebola", "outbreak", "in", "the", "Democratic", "Republic", "of", "Congo", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Amazon announces plans to open a new fulfillment center, creating 2,000 jobs in the local community.", "tokens": ["Amazon", "announces", "plans", "to", "open", "a", "new", "fulfillment", "center", ",", "creating", "2", ",", "000", "jobs", "in", "the", "local", "community", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Taylor Swift releases her highly anticipated album, \"Fearless (Taylor's Version).\"", "tokens": ["Taylor", "Swift", "releases", "her", "highly", "anticipated", "album", ",", "\"", "Fearless", "(", "Taylor", "'", "s", "Version", ")", ".", "\""], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The United Nations urges immediate action to address the humanitarian crisis in Yemen.", "tokens": ["The", "United", "Nations", "urges", "immediate", "action", "to", "address", "the", "humanitarian", "crisis", "in", "Yemen", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The Los Angeles Lakers defeat the Brooklyn Nets in a thrilling overtime game.", "tokens": ["The", "Los", "Angeles", "Lakers", "defeat", "the", "Brooklyn", "Nets", "in", "a", "thrilling", "overtime", "game", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "President Joe Biden signs an executive order to address climate change and promote clean energy.", "tokens": ["President", "Joe", "Biden", "signs", "an", "executive", "order", "to", "address", "climate", "change", "and", "promote", "clean", "energy", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The Tokyo Olympics are facing uncertainty as concerns over the COVID-19 pandemic persist.", "tokens": ["The", "Tokyo", "Olympics", "are", "facing", "uncertainty", "as", "concerns", "over", "the", "COVID", "-", "19", "pandemic", "persist", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-location", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "TikTok faces scrutiny over data privacy concerns and potential national security risks.", "tokens": ["TikTok", "faces", "scrutiny", "over", "data", "privacy", "concerns", "and", "potential", "national", "security", "risks", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Meghan Markle and Prince Harry announce their decision to step back from their royal duties.", "tokens": ["Meghan", "Markle", "and", "Prince", "Harry", "announce", "their", "decision", "to", "step", "back", "from", "their", "royal", "duties", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The United States imposes sanctions on Russia following the suspected poisoning of Alexei Navalny.", "tokens": ["The", "United", "States", "imposes", "sanctions", "on", "Russia", "following", "the", "suspected", "poisoning", "of", "Alexei", "Navalny", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tesla's stock prices surge as the company reports record-breaking sales and profits.", "tokens": ["Tesla", "'", "s", "stock", "prices", "surge", "as", "the", "company", "reports", "record", "-", "breaking", "sales", "and", "profits", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The United Nations Security Council condemns the recent terrorist attacks in Nigeria.", "tokens": ["The", "United", "Nations", "Security", "Council", "condemns", "the", "recent", "terrorist", "attacks", "in", "Nigeria", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tesla CEO Elon Musk announces plans to build a new gigafactory in Texas.", "tokens": ["Tesla", "CEO", "Elon", "Musk", "announces", "plans", "to", "build", "a", "new", "gigafactory", "in", "Texas", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The World Bank approves a $500 million loan to support education reform in India.", "tokens": ["The", "World", "Bank", "approves", "a", "$", "500", "million", "loan", "to", "support", "education", "reform", "in", "India", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "South Korea hosts a virtual summit with leaders from ASEAN countries to strengthen economic cooperation.", "tokens": ["South", "Korea", "hosts", "a", "virtual", "summit", "with", "leaders", "from", "ASEAN", "countries", "to", "strengthen", "economic", "cooperation", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The European Central Bank announces an expansion of its stimulus program to support the economy.", "tokens": ["The", "European", "Central", "Bank", "announces", "an", "expansion", "of", "its", "stimulus", "program", "to", "support", "the", "economy", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Wildfires continue to devastate parts of California.", "tokens": ["Wildfires", "continue", "to", "devastate", "parts", "of", "California", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Pfizer announces plans for booster shots in response to new COVID variants.", "tokens": ["Pfizer", "announces", "plans", "for", "booster", "shots", "in", "response", "to", "new", "COVID", "variants", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Serena Williams withdraws from Wimbledon due to injury.", "tokens": ["Serena", "Williams", "withdraws", "from", "Wimbledon", "due", "to", "injury", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "United Nations report shows increase in global poverty rates.", "tokens": ["United", "Nations", "report", "shows", "increase", "in", "global", "poverty", "rates", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tech giant Apple introduces new line of products.", "tokens": ["Tech", "giant", "Apple", "introduces", "new", "line", "of", "products", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Prime Minister Trudeau visits Indigenous community in northern Canada.", "tokens": ["Prime", "Minister", "Trudeau", "visits", "Indigenous", "community", "in", "northern", "Canada", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-person", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "SpaceX successfully launches new satellite into orbit.", "tokens": ["SpaceX", "successfully", "launches", "new", "satellite", "into", "orbit", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Record-breaking heatwave hits Western Europe.", "tokens": ["Record", "-", "breaking", "heatwave", "hits", "Western", "Europe", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Apple Inc. unveils latest iPhone model.", "tokens": ["Apple", "Inc", ".", "unveils", "latest", "iPhone", "model", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tropical storm makes landfall in Florida.", "tokens": ["Tropical", "storm", "makes", "landfall", "in", "Florida", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX launches satellite into orbit.", "tokens": ["Elon", "Musk", "'", "s", "SpaceX", "launches", "satellite", "into", "orbit", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "New study shows link between coffee consumption and reduced risk of heart disease.", "tokens": ["New", "study", "shows", "link", "between", "coffee", "consumption", "and", "reduced", "risk", "of", "heart", "disease", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "United Nations issues statement on human rights violations in Myanmar.", "tokens": ["United", "Nations", "issues", "statement", "on", "human", "rights", "violations", "in", "Myanmar", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Simone Biles wins gold in gymnastics competition.", "tokens": ["Simone", "Biles", "wins", "gold", "in", "gymnastics", "competition", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Google announces partnership with local schools to promote computer science education.", "tokens": ["Google", "announces", "partnership", "with", "local", "schools", "to", "promote", "computer", "science", "education", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Former President Obama visits Kenya for charity work.", "tokens": ["Former", "President", "Obama", "visits", "Kenya", "for", "charity", "work", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-person", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Wildfires continue to ravage California forests.", "tokens": ["Wildfires", "continue", "to", "ravage", "California", "forests", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Amazon to open new distribution center in Texas.", "tokens": ["Amazon", "to", "open", "new", "distribution", "center", "in", "Texas", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "New study finds potential link between obesity and increased risk of certain cancers.", "tokens": ["New", "study", "finds", "potential", "link", "between", "obesity", "and", "increased", "risk", "of", "certain", "cancers", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Beyoncé releases new album.", "tokens": ["Beyoncé", "releases", "new", "album", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "European Union imposes sanctions on Russia for human rights abuses.", "tokens": ["European", "Union", "imposes", "sanctions", "on", "Russia", "for", "human", "rights", "abuses", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "New York City to implement new public transportation system.", "tokens": ["New", "York", "City", "to", "implement", "new", "public", "transportation", "system", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Greta Thunberg speaks at climate change conference in Switzerland.", "tokens": ["Greta", "Thunberg", "speaks", "at", "climate", "change", "conference", "in", "Switzerland", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Toyota announces recall of over 1 million vehicles.", "tokens": ["Toyota", "announces", "recall", "of", "over", "1", "million", "vehicles", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Hurricane hits coastal town in Louisiana.", "tokens": ["Hurricane", "hits", "coastal", "town", "in", "Louisiana", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Researchers discover new species of dinosaur in South America.", "tokens": ["Researchers", "discover", "new", "species", "of", "dinosaur", "in", "South", "America", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Taylor Swift performs at sold-out concert in London.", "tokens": ["Taylor", "Swift", "performs", "at", "sold", "-", "out", "concert", "in", "London", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Microsoft CEO steps down from position.", "tokens": ["Microsoft", "CEO", "steps", "down", "from", "position", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Australia experiences record-breaking heatwave.", "tokens": ["Australia", "experiences", "record", "-", "breaking", "heatwave", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "LeBron James signs multi-million dollar contract with new team.", "tokens": ["LeBron", "James", "signs", "multi", "-", "million", "dollar", "contract", "with", "new", "team", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Alibaba founder faces investigation for alleged financial misconduct.", "tokens": ["Alibaba", "founder", "faces", "investigation", "for", "alleged", "financial", "misconduct", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Mount Everest climbers stranded in severe snowstorm.", "tokens": ["Mount", "Everest", "climbers", "stranded", "in", "severe", "snowstorm", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Taylor Jenkins named head coach of NBA team.", "tokens": ["Taylor", "Jenkins", "named", "head", "coach", "of", "NBA", "team", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "New study suggests link between social media use and increased anxiety.", "tokens": ["New", "study", "suggests", "link", "between", "social", "media", "use", "and", "increased", "anxiety", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Thousands protest for democracy in Hong Kong.", "tokens": ["Thousands", "protest", "for", "democracy", "in", "Hong", "Kong", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Warren Buffett donates $1 billion to charity.", "tokens": ["Warren", "Buffett", "donates", "$", "1", "billion", "to", "charity", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Ford to invest in new electric vehicle technology.", "tokens": ["Ford", "to", "invest", "in", "new", "electric", "vehicle", "technology", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Severe drought threatens crops in Midwest.", "tokens": ["Severe", "drought", "threatens", "crops", "in", "Midwest", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Jennifer Lawrence to star in upcoming film.", "tokens": ["Jennifer", "Lawrence", "to", "star", "in", "upcoming", "film", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "World Health Organization issues warning about new strain of flu virus.", "tokens": ["World", "Health", "Organization", "issues", "warning", "about", "new", "strain", "of", "flu", "virus", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "New York Yankees win World Series.", "tokens": ["New", "York", "Yankees", "win", "World", "Series", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Duchess of Cambridge visits children's hospital in London.", "tokens": ["Duchess", "of", "Cambridge", "visits", "children", "'", "s", "hospital", "in", "London", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Uber to launch new food delivery service.", "tokens": ["Uber", "to", "launch", "new", "food", "delivery", "service", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Scientists confirm presence of water on Mars.", "tokens": ["Scientists", "confirm", "presence", "of", "water", "on", "Mars", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Singer Rihanna starts new fashion line.", "tokens": ["Singer", "Rihanna", "starts", "new", "fashion", "line", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "United Airlines to add new routes to Europe.", "tokens": ["United", "Airlines", "to", "add", "new", "routes", "to", "Europe", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "FBI warns of potential cyberattack on government agencies.", "tokens": ["FBI", "warns", "of", "potential", "cyberattack", "on", "government", "agencies", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Italian restaurant chain announces expansion to Asia.", "tokens": ["Italian", "restaurant", "chain", "announces", "expansion", "to", "Asia", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "New study shows link between air pollution and increased risk of respiratory illnesses.", "tokens": ["New", "study", "shows", "link", "between", "air", "pollution", "and", "increased", "risk", "of", "respiratory", "illnesses", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Prince Harry and Meghan Markle visit Africa for charity work.", "tokens": ["Prince", "Harry", "and", "Meghan", "Markle", "visit", "Africa", "for", "charity", "work", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Facebook launches new initiative to combat misinformation.", "tokens": ["Facebook", "launches", "new", "initiative", "to", "combat", "misinformation", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Iran announces plan to increase uranium enrichment.", "tokens": ["Iran", "announces", "plan", "to", "increase", "uranium", "enrichment", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Nobel Peace Prize awarded to humanitarian organization for work in conflict zones.", "tokens": ["Nobel", "Peace", "Prize", "awarded", "to", "humanitarian", "organization", "for", "work", "in", "conflict", "zones", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Severe flooding hits coastal town in Japan.", "tokens": ["Severe", "flooding", "hits", "coastal", "town", "in", "Japan", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Apple announces new iPhone 13 launch date.", "tokens": ["Apple", "announces", "new", "iPhone", "13", "launch", "date", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Prime Minister Johnson meets with French President Macron.", "tokens": ["Prime", "Minister", "Johnson", "meets", "with", "French", "President", "Macron", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-person", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Hurricane hits Florida, causing widespread damage.", "tokens": ["Hurricane", "hits", "Florida", ",", "causing", "widespread", "damage", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Amazon faces lawsuit over worker conditions.", "tokens": ["Amazon", "faces", "lawsuit", "over", "worker", "conditions", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Elon Musk plans to visit SpaceX headquarters.", "tokens": ["Elon", "Musk", "plans", "to", "visit", "SpaceX", "headquarters", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "New York City imposes vaccine mandate for indoor activities.", "tokens": ["New", "York", "City", "imposes", "vaccine", "mandate", "for", "indoor", "activities", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "President Biden unveils new infrastructure plan.", "tokens": ["President", "Biden", "unveils", "new", "infrastructure", "plan", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "COVID-19 cases surge in California.", "tokens": ["COVID", "-", "19", "cases", "surge", "in", "California", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Facebook to launch new virtual reality headset.", "tokens": ["Facebook", "to", "launch", "new", "virtual", "reality", "headset", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tiger Woods returns to golf after injury.", "tokens": ["Tiger", "Woods", "returns", "to", "golf", "after", "injury", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "United Nations adopts resolution on climate change.", "tokens": ["United", "Nations", "adopts", "resolution", "on", "climate", "change", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Wildfires continue to ravage Australian countryside.", "tokens": ["Wildfires", "continue", "to", "ravage", "Australian", "countryside", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "CEO of Microsoft steps down after 20 years.", "tokens": ["CEO", "of", "Microsoft", "steps", "down", "after", "20", "years", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "German Chancellor Merkel wins reelection.", "tokens": ["German", "Chancellor", "Merkel", "wins", "reelection", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-person", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tokyo Olympics conclude after two-week event.", "tokens": ["Tokyo", "Olympics", "conclude", "after", "two", "-", "week", "event", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tesla announces record-breaking quarterly profits.", "tokens": ["Tesla", "announces", "record", "-", "breaking", "quarterly", "profits", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Los Angeles Lakers sign new star player.", "tokens": ["Los", "Angeles", "Lakers", "sign", "new", "star", "player", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Russian President Putin meets with Chinese leader Xi.", "tokens": ["Russian", "President", "Putin", "meets", "with", "Chinese", "leader", "Xi", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-person", "O"]}
{"sentence": "NASA launches new rover to explore Mars.", "tokens": ["NASA", "launches", "new", "rover", "to", "explore", "Mars", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Pfizer seeks approval for COVID-19 vaccine booster.", "tokens": ["Pfizer", "seeks", "approval", "for", "COVID", "-", "19", "vaccine", "booster", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "London experiences heavy flooding after rainstorm.", "tokens": ["London", "experiences", "heavy", "flooding", "after", "rainstorm", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Goldman Sachs CEO testifies before Congress.", "tokens": ["Goldman", "Sachs", "CEO", "testifies", "before", "Congress", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Syrian refugees stranded at border.", "tokens": ["Syrian", "refugees", "stranded", "at", "border", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Famous chef opens new restaurant in Paris.", "tokens": ["Famous", "chef", "opens", "new", "restaurant", "in", "Paris", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Federal Reserve announces interest rate hike.", "tokens": ["Federal", "Reserve", "announces", "interest", "rate", "hike", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Canadian Prime Minister Trudeau faces backlash over pipeline decision.", "tokens": ["Canadian", "Prime", "Minister", "Trudeau", "faces", "backlash", "over", "pipeline", "decision", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "B-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Oil prices soar amid global supply chain issues.", "tokens": ["Oil", "prices", "soar", "amid", "global", "supply", "chain", "issues", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Mumbai hit by massive power outage.", "tokens": ["Mumbai", "hit", "by", "massive", "power", "outage", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Anti-government protests erupt in Hong Kong.", "tokens": ["Anti", "-", "government", "protests", "erupt", "in", "Hong", "Kong", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "CEO of Amazon donates millions to charity.", "tokens": ["CEO", "of", "Amazon", "donates", "millions", "to", "charity", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "New study shows link between air pollution and health problems.", "tokens": ["New", "study", "shows", "link", "between", "air", "pollution", "and", "health", "problems", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "United Nations peacekeepers deployed to conflict zone in Africa.", "tokens": ["United", "Nations", "peacekeepers", "deployed", "to", "conflict", "zone", "in", "Africa", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Egyptian archaeologists discover ancient tombs.", "tokens": ["Egyptian", "archaeologists", "discover", "ancient", "tombs", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Google unveils new AI technology for healthcare.", "tokens": ["Google", "unveils", "new", "AI", "technology", "for", "healthcare", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "FBI warns of potential cyberattack on U.S. infrastructure.", "tokens": ["FBI", "warns", "of", "potential", "cyberattack", "on", "U", ".", "S", ".", "infrastructure", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Italy imposes new COVID-19 restrictions.", "tokens": ["Italy", "imposes", "new", "COVID", "-", "19", "restrictions", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Starbucks announces plan to phase out plastic straws.", "tokens": ["Starbucks", "announces", "plan", "to", "phase", "out", "plastic", "straws", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Violence erupts in Ukraine-Russia border region.", "tokens": ["Violence", "erupts", "in", "Ukraine", "-", "Russia", "border", "region", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Japan to host 2021 Summer Olympics.", "tokens": ["Japan", "to", "host", "2021", "Summer", "Olympics", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "New study finds link between sugary drinks and obesity.", "tokens": ["New", "study", "finds", "link", "between", "sugary", "drinks", "and", "obesity", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Hollywood actress files lawsuit against tabloid magazine.", "tokens": ["Hollywood", "actress", "files", "lawsuit", "against", "tabloid", "magazine", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "U.N. Secretary-General calls for global ceasefire.", "tokens": ["U", ".", "N", ".", "Secretary", "-", "General", "calls", "for", "global", "ceasefire", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Thousands evacuated as volcano erupts in Indonesia.", "tokens": ["Thousands", "evacuated", "as", "volcano", "erupts", "in", "Indonesia", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Twitter suspends accounts linked to misinformation.", "tokens": ["Twitter", "suspends", "accounts", "linked", "to", "misinformation", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Germany announces new climate action plan.", "tokens": ["Germany", "announces", "new", "climate", "action", "plan", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Warren Buffett donates billions to charity.", "tokens": ["Warren", "Buffett", "donates", "billions", "to", "charity", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "South Korea reports record high daily COVID-19 cases.", "tokens": ["South", "Korea", "reports", "record", "high", "daily", "COVID", "-", "19", "cases", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Paris Agreement anniversary marked with climate rallies worldwide.", "tokens": ["Paris", "Agreement", "anniversary", "marked", "with", "climate", "rallies", "worldwide", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Apple announces launch of new iPhone.", "tokens": ["Apple", "announces", "launch", "of", "new", "iPhone", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Earthquake hits Los Angeles, causing minor damages.", "tokens": ["Earthquake", "hits", "Los", "Angeles", ",", "causing", "minor", "damages", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Facebook to acquire virtual reality company for $2 billion.", "tokens": ["Facebook", "to", "acquire", "virtual", "reality", "company", "for", "$", "2", "billion", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Elon Musk's SpaceX to send astronauts to Mars by 2024.", "tokens": ["Elon", "Musk", "'", "s", "SpaceX", "to", "send", "astronauts", "to", "Mars", "by", "2024", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tropical storm warning in effect for Florida coast.", "tokens": ["Tropical", "storm", "warning", "in", "effect", "for", "Florida", "coast", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Amazon faces antitrust investigation in Europe.", "tokens": ["Amazon", "faces", "antitrust", "investigation", "in", "Europe", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "New York City to implement vaccine mandate for indoor activities.", "tokens": ["New", "York", "City", "to", "implement", "vaccine", "mandate", "for", "indoor", "activities", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "CEO of Microsoft steps down amid controversy.", "tokens": ["CEO", "of", "Microsoft", "steps", "down", "amid", "controversy", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Wildfire destroys homes in California.", "tokens": ["Wildfire", "destroys", "homes", "in", "California", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Marie Curie's Nobel Prize medal sells for record-breaking price.", "tokens": ["Marie", "Curie", "'", "s", "Nobel", "Prize", "medal", "sells", "for", "record", "-", "breaking", "price", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tokyo Olympics committee announces new COVID-19 protocols.", "tokens": ["Tokyo", "Olympics", "committee", "announces", "new", "COVID", "-", "19", "protocols", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "United Nations to hold emergency meeting on humanitarian crisis in Yemen.", "tokens": ["United", "Nations", "to", "hold", "emergency", "meeting", "on", "humanitarian", "crisis", "in", "Yemen", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Johnson & Johnson faces lawsuit over opioid crisis.", "tokens": ["Johnson", "&", "Johnson", "faces", "lawsuit", "over", "opioid", "crisis", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Hollywood actress Jennifer Lawrence to star in new film.", "tokens": ["Hollywood", "actress", "Jennifer", "Lawrence", "to", "star", "in", "new", "film", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "European Union introduces new regulations for plastic waste.", "tokens": ["European", "Union", "introduces", "new", "regulations", "for", "plastic", "waste", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Hurricane warning issued for Gulf Coast states.", "tokens": ["Hurricane", "warning", "issued", "for", "Gulf", "Coast", "states", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Nobel Peace Prize awarded to climate activist Greta Thunberg.", "tokens": ["Nobel", "Peace", "Prize", "awarded", "to", "climate", "activist", "Greta", "Thunberg", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O"]}
{"sentence": "SpaceX rocket launch successful, delivers supplies to International Space Station.", "tokens": ["SpaceX", "rocket", "launch", "successful", ",", "delivers", "supplies", "to", "International", "Space", "Station", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "New York City Mayor announces new policy on recycling.", "tokens": ["New", "York", "City", "Mayor", "announces", "new", "policy", "on", "recycling", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "B-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Apple Inc. unveils the new iPhone 13.", "tokens": ["Apple", "Inc", ".", "unveils", "the", "new", "iPhone", "13", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Global warming Summit to be held in Paris.", "tokens": ["Global", "warming", "Summit", "to", "be", "held", "in", "Paris", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "President Biden to meet with G7 leaders next week.", "tokens": ["President", "Biden", "to", "meet", "with", "G7", "leaders", "next", "week", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-person", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Massive wildfire destroys homes in California.", "tokens": ["Massive", "wildfire", "destroys", "homes", "in", "California", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "SpaceX launches new satellite into orbit.", "tokens": ["SpaceX", "launches", "new", "satellite", "into", "orbit", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "World Health Organization issues new guidelines for COVID-19 vaccinations.", "tokens": ["World", "Health", "Organization", "issues", "new", "guidelines", "for", "COVID", "-", "19", "vaccinations", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Paris Fashion Week announces new designers.", "tokens": ["Paris", "Fashion", "Week", "announces", "new", "designers", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "United Nations releases report on global hunger crisis.", "tokens": ["United", "Nations", "releases", "report", "on", "global", "hunger", "crisis", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Celebrity couple files for divorce.", "tokens": ["Celebrity", "couple", "files", "for", "divorce", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Google to expand its headquarters in Silicon Valley.", "tokens": ["Google", "to", "expand", "its", "headquarters", "in", "Silicon", "Valley", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Hurricane hits Florida coast.", "tokens": ["Hurricane", "hits", "Florida", "coast", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Prince Harry and Meghan Markle welcome their second child.", "tokens": ["Prince", "Harry", "and", "Meghan", "Markle", "welcome", "their", "second", "child", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "New study shows the benefits of meditation for mental health.", "tokens": ["New", "study", "shows", "the", "benefits", "of", "meditation", "for", "mental", "health", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Sydney Opera House to host international music festival.", "tokens": ["Sydney", "Opera", "House", "to", "host", "international", "music", "festival", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Amazon CEO Jeff Bezos steps down from his position.", "tokens": ["Amazon", "CEO", "Jeff", "Bezos", "steps", "down", "from", "his", "position", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Delta variant of COVID-19 spreads rapidly in Texas.", "tokens": ["Delta", "variant", "of", "COVID", "-", "19", "spreads", "rapidly", "in", "Texas", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Famous chef opens new restaurant in London.", "tokens": ["Famous", "chef", "opens", "new", "restaurant", "in", "London", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Pfizer and BioNTech develop new vaccine for coronavirus.", "tokens": ["Pfizer", "and", "BioNTech", "develop", "new", "vaccine", "for", "coronavirus", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Ohio State University to require COVID-19 vaccinations for all students.", "tokens": ["Ohio", "State", "University", "to", "require", "COVID", "-", "19", "vaccinations", "for", "all", "students", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tokyo Olympics announce new safety protocols for athletes.", "tokens": ["Tokyo", "Olympics", "announce", "new", "safety", "protocols", "for", "athletes", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Soccer star Cristiano Ronaldo signs new contract with Manchester United.", "tokens": ["Soccer", "star", "Cristiano", "Ronaldo", "signs", "new", "contract", "with", "Manchester", "United", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Wild bison herd sighted in Yellowstone National Park.", "tokens": ["Wild", "bison", "herd", "sighted", "in", "Yellowstone", "National", "Park", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Bill Gates donates $1 million to charity.", "tokens": ["Bill", "Gates", "donates", "$", "1", "million", "to", "charity", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "New York Stock Exchange experiences record-breaking gains.", "tokens": ["New", "York", "Stock", "Exchange", "experiences", "record", "-", "breaking", "gains", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Paris Hilton launches new fashion line.", "tokens": ["Paris", "Hilton", "launches", "new", "fashion", "line", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "United States imposes new sanctions on Russia.", "tokens": ["United", "States", "imposes", "new", "sanctions", "on", "Russia", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Pop singer Taylor Swift releases new album.", "tokens": ["Pop", "singer", "Taylor", "Swift", "releases", "new", "album", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Microsoft to acquire gaming company Bethesda.", "tokens": ["Microsoft", "to", "acquire", "gaming", "company", "Bethesda", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Former President Obama to write a memoir.", "tokens": ["Former", "President", "Obama", "to", "write", "a", "memoir", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "London Marathon raises millions for charity.", "tokens": ["London", "Marathon", "raises", "millions", "for", "charity", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "In-N-Out Burger opens new location in Arizona.", "tokens": ["In", "-", "N", "-", "Out", "Burger", "opens", "new", "location", "in", "Arizona", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "High-speed rail project approved for construction in California.", "tokens": ["High", "-", "speed", "rail", "project", "approved", "for", "construction", "in", "California", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Fashion designer Karl Lagerfeld passes away at 85.", "tokens": ["Fashion", "designer", "Karl", "Lagerfeld", "passes", "away", "at", "85", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "American actress Angelina Jolie visits Syrian refugee camp.", "tokens": ["American", "actress", "Angelina", "Jolie", "visits", "Syrian", "refugee", "camp", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "SpaceX founder Elon Musk plans trip to space.", "tokens": ["SpaceX", "founder", "Elon", "Musk", "plans", "trip", "to", "space", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Apple Store robbed in downtown Chicago.", "tokens": ["Apple", "Store", "robbed", "in", "downtown", "Chicago", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "World Bank warns of economic downturn in developing countries.", "tokens": ["World", "Bank", "warns", "of", "economic", "downturn", "in", "developing", "countries", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "New York Yankees defeat Boston Red Sox in extra innings.", "tokens": ["New", "York", "Yankees", "defeat", "Boston", "Red", "Sox", "in", "extra", "innings", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "South Africa imposes strict lockdown measures to curb COVID-19 spread.", "tokens": ["South", "Africa", "imposes", "strict", "lockdown", "measures", "to", "curb", "COVID", "-", "19", "spread", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Australian airline Qantas to resume international flights.", "tokens": ["Australian", "airline", "Qantas", "to", "resume", "international", "flights", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Technology giant IBM announces new sustainability initiative.", "tokens": ["Technology", "giant", "IBM", "announces", "new", "sustainability", "initiative", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Instagram influencer faces backlash over controversial post.", "tokens": ["Instagram", "influencer", "faces", "backlash", "over", "controversial", "post", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "United Nations appoints new envoy for climate change.", "tokens": ["United", "Nations", "appoints", "new", "envoy", "for", "climate", "change", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "New study shows the benefits of exercise for heart health.", "tokens": ["New", "study", "shows", "the", "benefits", "of", "exercise", "for", "heart", "health", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Microsoft CEO Satya Nadella speaks at technology conference.", "tokens": ["Microsoft", "CEO", "Satya", "Nadella", "speaks", "at", "technology", "conference", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Los Angeles Lakers star LeBron James sidelined with ankle injury.", "tokens": ["Los", "Angeles", "Lakers", "star", "LeBron", "James", "sidelined", "with", "ankle", "injury", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The CEO of Apple announced a new product launch.", "tokens": ["The", "CEO", "of", "Apple", "announced", "a", "new", "product", "launch", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "London's mayor declares a state of emergency due to extreme weather conditions.", "tokens": ["London", "'", "s", "mayor", "declares", "a", "state", "of", "emergency", "due", "to", "extreme", "weather", "conditions", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The United Nations has issued a statement condemning the recent acts of violence in the region.", "tokens": ["The", "United", "Nations", "has", "issued", "a", "statement", "condemning", "the", "recent", "acts", "of", "violence", "in", "the", "region", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Famous actress Jennifer Lawrence will star in a new film adaptation of a classic novel.", "tokens": ["Famous", "actress", "Jennifer", "Lawrence", "will", "star", "in", "a", "new", "film", "adaptation", "of", "a", "classic", "novel", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The European Union has implemented new trade tariffs on imported goods.", "tokens": ["The", "European", "Union", "has", "implemented", "new", "trade", "tariffs", "on", "imported", "goods", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "New York City plans to invest millions of dollars in upgrading its public transportation system.", "tokens": ["New", "York", "City", "plans", "to", "invest", "millions", "of", "dollars", "in", "upgrading", "its", "public", "transportation", "system", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The former president of the United States will be delivering a keynote speech at the upcoming conference.", "tokens": ["The", "former", "president", "of", "the", "United", "States", "will", "be", "delivering", "a", "keynote", "speech", "at", "the", "upcoming", "conference", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Facebook is facing scrutiny over its data privacy policies.", "tokens": ["Facebook", "is", "facing", "scrutiny", "over", "its", "data", "privacy", "policies", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Thousands of protesters gathered outside the headquarters of the multinational corporation to demand better working conditions.", "tokens": ["Thousands", "of", "protesters", "gathered", "outside", "the", "headquarters", "of", "the", "multinational", "corporation", "to", "demand", "better", "working", "conditions", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Australian Prime Minister announces a new policy to combat climate change.", "tokens": ["Australian", "Prime", "Minister", "announces", "a", "new", "policy", "to", "combat", "climate", "change", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The latest study conducted by the World Health Organization reveals alarming statistics about global obesity rates.", "tokens": ["The", "latest", "study", "conducted", "by", "the", "World", "Health", "Organization", "reveals", "alarming", "statistics", "about", "global", "obesity", "rates", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The CEO of Tesla unveils plans for a revolutionary new electric vehicle.", "tokens": ["The", "CEO", "of", "Tesla", "unveils", "plans", "for", "a", "revolutionary", "new", "electric", "vehicle", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tokyo Olympics organizers reveal new safety measures for the upcoming games.", "tokens": ["Tokyo", "Olympics", "organizers", "reveal", "new", "safety", "measures", "for", "the", "upcoming", "games", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The famous singer Taylor Swift announces a world tour.", "tokens": ["The", "famous", "singer", "Taylor", "Swift", "announces", "a", "world", "tour", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The World Bank has approved a loan for infrastructure development in developing countries.", "tokens": ["The", "World", "Bank", "has", "approved", "a", "loan", "for", "infrastructure", "development", "in", "developing", "countries", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "NASA launches a new satellite into orbit to study climate patterns.", "tokens": ["NASA", "launches", "a", "new", "satellite", "into", "orbit", "to", "study", "climate", "patterns", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The Italian government is facing backlash over its immigration policies.", "tokens": ["The", "Italian", "government", "is", "facing", "backlash", "over", "its", "immigration", "policies", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Pop star Lady Gaga cancels her upcoming concert due to illness.", "tokens": ["Pop", "star", "Lady", "Gaga", "cancels", "her", "upcoming", "concert", "due", "to", "illness", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The United Nations Security Council condemns the recent terrorist attacks in the Middle East.", "tokens": ["The", "United", "Nations", "Security", "Council", "condemns", "the", "recent", "terrorist", "attacks", "in", "the", "Middle", "East", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The city of Paris is implementing new measures to reduce air pollution.", "tokens": ["The", "city", "of", "Paris", "is", "implementing", "new", "measures", "to", "reduce", "air", "pollution", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The CEO of Amazon announces plans for expansion into new markets.", "tokens": ["The", "CEO", "of", "Amazon", "announces", "plans", "for", "expansion", "into", "new", "markets", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Indian Prime Minister addresses the nation on Independence Day.", "tokens": ["Indian", "Prime", "Minister", "addresses", "the", "nation", "on", "Independence", "Day", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The International Monetary Fund warns of a global economic slowdown.", "tokens": ["The", "International", "Monetary", "Fund", "warns", "of", "a", "global", "economic", "slowdown", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The Russian government denies allegations of election interference.", "tokens": ["The", "Russian", "government", "denies", "allegations", "of", "election", "interference", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Renowned chef Gordon Ramsay opens a new restaurant in Los Angeles.", "tokens": ["Renowned", "chef", "Gordon", "Ramsay", "opens", "a", "new", "restaurant", "in", "Los", "Angeles", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The World Trade Organization reports a significant increase in global trade tensions.", "tokens": ["The", "World", "Trade", "Organization", "reports", "a", "significant", "increase", "in", "global", "trade", "tensions", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "London Symphony Orchestra announces a series of upcoming performances.", "tokens": ["London", "Symphony", "Orchestra", "announces", "a", "series", "of", "upcoming", "performances", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The British monarchy faces criticism over its handling of recent scandals.", "tokens": ["The", "British", "monarchy", "faces", "criticism", "over", "its", "handling", "of", "recent", "scandals", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Microsoft unveils a new line of products at its annual conference.", "tokens": ["Microsoft", "unveils", "a", "new", "line", "of", "products", "at", "its", "annual", "conference", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "French President Macron delivers a speech on national security.", "tokens": ["French", "President", "Macron", "delivers", "a", "speech", "on", "national", "security", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The World Wildlife Fund is raising awareness about endangered species in Africa.", "tokens": ["The", "World", "Wildlife", "Fund", "is", "raising", "awareness", "about", "endangered", "species", "in", "Africa", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The Chinese government announces a crackdown on corruption within the Communist Party.", "tokens": ["The", "Chinese", "government", "announces", "a", "crackdown", "on", "corruption", "within", "the", "Communist", "Party", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Hollywood actor Brad Pitt to star in a new action thriller film.", "tokens": ["Hollywood", "actor", "Brad", "Pitt", "to", "star", "in", "a", "new", "action", "thriller", "film", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The International Red Cross issues a statement on the humanitarian crisis in Syria.", "tokens": ["The", "International", "Red", "Cross", "issues", "a", "statement", "on", "the", "humanitarian", "crisis", "in", "Syria", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tokyo Electric Power Company faces lawsuits over the Fukushima nuclear disaster.", "tokens": ["Tokyo", "Electric", "Power", "Company", "faces", "lawsuits", "over", "the", "Fukushima", "nuclear", "disaster", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The German Chancellor meets with world leaders to discuss trade agreements.", "tokens": ["The", "German", "Chancellor", "meets", "with", "world", "leaders", "to", "discuss", "trade", "agreements", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The American Red Cross provides aid to victims of a natural disaster in the Midwest.", "tokens": ["The", "American", "Red", "Cross", "provides", "aid", "to", "victims", "of", "a", "natural", "disaster", "in", "the", "Midwest", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "South Korean pop sensation BTS breaks records with their latest album release.", "tokens": ["South", "Korean", "pop", "sensation", "BTS", "breaks", "records", "with", "their", "latest", "album", "release", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The European Central Bank announces an interest rate hike.", "tokens": ["The", "European", "Central", "Bank", "announces", "an", "interest", "rate", "hike", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "New Zealand Prime Minister addresses climate change at the United Nations summit.", "tokens": ["New", "Zealand", "Prime", "Minister", "addresses", "climate", "change", "at", "the", "United", "Nations", "summit", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "I-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The World Economic Forum releases its annual report on global competitiveness.", "tokens": ["The", "World", "Economic", "Forum", "releases", "its", "annual", "report", "on", "global", "competitiveness", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Australian wildfires devastate wildlife and natural habitats.", "tokens": ["Australian", "wildfires", "devastate", "wildlife", "and", "natural", "habitats", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The Gates Foundation pledges millions of dollars to combat infectious diseases in developing countries.", "tokens": ["The", "Gates", "Foundation", "pledges", "millions", "of", "dollars", "to", "combat", "infectious", "diseases", "in", "developing", "countries", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The Filipino government faces criticism over human rights abuses.", "tokens": ["The", "Filipino", "government", "faces", "criticism", "over", "human", "rights", "abuses", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The Swedish pop group ABBA announces a reunion tour.", "tokens": ["The", "Swedish", "pop", "group", "ABBA", "announces", "a", "reunion", "tour", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Harvard University researchers make a breakthrough in cancer treatment.", "tokens": ["Harvard", "University", "researchers", "make", "a", "breakthrough", "in", "cancer", "treatment", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "South African President delivers a speech on economic reforms.", "tokens": ["South", "African", "President", "delivers", "a", "speech", "on", "economic", "reforms", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The World Health Organization warns of a new strain of flu virus in Southeast Asia.", "tokens": ["The", "World", "Health", "Organization", "warns", "of", "a", "new", "strain", "of", "flu", "virus", "in", "Southeast", "Asia", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "New study shows that eating fruits and vegetables can lower the risk of heart disease.", "tokens": ["New", "study", "shows", "that", "eating", "fruits", "and", "vegetables", "can", "lower", "the", "risk", "of", "heart", "disease", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "President Biden announces new infrastructure plan to improve roads and bridges.", "tokens": ["President", "Biden", "announces", "new", "infrastructure", "plan", "to", "improve", "roads", "and", "bridges", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tesla CEO Elon Musk predicts that self-driving cars will be on the road by next year.", "tokens": ["Tesla", "CEO", "Elon", "Musk", "predicts", "that", "self", "-", "driving", "cars", "will", "be", "on", "the", "road", "by", "next", "year", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Japan to host 2021 Summer Olympics despite concerns over COVID-19.", "tokens": ["Japan", "to", "host", "2021", "Summer", "Olympics", "despite", "concerns", "over", "COVID", "-", "19", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Apple unveils new iPhone with advanced features and expanded battery life.", "tokens": ["Apple", "unveils", "new", "iPhone", "with", "advanced", "features", "and", "expanded", "battery", "life", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Rising star actress Emma Watson takes a break from acting to focus on activism.", "tokens": ["Rising", "star", "actress", "Emma", "Watson", "takes", "a", "break", "from", "acting", "to", "focus", "on", "activism", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Wildfires continue to ravage California, forcing thousands to evacuate their homes.", "tokens": ["Wildfires", "continue", "to", "ravage", "California", ",", "forcing", "thousands", "to", "evacuate", "their", "homes", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Amazon founder Jeff Bezos announces plans for space tourism company.", "tokens": ["Amazon", "founder", "Jeff", "Bezos", "announces", "plans", "for", "space", "tourism", "company", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Study finds that regular exercise can improve mental health and cognitive function.", "tokens": ["Study", "finds", "that", "regular", "exercise", "can", "improve", "mental", "health", "and", "cognitive", "function", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "European Union leaders meet to discuss climate change and environmental policies.", "tokens": ["European", "Union", "leaders", "meet", "to", "discuss", "climate", "change", "and", "environmental", "policies", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The United Nations convened a special session to discuss climate change.", "tokens": ["The", "United", "Nations", "convened", "a", "special", "session", "to", "discuss", "climate", "change", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O"]}
{"sentence": "President Biden announced new policies on immigration reform.", "tokens": ["President", "Biden", "announced", "new", "policies", "on", "immigration", "reform", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The city of London broke ground on a new public transportation project.", "tokens": ["The", "city", "of", "London", "broke", "ground", "on", "a", "new", "public", "transportation", "project", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Amazon employees protest for better working conditions.", "tokens": ["Amazon", "employees", "protest", "for", "better", "working", "conditions", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Elon Musk launches new space exploration company.", "tokens": ["Elon", "Musk", "launches", "new", "space", "exploration", "company", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The New York Stock Exchange experienced a record high trading day.", "tokens": ["The", "New", "York", "Stock", "Exchange", "experienced", "a", "record", "high", "trading", "day", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Thousands of people gathered in Paris to protest vaccine mandates.", "tokens": ["Thousands", "of", "people", "gathered", "in", "Paris", "to", "protest", "vaccine", "mandates", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Apple releases the latest iPhone model.", "tokens": ["Apple", "releases", "the", "latest", "iPhone", "model", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Spanish soccer star Lionel Messi signs with Paris Saint-Germain.", "tokens": ["Spanish", "soccer", "star", "Lionel", "Messi", "signs", "with", "Paris", "Saint", "-", "Germain", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The European Union announces new trade agreements with China.", "tokens": ["The", "European", "Union", "announces", "new", "trade", "agreements", "with", "China", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "CEO of Tesla, Elon Musk, becomes the world's richest person.", "tokens": ["CEO", "of", "Tesla", ",", "Elon", "Musk", ",", "becomes", "the", "world", "'", "s", "richest", "person", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Hurricane season devastates coastal communities in the Caribbean.", "tokens": ["Hurricane", "season", "devastates", "coastal", "communities", "in", "the", "Caribbean", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Australian government invests in renewable energy projects.", "tokens": ["Australian", "government", "invests", "in", "renewable", "energy", "projects", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Grammy award-winning artist Beyoncé releases new album.", "tokens": ["Grammy", "award", "-", "winning", "artist", "Beyoncé", "releases", "new", "album", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-person", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Russian President Vladimir Putin meets with German Chancellor Angela Merkel.", "tokens": ["Russian", "President", "Vladimir", "Putin", "meets", "with", "German", "Chancellor", "Angela", "Merkel", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "I-person", "I-person", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tokyo to host 2021 Summer Olympics.", "tokens": ["Tokyo", "to", "host", "2021", "Summer", "Olympics", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Facebook under fire for privacy breaches.", "tokens": ["Facebook", "under", "fire", "for", "privacy", "breaches", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The World Health Organization warns of a new strain of flu virus.", "tokens": ["The", "World", "Health", "Organization", "warns", "of", "a", "new", "strain", "of", "flu", "virus", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "South African activist Desmond Tutu awarded Nobel Peace Prize.", "tokens": ["South", "African", "activist", "Desmond", "Tutu", "awarded", "Nobel", "Peace", "Prize", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Amazon announces plans to open new headquarters in Atlanta.", "tokens": ["Amazon", "announces", "plans", "to", "open", "new", "headquarters", "in", "Atlanta", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Scientists discover new species of dinosaur in Patagonia.", "tokens": ["Scientists", "discover", "new", "species", "of", "dinosaur", "in", "Patagonia", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Apple releases new iPhone with advanced camera features.", "tokens": ["Apple", "releases", "new", "iPhone", "with", "advanced", "camera", "features", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "European Union imposes sanctions on Russia.", "tokens": ["European", "Union", "imposes", "sanctions", "on", "Russia", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Actress Emma Watson speaks out against gender inequality in Hollywood.", "tokens": ["Actress", "Emma", "Watson", "speaks", "out", "against", "gender", "inequality", "in", "Hollywood", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Ford recalls over 100,000 vehicles due to safety concerns.", "tokens": ["Ford", "recalls", "over", "100", ",", "000", "vehicles", "due", "to", "safety", "concerns", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "United Nations announces humanitarian aid for refugees in Syria.", "tokens": ["United", "Nations", "announces", "humanitarian", "aid", "for", "refugees", "in", "Syria", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "CEO Elon Musk steps down from Tesla.", "tokens": ["CEO", "Elon", "Musk", "steps", "down", "from", "Tesla", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O"]}
{"sentence": "New York City implements new COVID-19 restrictions.", "tokens": ["New", "York", "City", "implements", "new", "COVID", "-", "19", "restrictions", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Former President Obama to release memoir next year.", "tokens": ["Former", "President", "Obama", "to", "release", "memoir", "next", "year", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Starbucks to expand its presence in China.", "tokens": ["Starbucks", "to", "expand", "its", "presence", "in", "China", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tennis player Serena Williams advances to the semifinals.", "tokens": ["Tennis", "player", "Serena", "Williams", "advances", "to", "the", "semifinals", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Google faces antitrust lawsuit from the Department of Justice.", "tokens": ["Google", "faces", "antitrust", "lawsuit", "from", "the", "Department", "of", "Justice", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Hurricane season expected to be particularly active this year.", "tokens": ["Hurricane", "season", "expected", "to", "be", "particularly", "active", "this", "year", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Microsoft acquires artificial intelligence startup.", "tokens": ["Microsoft", "acquires", "artificial", "intelligence", "startup", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "French government proposes new tax reforms.", "tokens": ["French", "government", "proposes", "new", "tax", "reforms", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Pilot reported seeing unidentified flying object over Arizona.", "tokens": ["Pilot", "reported", "seeing", "unidentified", "flying", "object", "over", "Arizona", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Legendary musician Paul McCartney to perform at charity concert.", "tokens": ["Legendary", "musician", "Paul", "McCartney", "to", "perform", "at", "charity", "concert", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Walmart to launch same-day delivery service.", "tokens": ["Walmart", "to", "launch", "same", "-", "day", "delivery", "service", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "California wildfires continue to devastate communities.", "tokens": ["California", "wildfires", "continue", "to", "devastate", "communities", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "CEO Tim Cook unveils new line of products at Apple event.", "tokens": ["CEO", "Tim", "Cook", "unveils", "new", "line", "of", "products", "at", "Apple", "event", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Renowned chef Gordon Ramsay opens new restaurant in Las Vegas.", "tokens": ["Renowned", "chef", "Gordon", "Ramsay", "opens", "new", "restaurant", "in", "Las", "Vegas", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "South Korea imposes strict lockdown measures amid surge in COVID-19 cases.", "tokens": ["South", "Korea", "imposes", "strict", "lockdown", "measures", "amid", "surge", "in", "COVID", "-", "19", "cases", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Bitcoin reaches new all-time high in trading value.", "tokens": ["Bitcoin", "reaches", "new", "all", "-", "time", "high", "in", "trading", "value", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Amazon founder Jeff Bezos steps down as CEO.", "tokens": ["Amazon", "founder", "Jeff", "Bezos", "steps", "down", "as", "CEO", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Broadway musical Hamilton to return to theaters next year.", "tokens": ["Broadway", "musical", "Hamilton", "to", "return", "to", "theaters", "next", "year", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "AstraZeneca vaccine found to be highly effective in new study.", "tokens": ["AstraZeneca", "vaccine", "found", "to", "be", "highly", "effective", "in", "new", "study", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Manchester United signs new sponsorship deal with major tech company.", "tokens": ["Manchester", "United", "signs", "new", "sponsorship", "deal", "with", "major", "tech", "company", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "McDonald's introduces new plant-based burger to its menu.", "tokens": ["McDonald", "'", "s", "introduces", "new", "plant", "-", "based", "burger", "to", "its", "menu", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Swiss government announces plans to reduce carbon emissions.", "tokens": ["Swiss", "government", "announces", "plans", "to", "reduce", "carbon", "emissions", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Violent protests erupt in downtown Los Angeles.", "tokens": ["Violent", "protests", "erupt", "in", "downtown", "Los", "Angeles", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "CEO Mark Zuckerberg faces congressional hearing on privacy issues.", "tokens": ["CEO", "Mark", "Zuckerberg", "faces", "congressional", "hearing", "on", "privacy", "issues", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tokyo Olympics organizers announce new COVID-19 protocols for athletes.", "tokens": ["Tokyo", "Olympics", "organizers", "announce", "new", "COVID", "-", "19", "protocols", "for", "athletes", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Starbucks CEO Howard Schultz to step down from his position.", "tokens": ["Starbucks", "CEO", "Howard", "Schultz", "to", "step", "down", "from", "his", "position", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "New Zealand experiences 6.5 magnitude earthquake.", "tokens": ["New", "Zealand", "experiences", "6", ".", "5", "magnitude", "earthquake", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Grammy-winning artist Beyoncé to headline music festival in Chicago.", "tokens": ["Grammy", "-", "winning", "artist", "Beyoncé", "to", "headline", "music", "festival", "in", "Chicago", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tesla announces plans to build new Gigafactory in Texas.", "tokens": ["Tesla", "announces", "plans", "to", "build", "new", "Gigafactory", "in", "Texas", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Germany approves new climate change legislation.", "tokens": ["Germany", "approves", "new", "climate", "change", "legislation", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Legendary director Steven Spielberg to produce new film.", "tokens": ["Legendary", "director", "Steven", "Spielberg", "to", "produce", "new", "film", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "SpaceX CEO Elon Musk announces plans for manned mission to Mars.", "tokens": ["SpaceX", "CEO", "Elon", "Musk", "announces", "plans", "for", "manned", "mission", "to", "Mars", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Australian government launches inquiry into banking industry practices.", "tokens": ["Australian", "government", "launches", "inquiry", "into", "banking", "industry", "practices", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Major snowstorm expected to hit northeastern United States.", "tokens": ["Major", "snowstorm", "expected", "to", "hit", "northeastern", "United", "States", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Instagram introduces new feature to combat cyberbullying.", "tokens": ["Instagram", "introduces", "new", "feature", "to", "combat", "cyberbullying", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "New York City mayor announces new infrastructure plan.", "tokens": ["New", "York", "City", "mayor", "announces", "new", "infrastructure", "plan", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "CEO of Apple speaks at annual tech conference.", "tokens": ["CEO", "of", "Apple", "speaks", "at", "annual", "tech", "conference", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Protests erupt in Paris over new labor laws.", "tokens": ["Protests", "erupt", "in", "Paris", "over", "new", "labor", "laws", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Famous actor arrested for drunk driving.", "tokens": ["Famous", "actor", "arrested", "for", "drunk", "driving", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "United Nations report highlights climate change concerns.", "tokens": ["United", "Nations", "report", "highlights", "climate", "change", "concerns", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Prime Minister of Japan meets with President of the United States.", "tokens": ["Prime", "Minister", "of", "Japan", "meets", "with", "President", "of", "the", "United", "States", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "I-person", "I-person", "I-person", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Major earthquake hits southern California.", "tokens": ["Major", "earthquake", "hits", "southern", "California", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Olympic athlete breaks world record in 100m dash.", "tokens": ["Olympic", "athlete", "breaks", "world", "record", "in", "100m", "dash", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "New study shows link between diet and heart disease.", "tokens": ["New", "study", "shows", "link", "between", "diet", "and", "heart", "disease", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Hurricane warning issued for Florida coast.", "tokens": ["Hurricane", "warning", "issued", "for", "Florida", "coast", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Apple announces new iPhone models.", "tokens": ["Apple", "announces", "new", "iPhone", "models", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "President Biden visits troops in Afghanistan.", "tokens": ["President", "Biden", "visits", "troops", "in", "Afghanistan", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Google CEO resigns amid controversy.", "tokens": ["Google", "CEO", "resigns", "amid", "controversy", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "California wildfires rage on, threatening homes.", "tokens": ["California", "wildfires", "rage", "on", ",", "threatening", "homes", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tesla stock reaches all-time high.", "tokens": ["Tesla", "stock", "reaches", "all", "-", "time", "high", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Dr. Anthony Fauci warns of potential COVID-19 surge.", "tokens": ["Dr", ".", "Anthony", "Fauci", "warns", "of", "potential", "COVID", "-", "19", "surge", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "I-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "United Nations calls for ceasefire in Syria.", "tokens": ["United", "Nations", "calls", "for", "ceasefire", "in", "Syria", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Amazon Prime Day sales exceed expectations.", "tokens": ["Amazon", "Prime", "Day", "sales", "exceed", "expectations", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "New York City imposes vaccine mandate for indoor dining.", "tokens": ["New", "York", "City", "imposes", "vaccine", "mandate", "for", "indoor", "dining", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Facebook faces backlash over privacy concerns.", "tokens": ["Facebook", "faces", "backlash", "over", "privacy", "concerns", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Angela Merkel elected as President of the European Union.", "tokens": ["Angela", "Merkel", "elected", "as", "President", "of", "the", "European", "Union", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tokyo Olympics postponed due to pandemic.", "tokens": ["Tokyo", "Olympics", "postponed", "due", "to", "pandemic", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "International Monetary Fund projects global economic slowdown.", "tokens": ["International", "Monetary", "Fund", "projects", "global", "economic", "slowdown", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "FDA approves new cancer treatment.", "tokens": ["FDA", "approves", "new", "cancer", "treatment", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "World Health Organization declares polio eradicated in Africa.", "tokens": ["World", "Health", "Organization", "declares", "polio", "eradicated", "in", "Africa", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Uber partners with local restaurant to offer food delivery.", "tokens": ["Uber", "partners", "with", "local", "restaurant", "to", "offer", "food", "delivery", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Apple plans to open a new store in downtown Miami.", "tokens": ["Apple", "plans", "to", "open", "a", "new", "store", "in", "downtown", "Miami", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The CEO of Tesla announced a new electric car model at the conference.", "tokens": ["The", "CEO", "of", "Tesla", "announced", "a", "new", "electric", "car", "model", "at", "the", "conference", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Mexico surpasses 100,000 COVID-19 deaths.", "tokens": ["Mexico", "surpasses", "100", ",", "000", "COVID", "-", "19", "deaths", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Japanese Prime Minister to visit South Korea next week.", "tokens": ["Japanese", "Prime", "Minister", "to", "visit", "South", "Korea", "next", "week", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Facebook acquires a leading artificial intelligence startup.", "tokens": ["Facebook", "acquires", "a", "leading", "artificial", "intelligence", "startup", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The famous actor, Tom Hanks, to star in a new war film.", "tokens": ["The", "famous", "actor", ",", "Tom", "Hanks", ",", "to", "star", "in", "a", "new", "war", "film", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Germany imposes strict lockdown measures in response to rising COVID-19 cases.", "tokens": ["Germany", "imposes", "strict", "lockdown", "measures", "in", "response", "to", "rising", "COVID", "-", "19", "cases", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The United Nations peacekeeping mission in the Middle East extends for another year.", "tokens": ["The", "United", "Nations", "peacekeeping", "mission", "in", "the", "Middle", "East", "extends", "for", "another", "year", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "New York City to invest $1 billion in affordable housing initiatives.", "tokens": ["New", "York", "City", "to", "invest", "$", "1", "billion", "in", "affordable", "housing", "initiatives", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Samsung to launch its latest smartphone model next month.", "tokens": ["Samsung", "to", "launch", "its", "latest", "smartphone", "model", "next", "month", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The president of France addresses the nation in a televised speech.", "tokens": ["The", "president", "of", "France", "addresses", "the", "nation", "in", "a", "televised", "speech", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Harvard University announces new financial aid initiatives for low-income students.", "tokens": ["Harvard", "University", "announces", "new", "financial", "aid", "initiatives", "for", "low", "-", "income", "students", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Hurricane Maria causes widespread devastation in Puerto Rico.", "tokens": ["Hurricane", "Maria", "causes", "widespread", "devastation", "in", "Puerto", "Rico", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The popular singer Taylor Swift releases a new album.", "tokens": ["The", "popular", "singer", "Taylor", "Swift", "releases", "a", "new", "album", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Google's parent company, Alphabet, faces antitrust investigation by the European Union.", "tokens": ["Google", "'", "s", "parent", "company", ",", "Alphabet", ",", "faces", "antitrust", "investigation", "by", "the", "European", "Union", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The mayor of London introduces new cycling infrastructure to reduce traffic congestion.", "tokens": ["The", "mayor", "of", "London", "introduces", "new", "cycling", "infrastructure", "to", "reduce", "traffic", "congestion", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Microsoft announces a partnership with a leading tech startup to develop innovative software solutions.", "tokens": ["Microsoft", "announces", "a", "partnership", "with", "a", "leading", "tech", "startup", "to", "develop", "innovative", "software", "solutions", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The renowned chef Julia Child's cookbook sells for a record price at auction.", "tokens": ["The", "renowned", "chef", "Julia", "Child", "'", "s", "cookbook", "sells", "for", "a", "record", "price", "at", "auction", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Brazil's president signs an executive order to address deforestation in the Amazon rainforest.", "tokens": ["Brazil", "'", "s", "president", "signs", "an", "executive", "order", "to", "address", "deforestation", "in", "the", "Amazon", "rainforest", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "SpaceX launches a new satellite into orbit.", "tokens": ["SpaceX", "launches", "a", "new", "satellite", "into", "orbit", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The famous basketball player Michael Jordan to invest in a new sports team.", "tokens": ["The", "famous", "basketball", "player", "Michael", "Jordan", "to", "invest", "in", "a", "new", "sports", "team", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The European Central Bank announces new stimulus measures to support the economy.", "tokens": ["The", "European", "Central", "Bank", "announces", "new", "stimulus", "measures", "to", "support", "the", "economy", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The iconic landmark, the Eiffel Tower, reopens to tourists after a lengthy renovation.", "tokens": ["The", "iconic", "landmark", ",", "the", "Eiffel", "Tower", ",", "reopens", "to", "tourists", "after", "a", "lengthy", "renovation", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The United States announces new trade tariffs on Chinese goods.", "tokens": ["The", "United", "States", "announces", "new", "trade", "tariffs", "on", "Chinese", "goods", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Mary Smith appointed as new CEO of ABC Corporation.", "tokens": ["Mary", "Smith", "appointed", "as", "new", "CEO", "of", "ABC", "Corporation", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Firefighters battle massive wildfire in California.", "tokens": ["Firefighters", "battle", "massive", "wildfire", "in", "California", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Researchers discover potential new treatment for Alzheimer's disease.", "tokens": ["Researchers", "discover", "potential", "new", "treatment", "for", "Alzheimer", "'", "s", "disease", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "President Johnson delivers annual State of the Union address.", "tokens": ["President", "Johnson", "delivers", "annual", "State", "of", "the", "Union", "address", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "NASA launches new Mars rover mission.", "tokens": ["NASA", "launches", "new", "Mars", "rover", "mission", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Prime Minister Lee visits South Korea to discuss trade agreements.", "tokens": ["Prime", "Minister", "Lee", "visits", "South", "Korea", "to", "discuss", "trade", "agreements", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "I-person", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tennis star Serena Williams wins Wimbledon championship.", "tokens": ["Tennis", "star", "Serena", "Williams", "wins", "Wimbledon", "championship", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "B-location", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "A new study reveals the impact of climate change on polar bears in the Arctic.", "tokens": ["A", "new", "study", "reveals", "the", "impact", "of", "climate", "change", "on", "polar", "bears", "in", "the", "Arctic", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
