{"sentence": "New York City's unemployment rate drops to 4.2 percent, signaling a strong job market recovery.", "tokens": ["New", "York", "City", "'", "s", "unemployment", "rate", "drops", "to", "4", ".", "2", "percent", ",", "signaling", "a", "strong", "job", "market", "recovery", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tokyo stock market sees a 3% increase following positive corporate earnings reports.", "tokens": ["Tokyo", "stock", "market", "sees", "a", "3", "%", "increase", "following", "positive", "corporate", "earnings", "reports", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The New York City Chamber of Commerce reports a 10% increase in small business openings in the past year.", "tokens": ["The", "New", "York", "City", "Chamber", "of", "Commerce", "reports", "a", "10", "%", "increase", "in", "small", "business", "openings", "in", "the", "past", "year", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Art Institute of Chicago unveils new digital art collection.", "tokens": ["Art", "Institute", "of", "Chicago", "unveils", "new", "digital", "art", "collection", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Renowned artist to create a new mural for the Public Art Fund in Rome.", "tokens": ["Renowned", "artist", "to", "create", "a", "new", "mural", "for", "the", "Public", "Art", "Fund", "in", "Rome", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "LeBron James scores 30 points to lead Lakers to victory at Madison Square Garden, New York City.", "tokens": ["LeBron", "James", "scores", "30", "points", "to", "lead", "Lakers", "to", "victory", "at", "Madison", "Square", "Garden", ",", "New", "York", "City", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Madison Square Garden, New York City, to host the World Heavyweight Championship boxing match next month.", "tokens": ["Madison", "Square", "Garden", ",", "New", "York", "City", ",", "to", "host", "the", "World", "Heavyweight", "Championship", "boxing", "match", "next", "month", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "New York City Marathon sees record number of participants crossing the finish line at Central Park, near Madison Square Garden.", "tokens": ["New", "York", "City", "Marathon", "sees", "record", "number", "of", "participants", "crossing", "the", "finish", "line", "at", "Central", "Park", ",", "near", "Madison", "Square", "Garden", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The Louvre Museum acquires a rare painting by Indian artist.", "tokens": ["The", "Louvre", "Museum", "acquires", "a", "rare", "painting", "by", "Indian", "artist", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Renowned Indian sculptor to debut exhibit at Taj Mahal.", "tokens": ["Renowned", "Indian", "sculptor", "to", "debut", "exhibit", "at", "Taj", "Mahal", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Art installation inspired by the Taj Mahal to be displayed in India.", "tokens": ["Art", "installation", "inspired", "by", "the", "Taj", "Mahal", "to", "be", "displayed", "in", "India", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Annette Winkler appointed as the new CEO of a major automotive company.", "tokens": ["Annette", "Winkler", "appointed", "as", "the", "new", "CEO", "of", "a", "major", "automotive", "company", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "William C. Durant's pioneering contributions to the automotive industry remembered on his birth anniversary.", "tokens": ["William", "C", ".", "Durant", "'", "s", "pioneering", "contributions", "to", "the", "automotive", "industry", "remembered", "on", "his", "birth", "anniversary", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "I-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The automotive industry pays tribute to Annette Winkler for her innovative leadership and vision.", "tokens": ["The", "automotive", "industry", "pays", "tribute", "to", "Annette", "Winkler", "for", "her", "innovative", "leadership", "and", "vision", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "A new study conducted by Dr. Jane Smith finds a correlation between higher education funding and student achievement.", "tokens": ["A", "new", "study", "conducted", "by", "Dr", ".", "Jane", "Smith", "finds", "a", "correlation", "between", "higher", "education", "funding", "and", "student", "achievement", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "I-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The Department of Education announced a partnership with Dr. Jane Smith to improve the quality of early childhood education across the country.", "tokens": ["The", "Department", "of", "Education", "announced", "a", "partnership", "with", "Dr", ".", "Jane", "Smith", "to", "improve", "the", "quality", "of", "early", "childhood", "education", "across", "the", "country", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "I-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Environmental activist Bill McKibben urges global action to protect the Amazon Rainforest.", "tokens": ["Environmental", "activist", "Bill", "McKibben", "urges", "global", "action", "to", "protect", "the", "Amazon", "Rainforest", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Study shows deforestation in the Amazon Rainforest accelerating at an alarming rate.", "tokens": ["Study", "shows", "deforestation", "in", "the", "Amazon", "Rainforest", "accelerating", "at", "an", "alarming", "rate", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "International organization launches campaign to preserve the biodiversity of the Amazon Rainforest.", "tokens": ["International", "organization", "launches", "campaign", "to", "preserve", "the", "biodiversity", "of", "the", "Amazon", "Rainforest", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Poland wins legal battle to continue logging in Bialowieza Forest.", "tokens": ["Poland", "wins", "legal", "battle", "to", "continue", "logging", "in", "Bialowieza", "Forest", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The Everglades facing threat from invasive species, experts warn.", "tokens": ["The", "Everglades", "facing", "threat", "from", "invasive", "species", ",", "experts", "warn", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "David Sheldrick Wildlife Trust rescues and rehabilitates orphaned elephants in Kenya.", "tokens": ["David", "Sheldrick", "Wildlife", "Trust", "rescues", "and", "rehabilitates", "orphaned", "elephants", "in", "Kenya", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Toronto experiences record-breaking heat wave, with temperatures reaching 40°C.", "tokens": ["Toronto", "experiences", "record", "-", "breaking", "heat", "wave", ",", "with", "temperatures", "reaching", "40", "°", "C", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Kim Jong Un announces plans for historic summit with South Korea.", "tokens": ["Kim", "Jong", "Un", "announces", "plans", "for", "historic", "summit", "with", "South", "Korea", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Mass shooting in downtown Toronto leaves five dead and several injured.", "tokens": ["Mass", "shooting", "in", "downtown", "Toronto", "leaves", "five", "dead", "and", "several", "injured", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The World Health Organization congratulates Greta Thunberg for her efforts to raise awareness about climate change.", "tokens": ["The", "World", "Health", "Organization", "congratulates", "Greta", "Thunberg", "for", "her", "efforts", "to", "raise", "awareness", "about", "climate", "change", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The government announced a new initiative to improve access to mental health services for adolescents, following Greta Thunberg's advocacy for youth mental health.", "tokens": ["The", "government", "announced", "a", "new", "initiative", "to", "improve", "access", "to", "mental", "health", "services", "for", "adolescents", ",", "following", "Greta", "Thunberg", "'", "s", "advocacy", "for", "youth", "mental", "health", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Oxfam report reveals alarming rise in global income inequality.", "tokens": ["Oxfam", "report", "reveals", "alarming", "rise", "in", "global", "income", "inequality", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Oxfam's latest study highlights the impact of gender inequality on poverty levels.", "tokens": ["Oxfam", "'", "s", "latest", "study", "highlights", "the", "impact", "of", "gender", "inequality", "on", "poverty", "levels", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Government accused of ignoring Oxfam's warnings about increasing homelessness.", "tokens": ["Government", "accused", "of", "ignoring", "Oxfam", "'", "s", "warnings", "about", "increasing", "homelessness", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Miami police department announces new community outreach program.", "tokens": ["Miami", "police", "department", "announces", "new", "community", "outreach", "program", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Local Miami artist wins prestigious national art award.", "tokens": ["Local", "Miami", "artist", "wins", "prestigious", "national", "art", "award", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-location", "B-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Miami residents express concerns over rising sea levels and coastal erosion.", "tokens": ["Miami", "residents", "express", "concerns", "over", "rising", "sea", "levels", "and", "coastal", "erosion", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Sao Paulo Stock Exchange sets new record as economic indicators point to strong growth.", "tokens": ["Sao", "Paulo", "Stock", "Exchange", "sets", "new", "record", "as", "economic", "indicators", "point", "to", "strong", "growth", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Investors flock to Sao Paulo Stock Exchange as inflation rates remain stable.", "tokens": ["Investors", "flock", "to", "Sao", "Paulo", "Stock", "Exchange", "as", "inflation", "rates", "remain", "stable", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Sao Paulo Stock Exchange reacts positively to government's new economic policies.", "tokens": ["Sao", "Paulo", "Stock", "Exchange", "reacts", "positively", "to", "government", "'", "s", "new", "economic", "policies", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Detroit police arrest three suspects in connection with a series of robberies in the downtown area.", "tokens": ["Detroit", "police", "arrest", "three", "suspects", "in", "connection", "with", "a", "series", "of", "robberies", "in", "the", "downtown", "area", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Gun violence continues to plague Detroit neighborhoods, with multiple shootings reported over the weekend.", "tokens": ["Gun", "violence", "continues", "to", "plague", "Detroit", "neighborhoods", ",", "with", "multiple", "shootings", "reported", "over", "the", "weekend", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Authorities in Detroit are investigating a string of carjackings targeting drivers in the East side of the city.", "tokens": ["Authorities", "in", "Detroit", "are", "investigating", "a", "string", "of", "carjackings", "targeting", "drivers", "in", "the", "East", "side", "of", "the", "city", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Cape Town to experience heavy rainfall and strong winds in the coming week.", "tokens": ["Cape", "Town", "to", "experience", "heavy", "rainfall", "and", "strong", "winds", "in", "the", "coming", "week", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Severe snowstorm hits the Himalayas, causing travel disruptions and power outages.", "tokens": ["Severe", "snowstorm", "hits", "the", "Himalayas", ",", "causing", "travel", "disruptions", "and", "power", "outages", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Olympic gymnast Simone Biles donates $100,000 for relief efforts in areas affected by extreme weather.", "tokens": ["Olympic", "gymnast", "Simone", "Biles", "donates", "$", "100", ",", "000", "for", "relief", "efforts", "in", "areas", "affected", "by", "extreme", "weather", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "New health and wellness center opening in Mumbai to promote healthy living and fitness.", "tokens": ["New", "health", "and", "wellness", "center", "opening", "in", "Mumbai", "to", "promote", "healthy", "living", "and", "fitness", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Actress from Mumbai spotted shopping in Los Angeles, setting a new fashion trend.", "tokens": ["Actress", "from", "Mumbai", "spotted", "shopping", "in", "Los", "Angeles", ",", "setting", "a", "new", "fashion", "trend", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Renowned celebrity chef from Los Angeles to launch a new restaurant concept in Mumbai.", "tokens": ["Renowned", "celebrity", "chef", "from", "Los", "Angeles", "to", "launch", "a", "new", "restaurant", "concept", "in", "Mumbai", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Joe Biden spotted at National Basketball Association game.", "tokens": ["Joe", "Biden", "spotted", "at", "National", "Basketball", "Association", "game", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "New study shows correlation between exercise and mental health.", "tokens": ["New", "study", "shows", "correlation", "between", "exercise", "and", "mental", "health", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Local yoga studio offering free classes for healthcare workers.", "tokens": ["Local", "yoga", "studio", "offering", "free", "classes", "for", "healthcare", "workers", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Fashion designers from around the world showcase their latest creations at the prestigious Paris Fashion Week.", "tokens": ["Fashion", "designers", "from", "around", "the", "world", "showcase", "their", "latest", "creations", "at", "the", "prestigious", "Paris", "Fashion", "Week", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The bustling shopping districts of Tokyo attract fashion enthusiasts with their eclectic mix of traditional and cutting-edge styles.", "tokens": ["The", "bustling", "shopping", "districts", "of", "Tokyo", "attract", "fashion", "enthusiasts", "with", "their", "eclectic", "mix", "of", "traditional", "and", "cutting", "-", "edge", "styles", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Luxury fashion brands open flagship stores in The Dubai Mall, catering to the affluent clientele of the Middle East.", "tokens": ["Luxury", "fashion", "brands", "open", "flagship", "stores", "in", "The", "Dubai", "Mall", ",", "catering", "to", "the", "affluent", "clientele", "of", "the", "Middle", "East", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "New report reveals alarming levels of air pollution in major cities, prompting calls for government action.", "tokens": ["New", "report", "reveals", "alarming", "levels", "of", "air", "pollution", "in", "major", "cities", ",", "prompting", "calls", "for", "government", "action", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Environmental group files lawsuit against corporation for alleged toxic waste dumping, citing violations of federal regulations.", "tokens": ["Environmental", "group", "files", "lawsuit", "against", "corporation", "for", "alleged", "toxic", "waste", "dumping", ",", "citing", "violations", "of", "federal", "regulations", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Violent protests erupt in Rio de Janeiro following controversial government decision.", "tokens": ["Violent", "protests", "erupt", "in", "Rio", "de", "Janeiro", "following", "controversial", "government", "decision", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Rio de Janeiro Mayor declares state of emergency in response to record-breaking heatwave.", "tokens": ["Rio", "de", "Janeiro", "Mayor", "declares", "state", "of", "emergency", "in", "response", "to", "record", "-", "breaking", "heatwave", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Rio de Janeiro police chief resigns amidst corruption scandal.", "tokens": ["Rio", "de", "Janeiro", "police", "chief", "resigns", "amidst", "corruption", "scandal", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Twitter chairman resigns amid pressure from activist investors.", "tokens": ["Twitter", "chairman", "resigns", "amid", "pressure", "from", "activist", "investors", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Amazon announces plans to invest $1.2 billion in building new data centers.", "tokens": ["Amazon", "announces", "plans", "to", "invest", "$", "1", ".", "2", "billion", "in", "building", "new", "data", "centers", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tech giant Twitter unveils new feature to combat misinformation on its platform.", "tokens": ["Tech", "giant", "Twitter", "unveils", "new", "feature", "to", "combat", "misinformation", "on", "its", "platform", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Taylor Swift wins Grammy for Album of the Year.", "tokens": ["Taylor", "Swift", "wins", "Grammy", "for", "Album", "of", "the", "Year", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Hollywood blockbuster 'Mystic River' to be adapted into a TV series.", "tokens": ["Hollywood", "blockbuster", "'", "Mystic", "River", "'", "to", "be", "adapted", "into", "a", "TV", "series", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Brad Pitt and Angelina Jolie to star in new romantic comedy together.", "tokens": ["Brad", "Pitt", "and", "Angelina", "Jolie", "to", "star", "in", "new", "romantic", "comedy", "together", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tesla Motors unveils new electric vehicle with longer range and faster charging capabilities.", "tokens": ["Tesla", "Motors", "unveils", "new", "electric", "vehicle", "with", "longer", "range", "and", "faster", "charging", "capabilities", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Ford announces plans to invest $22 billion in electric vehicle production over the next five years, aiming to transition its lineup to all-electric models.", "tokens": ["Ford", "announces", "plans", "to", "invest", "$", "22", "billion", "in", "electric", "vehicle", "production", "over", "the", "next", "five", "years", ",", "aiming", "to", "transition", "its", "lineup", "to", "all", "-", "electric", "models", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Renowned automotive designer, John Smith, set to debut cutting-edge concept car at upcoming international auto show.", "tokens": ["Renowned", "automotive", "designer", ",", "John", "Smith", ",", "set", "to", "debut", "cutting", "-", "edge", "concept", "car", "at", "upcoming", "international", "auto", "show", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The Buddhist Peace Fellowship organizes a meditation retreat for peace and social justice.", "tokens": ["The", "Buddhist", "Peace", "Fellowship", "organizes", "a", "meditation", "retreat", "for", "peace", "and", "social", "justice", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The Dalai Lama to speak at the annual conference hosted by the Buddhist Peace Fellowship.", "tokens": ["The", "Dalai", "Lama", "to", "speak", "at", "the", "annual", "conference", "hosted", "by", "the", "Buddhist", "Peace", "Fellowship", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Local Buddhist Peace Fellowship chapter raises funds for humanitarian aid in Myanmar.", "tokens": ["Local", "Buddhist", "Peace", "Fellowship", "chapter", "raises", "funds", "for", "humanitarian", "aid", "in", "Myanmar", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "American Civil Liberties Union files lawsuit against government over immigration policy.", "tokens": ["American", "Civil", "Liberties", "Union", "files", "lawsuit", "against", "government", "over", "immigration", "policy", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "New immigration bill proposed by American Civil Liberties Union aims to protect undocumented immigrants.", "tokens": ["New", "immigration", "bill", "proposed", "by", "American", "Civil", "Liberties", "Union", "aims", "to", "protect", "undocumented", "immigrants", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Immigration rights rally organized by American Civil Liberties Union draws thousands to Washington D.C.", "tokens": ["Immigration", "rights", "rally", "organized", "by", "American", "Civil", "Liberties", "Union", "draws", "thousands", "to", "Washington", "D", ".", "C", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "I-location", "I-location"]}
{"sentence": "Anna Wintour steps down as editor-in-chief of Vogue after 32 years.", "tokens": ["Anna", "Wintour", "steps", "down", "as", "editor", "-", "in", "-", "chief", "of", "Vogue", "after", "32", "years", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Fashion industry leaders gather in Paris for the annual runway shows.", "tokens": ["Fashion", "industry", "leaders", "gather", "in", "Paris", "for", "the", "annual", "runway", "shows", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Anna Wintour's impact on the fashion world discussed in new documentary.", "tokens": ["Anna", "Wintour", "'", "s", "impact", "on", "the", "fashion", "world", "discussed", "in", "new", "documentary", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tesla's CEO Elon Musk announces plan to expand company's production in China.", "tokens": ["Tesla", "'", "s", "CEO", "Elon", "Musk", "announces", "plan", "to", "expand", "company", "'", "s", "production", "in", "China", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Global retail giant Walmart reports record-breaking quarterly profits.", "tokens": ["Global", "retail", "giant", "Walmart", "reports", "record", "-", "breaking", "quarterly", "profits", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Stock market experiences sharp decline as fears of inflation rise.", "tokens": ["Stock", "market", "experiences", "sharp", "decline", "as", "fears", "of", "inflation", "rise", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Los Angeles police arrest three suspects in connection with a string of violent robberies.", "tokens": ["Los", "Angeles", "police", "arrest", "three", "suspects", "in", "connection", "with", "a", "string", "of", "violent", "robberies", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "California man sentenced to 20 years in prison for drug trafficking.", "tokens": ["California", "man", "sentenced", "to", "20", "years", "in", "prison", "for", "drug", "trafficking", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Police investigate shooting at a nightclub in downtown Los Angeles.", "tokens": ["Police", "investigate", "shooting", "at", "a", "nightclub", "in", "downtown", "Los", "Angeles", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The Migration Policy Institute releases new report on the impact of immigration on the US economy.", "tokens": ["The", "Migration", "Policy", "Institute", "releases", "new", "report", "on", "the", "impact", "of", "immigration", "on", "the", "US", "economy", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Immigration reform bill proposed by senators backed by the Migration Policy Institute.", "tokens": ["Immigration", "reform", "bill", "proposed", "by", "senators", "backed", "by", "the", "Migration", "Policy", "Institute", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-person", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O"]}
{"sentence": "New study by the Migration Policy Institute reveals the challenges faced by immigrants in accessing healthcare services.", "tokens": ["New", "study", "by", "the", "Migration", "Policy", "Institute", "reveals", "the", "challenges", "faced", "by", "immigrants", "in", "accessing", "healthcare", "services", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "LeBron James scores a game-winning three-pointer to lead the Lakers to victory over the Warriors.", "tokens": ["LeBron", "James", "scores", "a", "game", "-", "winning", "three", "-", "pointer", "to", "lead", "the", "Lakers", "to", "victory", "over", "the", "Warriors", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The New York Yankees sign a record-breaking contract with All-Star pitcher.", "tokens": ["The", "New", "York", "Yankees", "sign", "a", "record", "-", "breaking", "contract", "with", "All", "-", "Star", "pitcher", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Simone Biles makes history with her incredible performance at the Gymnastics World Championships.", "tokens": ["Simone", "Biles", "makes", "history", "with", "her", "incredible", "performance", "at", "the", "Gymnastics", "World", "Championships", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Al-Qaeda claims responsibility for the 1998 U.S. embassy bombings in East Africa.", "tokens": ["Al", "-", "Qaeda", "claims", "responsibility", "for", "the", "1998", "U", ".", "S", ".", "embassy", "bombings", "in", "East", "Africa", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Former Al-Qaeda member provides insight into the organization's founding and early activities.", "tokens": ["Former", "Al", "-", "Qaeda", "member", "provides", "insight", "into", "the", "organization", "'", "s", "founding", "and", "early", "activities", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Lebron James signs a multi-million dollar contract with the Los Angeles Lakers.", "tokens": ["Lebron", "James", "signs", "a", "multi", "-", "million", "dollar", "contract", "with", "the", "Los", "Angeles", "Lakers", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The Tokyo Olympics committee announces new safety measures for the upcoming Games.", "tokens": ["The", "Tokyo", "Olympics", "committee", "announces", "new", "safety", "measures", "for", "the", "upcoming", "Games", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Serena Williams makes a stunning comeback at the US Open, securing her spot in the semi-finals.", "tokens": ["Serena", "Williams", "makes", "a", "stunning", "comeback", "at", "the", "US", "Open", ",", "securing", "her", "spot", "in", "the", "semi", "-", "finals", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "United We Dream organizes protest for immigrant rights in downtown Los Angeles.", "tokens": ["United", "We", "Dream", "organizes", "protest", "for", "immigrant", "rights", "in", "downtown", "Los", "Angeles", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Anti-Defamation League releases report on anti-immigrant sentiment in the U.S.", "tokens": ["Anti", "-", "Defamation", "League", "releases", "report", "on", "anti", "-", "immigrant", "sentiment", "in", "the", "U", ".", "S", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "I-location"]}
{"sentence": "Immigrant family reunites after years of separation due to immigration policies.", "tokens": ["Immigrant", "family", "reunites", "after", "years", "of", "separation", "due", "to", "immigration", "policies", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Principal David Lee resigns amid allegations of financial mismanagement at local high school.", "tokens": ["Principal", "David", "Lee", "resigns", "amid", "allegations", "of", "financial", "mismanagement", "at", "local", "high", "school", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Sydney Opera House to host international education summit with top researchers and policy makers.", "tokens": ["Sydney", "Opera", "House", "to", "host", "international", "education", "summit", "with", "top", "researchers", "and", "policy", "makers", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "New report from National Student Clearinghouse reveals decline in college enrollment rates across the country.", "tokens": ["New", "report", "from", "National", "Student", "Clearinghouse", "reveals", "decline", "in", "college", "enrollment", "rates", "across", "the", "country", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Jennifer Lopez to visit Angkor Wat in Cambodia for her next music video.", "tokens": ["Jennifer", "Lopez", "to", "visit", "Angkor", "Wat", "in", "Cambodia", "for", "her", "next", "music", "video", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "American Society of Travel Agents announces new tour packages to Cambodia's Angkor Wat.", "tokens": ["American", "Society", "of", "Travel", "Agents", "announces", "new", "tour", "packages", "to", "Cambodia", "'", "s", "Angkor", "Wat", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Cambodia sees a surge in tourism as travelers flock to visit Angkor Wat.", "tokens": ["Cambodia", "sees", "a", "surge", "in", "tourism", "as", "travelers", "flock", "to", "visit", "Angkor", "Wat", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The upcoming film festival will feature the latest works from renowned directors around the world.", "tokens": ["The", "upcoming", "film", "festival", "will", "feature", "the", "latest", "works", "from", "renowned", "directors", "around", "the", "world", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Oscar-winning actress Emma Stone to star in the new biopic about the life of astronaut Sally Ride.", "tokens": ["Oscar", "-", "winning", "actress", "Emma", "Stone", "to", "star", "in", "the", "new", "biopic", "about", "the", "life", "of", "astronaut", "Sally", "Ride", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Venice, Italy selected as the location for the shooting of the highly-anticipated action film sequel.", "tokens": ["Venice", ",", "Italy", "selected", "as", "the", "location", "for", "the", "shooting", "of", "the", "highly", "-", "anticipated", "action", "film", "sequel", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "American Atheists sue school district over prayer in classrooms.", "tokens": ["American", "Atheists", "sue", "school", "district", "over", "prayer", "in", "classrooms", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Survey shows growing number of Americans identifying as atheists.", "tokens": ["Survey", "shows", "growing", "number", "of", "Americans", "identifying", "as", "atheists", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "B-person", "O"]}
{"sentence": "American Atheists hold rally in support of separation of church and state.", "tokens": ["American", "Atheists", "hold", "rally", "in", "support", "of", "separation", "of", "church", "and", "state", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Beyoncé to headline virtual concert in support of Black-owned businesses.", "tokens": ["Beyoncé", "to", "headline", "virtual", "concert", "in", "support", "of", "Black", "-", "owned", "businesses", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Cardi B launches new fashion line in collaboration with luxury brand.", "tokens": ["Cardi", "B", "launches", "new", "fashion", "line", "in", "collaboration", "with", "luxury", "brand", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Royal Caribbean International announces partnership with popular TV show for new cruise entertainment.", "tokens": ["Royal", "Caribbean", "International", "announces", "partnership", "with", "popular", "TV", "show", "for", "new", "cruise", "entertainment", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Bank of America Corporation announces plans to expand its presence in Sydney.", "tokens": ["Bank", "of", "America", "Corporation", "announces", "plans", "to", "expand", "its", "presence", "in", "Sydney", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Sydney stock market experiences a surge in trading volume as investors react to economic indicators.", "tokens": ["Sydney", "stock", "market", "experiences", "a", "surge", "in", "trading", "volume", "as", "investors", "react", "to", "economic", "indicators", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Bank of America Corporation reports record-breaking profits in the latest fiscal quarter.", "tokens": ["Bank", "of", "America", "Corporation", "reports", "record", "-", "breaking", "profits", "in", "the", "latest", "fiscal", "quarter", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "United Nations Economic Commission for Europe predicts strong economic growth for Australia in the next quarter.", "tokens": ["United", "Nations", "Economic", "Commission", "for", "Europe", "predicts", "strong", "economic", "growth", "for", "Australia", "in", "the", "next", "quarter", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Nissan announces plans to invest in new manufacturing facilities, boosting the economy in the Midwest.", "tokens": ["Nissan", "announces", "plans", "to", "invest", "in", "new", "manufacturing", "facilities", ",", "boosting", "the", "economy", "in", "the", "Midwest", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Australia's economic recovery surpasses expectations, with the United Nations Economic Commission for Europe praising the government's policies.", "tokens": ["Australia", "'", "s", "economic", "recovery", "surpasses", "expectations", ",", "with", "the", "United", "Nations", "Economic", "Commission", "for", "Europe", "praising", "the", "government", "'", "s", "policies", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The renowned author Virginia Woolf's novels continue to be celebrated for their innovative narrative techniques and exploration of modernist themes.", "tokens": ["The", "renowned", "author", "Virginia", "Woolf", "'", "s", "novels", "continue", "to", "be", "celebrated", "for", "their", "innovative", "narrative", "techniques", "and", "exploration", "of", "modernist", "themes", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "A new biography reveals previously unknown details about Virginia Woolf's personal life and the impact it had on her literary works.", "tokens": ["A", "new", "biography", "reveals", "previously", "unknown", "details", "about", "Virginia", "Woolf", "'", "s", "personal", "life", "and", "the", "impact", "it", "had", "on", "her", "literary", "works", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Literary scholars gather at a conference to discuss the enduring legacy of Virginia Woolf and her contributions to the development of feminist literature.", "tokens": ["Literary", "scholars", "gather", "at", "a", "conference", "to", "discuss", "the", "enduring", "legacy", "of", "Virginia", "Woolf", "and", "her", "contributions", "to", "the", "development", "of", "feminist", "literature", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Fashion designer Stella McCartney launches new sustainable clothing line.", "tokens": ["Fashion", "designer", "Stella", "McCartney", "launches", "new", "sustainable", "clothing", "line", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Paris becomes the epicenter of global fashion as haute couture takes the spotlight.", "tokens": ["Paris", "becomes", "the", "epicenter", "of", "global", "fashion", "as", "haute", "couture", "takes", "the", "spotlight", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The European Union reaches a new trade agreement with Turkey, easing tensions in Ankara.", "tokens": ["The", "European", "Union", "reaches", "a", "new", "trade", "agreement", "with", "Turkey", ",", "easing", "tensions", "in", "Ankara", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Ilhan Omar calls for bipartisan support to address immigration reform in Congress.", "tokens": ["Ilhan", "Omar", "calls", "for", "bipartisan", "support", "to", "address", "immigration", "reform", "in", "Congress", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Turkey's president criticized the European Union for what he called a lack of support in handling the refugee crisis in Ankara.", "tokens": ["Turkey", "'", "s", "president", "criticized", "the", "European", "Union", "for", "what", "he", "called", "a", "lack", "of", "support", "in", "handling", "the", "refugee", "crisis", "in", "Ankara", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Teach for America expands its program to Johannesburg, South Africa.", "tokens": ["Teach", "for", "America", "expands", "its", "program", "to", "Johannesburg", ",", "South", "Africa", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "University of Cape Town partners with Teach for America to improve education in South Africa.", "tokens": ["University", "of", "Cape", "Town", "partners", "with", "Teach", "for", "America", "to", "improve", "education", "in", "South", "Africa", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Teach for America CEO discusses plans to address education disparities in Johannesburg.", "tokens": ["Teach", "for", "America", "CEO", "discusses", "plans", "to", "address", "education", "disparities", "in", "Johannesburg", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "B-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Veterans of Foreign Wars to hold annual memorial service for fallen soldiers.", "tokens": ["Veterans", "of", "Foreign", "Wars", "to", "hold", "annual", "memorial", "service", "for", "fallen", "soldiers", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Army National Guard troops deployed to support humanitarian relief efforts in hurricane-ravaged areas.", "tokens": ["Army", "National", "Guard", "troops", "deployed", "to", "support", "humanitarian", "relief", "efforts", "in", "hurricane", "-", "ravaged", "areas", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "National Military Museum opens new exhibition featuring the history of the Armed Forces.", "tokens": ["National", "Military", "Museum", "opens", "new", "exhibition", "featuring", "the", "history", "of", "the", "Armed", "Forces", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Researchers from the United Nations Environment Programme discover new species of coral in the depths of the Pacific Ocean.", "tokens": ["Researchers", "from", "the", "United", "Nations", "Environment", "Programme", "discover", "new", "species", "of", "coral", "in", "the", "depths", "of", "the", "Pacific", "Ocean", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Scientists working with the United Nations Environment Programme predict a significant increase in global temperatures by the end of the century.", "tokens": ["Scientists", "working", "with", "the", "United", "Nations", "Environment", "Programme", "predict", "a", "significant", "increase", "in", "global", "temperatures", "by", "the", "end", "of", "the", "century", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "New study supported by the United Nations Environment Programme shows the alarming rate of deforestation in the Amazon rainforest.", "tokens": ["New", "study", "supported", "by", "the", "United", "Nations", "Environment", "Programme", "shows", "the", "alarming", "rate", "of", "deforestation", "in", "the", "Amazon", "rainforest", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Buenos Aires Marathon sees record number of participants this year.", "tokens": ["Buenos", "Aires", "Marathon", "sees", "record", "number", "of", "participants", "this", "year", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Augusta National Golf Club announces plans for major renovation ahead of next year's Masters tournament.", "tokens": ["Augusta", "National", "Golf", "Club", "announces", "plans", "for", "major", "renovation", "ahead", "of", "next", "year", "'", "s", "Masters", "tournament", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Promising young athlete from Georgia breaks high school track record in 100m dash.", "tokens": ["Promising", "young", "athlete", "from", "Georgia", "breaks", "high", "school", "track", "record", "in", "100m", "dash", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Universal Pictures releases highly anticipated blockbuster movie.", "tokens": ["Universal", "Pictures", "releases", "highly", "anticipated", "blockbuster", "movie", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Famous actor signs multi-picture deal with Universal Pictures.", "tokens": ["Famous", "actor", "signs", "multi", "-", "picture", "deal", "with", "Universal", "Pictures", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Upcoming film festival to feature exclusive screenings of Universal Pictures' latest releases.", "tokens": ["Upcoming", "film", "festival", "to", "feature", "exclusive", "screenings", "of", "Universal", "Pictures", "'", "latest", "releases", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Beijing Normal University launches new online education platform.", "tokens": ["Beijing", "Normal", "University", "launches", "new", "online", "education", "platform", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Researchers at Beijing Normal University discover link between physical activity and academic performance.", "tokens": ["Researchers", "at", "Beijing", "Normal", "University", "discover", "link", "between", "physical", "activity", "and", "academic", "performance", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Beijing Normal University ranked top in education research and innovation.", "tokens": ["Beijing", "Normal", "University", "ranked", "top", "in", "education", "research", "and", "innovation", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Richard Branson's Virgin Galactic successfully launches its first manned spaceflight.", "tokens": ["Richard", "Branson", "'", "s", "Virgin", "Galactic", "successfully", "launches", "its", "first", "manned", "spaceflight", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "SpaceX announces partnership with Richard Branson's Virgin Orbit for satellite launches.", "tokens": ["SpaceX", "announces", "partnership", "with", "Richard", "Branson", "'", "s", "Virgin", "Orbit", "for", "satellite", "launches", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Renowned entrepreneur Richard Branson invests in new clean energy technology startup.", "tokens": ["Renowned", "entrepreneur", "Richard", "Branson", "invests", "in", "new", "clean", "energy", "technology", "startup", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tom Hanks to star in new film celebrating Berlin's cultural heritage.", "tokens": ["Tom", "Hanks", "to", "star", "in", "new", "film", "celebrating", "Berlin", "'", "s", "cultural", "heritage", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Renowned chef to open new restaurant in the heart of Berlin's artistic district.", "tokens": ["Renowned", "chef", "to", "open", "new", "restaurant", "in", "the", "heart", "of", "Berlin", "'", "s", "artistic", "district", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Volkswagen Group announces plans to invest $2 billion in electric vehicle production.", "tokens": ["Volkswagen", "Group", "announces", "plans", "to", "invest", "$", "2", "billion", "in", "electric", "vehicle", "production", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The latest automotive recall affects over 100,000 vehicles manufactured by Volkswagen Group.", "tokens": ["The", "latest", "automotive", "recall", "affects", "over", "100", ",", "000", "vehicles", "manufactured", "by", "Volkswagen", "Group", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Volkswagen Group partners with a major tech company to develop autonomous driving technology for their vehicles.", "tokens": ["Volkswagen", "Group", "partners", "with", "a", "major", "tech", "company", "to", "develop", "autonomous", "driving", "technology", "for", "their", "vehicles", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "United States Department of Defense announces new cyber security initiative.", "tokens": ["United", "States", "Department", "of", "Defense", "announces", "new", "cyber", "security", "initiative", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tensions rise between India and Pakistan after the Delhi bombing.", "tokens": ["Tensions", "rise", "between", "India", "and", "Pakistan", "after", "the", "Delhi", "bombing", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "United States Department of Defense deploys additional troops to the Middle East.", "tokens": ["United", "States", "Department", "of", "Defense", "deploys", "additional", "troops", "to", "the", "Middle", "East", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "United Nations High Commissioner for Refugees reports increase in number of asylum seekers at border.", "tokens": ["United", "Nations", "High", "Commissioner", "for", "Refugees", "reports", "increase", "in", "number", "of", "asylum", "seekers", "at", "border", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Australian Defence Force deploys troops to Fort Bragg for joint military training.", "tokens": ["Australian", "Defence", "Force", "deploys", "troops", "to", "Fort", "Bragg", "for", "joint", "military", "training", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "North Carolina National Guard partners with Australian Defence Force for disaster relief exercise.", "tokens": ["North", "Carolina", "National", "Guard", "partners", "with", "Australian", "Defence", "Force", "for", "disaster", "relief", "exercise", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Joint military exercise at Fort Bragg strengthens ties between Australian Defence Force and US Army.", "tokens": ["Joint", "military", "exercise", "at", "Fort", "Bragg", "strengthens", "ties", "between", "Australian", "Defence", "Force", "and", "US", "Army", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The National Center for Education Statistics reports a decline in high school graduation rates.", "tokens": ["The", "National", "Center", "for", "Education", "Statistics", "reports", "a", "decline", "in", "high", "school", "graduation", "rates", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The National Council of Teachers of English is launching a new literacy program in urban schools.", "tokens": ["The", "National", "Council", "of", "Teachers", "of", "English", "is", "launching", "a", "new", "literacy", "program", "in", "urban", "schools", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "A study by the National Center for Education Statistics reveals a widening achievement gap among students in rural areas.", "tokens": ["A", "study", "by", "the", "National", "Center", "for", "Education", "Statistics", "reveals", "a", "widening", "achievement", "gap", "among", "students", "in", "rural", "areas", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The Rainforest Action Network launches campaign to protect biodiversity in the Amazon rainforest.", "tokens": ["The", "Rainforest", "Action", "Network", "launches", "campaign", "to", "protect", "biodiversity", "in", "the", "Amazon", "rainforest", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Everglades National Park announces plan to restore wetlands and improve wildlife habitat.", "tokens": ["Everglades", "National", "Park", "announces", "plan", "to", "restore", "wetlands", "and", "improve", "wildlife", "habitat", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Environmentalist group partners with local schools to educate students on the importance of preserving the Everglades National Park.", "tokens": ["Environmentalist", "group", "partners", "with", "local", "schools", "to", "educate", "students", "on", "the", "importance", "of", "preserving", "the", "Everglades", "National", "Park", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "I-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Dubai police arrest international drug trafficker.", "tokens": ["Dubai", "police", "arrest", "international", "drug", "trafficker", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Immigration and Customs Enforcement cracks down on human trafficking ring.", "tokens": ["Immigration", "and", "Customs", "Enforcement", "cracks", "down", "on", "human", "trafficking", "ring", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "National Center for Missing and Exploited Children aids in the rescue of child kidnapping victim.", "tokens": ["National", "Center", "for", "Missing", "and", "Exploited", "Children", "aids", "in", "the", "rescue", "of", "child", "kidnapping", "victim", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Attenborough's naturalist, Jane Goodall, to receive lifetime achievement award.", "tokens": ["Attenborough", "'", "s", "naturalist", ",", "Jane", "Goodall", ",", "to", "receive", "lifetime", "achievement", "award", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "New study shows decline in wildlife population due to climate change.", "tokens": ["New", "study", "shows", "decline", "in", "wildlife", "population", "due", "to", "climate", "change", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Attenborough's naturalist, WWF, launches campaign to protect endangered species.", "tokens": ["Attenborough", "'", "s", "naturalist", ",", "WWF", ",", "launches", "campaign", "to", "protect", "endangered", "species", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Wangari Maathai, the renowned environmentalist, is set to lead a campaign to protect the natural habitats of endangered species in Africa.", "tokens": ["Wangari", "Maathai", ",", "the", "renowned", "environmentalist", ",", "is", "set", "to", "lead", "a", "campaign", "to", "protect", "the", "natural", "habitats", "of", "endangered", "species", "in", "Africa", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The government has announced a new initiative to conserve the wildlife population, with a focus on preserving the habitats of endangered species, in honor of Wangari Maathai's legacy.", "tokens": ["The", "government", "has", "announced", "a", "new", "initiative", "to", "conserve", "the", "wildlife", "population", ",", "with", "a", "focus", "on", "preserving", "the", "habitats", "of", "endangered", "species", ",", "in", "honor", "of", "Wangari", "Maathai", "'", "s", "legacy", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "A wildlife sanctuary in Kenya, established with the support of Wangari Maathai, has successfully reintroduced several rare species back into their natural habitat.", "tokens": ["A", "wildlife", "sanctuary", "in", "Kenya", ",", "established", "with", "the", "support", "of", "Wangari", "Maathai", ",", "has", "successfully", "reintroduced", "several", "rare", "species", "back", "into", "their", "natural", "habitat", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Beyoncé announces new collaboration with Ford Motor Company to support community grants program.", "tokens": ["Beyoncé", "announces", "new", "collaboration", "with", "Ford", "Motor", "Company", "to", "support", "community", "grants", "program", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Interview with Beyoncé on her upcoming humanitarian trip to South Africa.", "tokens": ["Interview", "with", "Beyoncé", "on", "her", "upcoming", "humanitarian", "trip", "to", "South", "Africa", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Ford Motor Company CEO discusses partnership with UNICEF for global education initiatives.", "tokens": ["Ford", "Motor", "Company", "CEO", "discusses", "partnership", "with", "UNICEF", "for", "global", "education", "initiatives", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Local woman raises $10,000 for children's hospital through charity marathon.", "tokens": ["Local", "woman", "raises", "$", "10", ",", "000", "for", "children", "'", "s", "hospital", "through", "charity", "marathon", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "High school student organizes food drive to help struggling families in the community.", "tokens": ["High", "school", "student", "organizes", "food", "drive", "to", "help", "struggling", "families", "in", "the", "community", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Firefighters rescue elderly man from burning building, bringing him to safety.", "tokens": ["Firefighters", "rescue", "elderly", "man", "from", "burning", "building", ",", "bringing", "him", "to", "safety", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The American Civil Liberties Union files lawsuit on behalf of Mary Smith, alleging wrongful imprisonment.", "tokens": ["The", "American", "Civil", "Liberties", "Union", "files", "lawsuit", "on", "behalf", "of", "Mary", "Smith", ",", "alleging", "wrongful", "imprisonment", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Man arrested in connection with robbery at local convenience store, police say.", "tokens": ["Man", "arrested", "in", "connection", "with", "robbery", "at", "local", "convenience", "store", ",", "police", "say", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "American Civil Liberties Union calls for reform in juvenile justice system after recent spike in youth crime rates.", "tokens": ["American", "Civil", "Liberties", "Union", "calls", "for", "reform", "in", "juvenile", "justice", "system", "after", "recent", "spike", "in", "youth", "crime", "rates", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Legendary musician Bob Dylan to release new album next month.", "tokens": ["Legendary", "musician", "Bob", "Dylan", "to", "release", "new", "album", "next", "month", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Bob Dylan's classic album \"Highway 61 Revisited\" celebrates 55th anniversary.", "tokens": ["Bob", "Dylan", "'", "s", "classic", "album", "\"", "Highway", "61", "Revisited", "\"", "celebrates", "55th", "anniversary", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Folk singer Bob Dylan honored with prestigious music award.", "tokens": ["Folk", "singer", "Bob", "Dylan", "honored", "with", "prestigious", "music", "award", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Walt Disney World to host an exclusive concert series featuring top artists from around the world.", "tokens": ["Walt", "Disney", "World", "to", "host", "an", "exclusive", "concert", "series", "featuring", "top", "artists", "from", "around", "the", "world", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Local teenager fulfills lifelong dream of performing on stage at Walt Disney World.", "tokens": ["Local", "teenager", "fulfills", "lifelong", "dream", "of", "performing", "on", "stage", "at", "Walt", "Disney", "World", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Walt Disney World's new immersive theater experience takes audiences on a magical journey through beloved Disney classics.", "tokens": ["Walt", "Disney", "World", "'", "s", "new", "immersive", "theater", "experience", "takes", "audiences", "on", "a", "magical", "journey", "through", "beloved", "Disney", "classics", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The National Gallery of Art opens new exhibit featuring works by Monet and Renoir.", "tokens": ["The", "National", "Gallery", "of", "Art", "opens", "new", "exhibit", "featuring", "works", "by", "Monet", "and", "Renoir", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-person", "O", "B-person", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Renowned author to speak at The National Gallery of Art's literary event next week.", "tokens": ["Renowned", "author", "to", "speak", "at", "The", "National", "Gallery", "of", "Art", "'", "s", "literary", "event", "next", "week", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Renowned pastor Rick Warren to host nationwide religious event to promote unity and fellowship among diverse faith communities.", "tokens": ["Renowned", "pastor", "Rick", "Warren", "to", "host", "nationwide", "religious", "event", "to", "promote", "unity", "and", "fellowship", "among", "diverse", "faith", "communities", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Sikh American Legal Defense and Education Fund launches initiative to combat discrimination and promote religious freedom for Sikh Americans.", "tokens": ["Sikh", "American", "Legal", "Defense", "and", "Education", "Fund", "launches", "initiative", "to", "combat", "discrimination", "and", "promote", "religious", "freedom", "for", "Sikh", "Americans", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "In light of recent religious tensions, leaders of various faith-based organizations come together to discuss ways to promote understanding and tolerance in their communities.", "tokens": ["In", "light", "of", "recent", "religious", "tensions", ",", "leaders", "of", "various", "faith", "-", "based", "organizations", "come", "together", "to", "discuss", "ways", "to", "promote", "understanding", "and", "tolerance", "in", "their", "communities", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Human Rights Watch criticizes China's treatment of Uighur minority.", "tokens": ["Human", "Rights", "Watch", "criticizes", "China", "'", "s", "treatment", "of", "Uighur", "minority", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-person", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Human Rights Watch calls for investigation into alleged war crimes in Syria.", "tokens": ["Human", "Rights", "Watch", "calls", "for", "investigation", "into", "alleged", "war", "crimes", "in", "Syria", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "European Union partners with Human Rights Watch to address refugee crisis.", "tokens": ["European", "Union", "partners", "with", "Human", "Rights", "Watch", "to", "address", "refugee", "crisis", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Twitter announces new feature to combat misinformation on its platform.", "tokens": ["Twitter", "announces", "new", "feature", "to", "combat", "misinformation", "on", "its", "platform", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Tech giant Apple partners with Twitter to integrate new social media features on its devices.", "tokens": ["Tech", "giant", "Apple", "partners", "with", "Twitter", "to", "integrate", "new", "social", "media", "features", "on", "its", "devices", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Twitter CEO Jack Dorsey steps down, citing the need for new leadership to steer the company through challenging times.", "tokens": ["Twitter", "CEO", "Jack", "Dorsey", "steps", "down", ",", "citing", "the", "need", "for", "new", "leadership", "to", "steer", "the", "company", "through", "challenging", "times", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Local volunteers rally to support Red Cross relief efforts after natural disaster.", "tokens": ["Local", "volunteers", "rally", "to", "support", "Red", "Cross", "relief", "efforts", "after", "natural", "disaster", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Red Cross blood drive collects record donations in the local community.", "tokens": ["Red", "Cross", "blood", "drive", "collects", "record", "donations", "in", "the", "local", "community", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Local Red Cross chapter hosts emergency preparedness seminar for residents.", "tokens": ["Local", "Red", "Cross", "chapter", "hosts", "emergency", "preparedness", "seminar", "for", "residents", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "European Union leaders reach historic agreement on climate change goals.", "tokens": ["European", "Union", "leaders", "reach", "historic", "agreement", "on", "climate", "change", "goals", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Michael Phelps breaks Olympic record with his 23rd gold medal.", "tokens": ["Michael", "Phelps", "breaks", "Olympic", "record", "with", "his", "23rd", "gold", "medal", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Major League Baseball announces new rule changes for the upcoming season.", "tokens": ["Major", "League", "Baseball", "announces", "new", "rule", "changes", "for", "the", "upcoming", "season", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Naomi Osaka advances to the semi-finals after a stunning victory in the quarter-finals.", "tokens": ["Naomi", "Osaka", "advances", "to", "the", "semi", "-", "finals", "after", "a", "stunning", "victory", "in", "the", "quarter", "-", "finals", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Sony Pictures Entertainment announces partnership with Apple Music for exclusive film soundtracks.", "tokens": ["Sony", "Pictures", "Entertainment", "announces", "partnership", "with", "Apple", "Music", "for", "exclusive", "film", "soundtracks", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Pop star Taylor Swift signs multi-million dollar deal with Sony Pictures Entertainment for original content production.", "tokens": ["Pop", "star", "Taylor", "Swift", "signs", "multi", "-", "million", "dollar", "deal", "with", "Sony", "Pictures", "Entertainment", "for", "original", "content", "production", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Actor Will Smith to star in upcoming blockbuster movie produced by Sony Pictures Entertainment in collaboration with Apple Music.", "tokens": ["Actor", "Will", "Smith", "to", "star", "in", "upcoming", "blockbuster", "movie", "produced", "by", "Sony", "Pictures", "Entertainment", "in", "collaboration", "with", "Apple", "Music", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Ted Cruz calls for reforms to United Nations Security Council.", "tokens": ["Ted", "Cruz", "calls", "for", "reforms", "to", "United", "Nations", "Security", "Council", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O"]}
{"sentence": "United Nations Security Council debates new resolution proposed by Ted Cruz.", "tokens": ["United", "Nations", "Security", "Council", "debates", "new", "resolution", "proposed", "by", "Ted", "Cruz", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Ted Cruz criticizes the United Nations Security Council's handling of recent conflicts.", "tokens": ["Ted", "Cruz", "criticizes", "the", "United", "Nations", "Security", "Council", "'", "s", "handling", "of", "recent", "conflicts", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Toyota Motor Corporation to open new assembly plant in Sydney.", "tokens": ["Toyota", "Motor", "Corporation", "to", "open", "new", "assembly", "plant", "in", "Sydney", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Bomb explosion in Baghdad kills at least 20 people.", "tokens": ["Bomb", "explosion", "in", "Baghdad", "kills", "at", "least", "20", "people", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Toyota Motor Corporation reports record-breaking quarterly sales.", "tokens": ["Toyota", "Motor", "Corporation", "reports", "record", "-", "breaking", "quarterly", "sales", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "LeBron James speaks out on police brutality, calling for accountability and change in partnership with the ACLU.", "tokens": ["LeBron", "James", "speaks", "out", "on", "police", "brutality", ",", "calling", "for", "accountability", "and", "change", "in", "partnership", "with", "the", "ACLU", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Local police department hosts annual community safety fair.", "tokens": ["Local", "police", "department", "hosts", "annual", "community", "safety", "fair", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "New community center opens in downtown area, offering various programs for residents.", "tokens": ["New", "community", "center", "opens", "in", "downtown", "area", ",", "offering", "various", "programs", "for", "residents", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Local high school student receives scholarship for academic achievement.", "tokens": ["Local", "high", "school", "student", "receives", "scholarship", "for", "academic", "achievement", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-person", "I-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Local family opens up their home to travelers through Airbnb, transforming their spare room into a cozy guest retreat.", "tokens": ["Local", "family", "opens", "up", "their", "home", "to", "travelers", "through", "Airbnb", ",", "transforming", "their", "spare", "room", "into", "a", "cozy", "guest", "retreat", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Retired couple funds their global adventures by renting out their property on Airbnb when they're away, turning their travel dreams into a reality.", "tokens": ["Retired", "couple", "funds", "their", "global", "adventures", "by", "renting", "out", "their", "property", "on", "Airbnb", "when", "they", "'", "re", "away", ",", "turning", "their", "travel", "dreams", "into", "a", "reality", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Single mother creates a welcoming sanctuary for guests in her home through Airbnb, providing a personalized and affordable travel experience for visitors to the area.", "tokens": ["Single", "mother", "creates", "a", "welcoming", "sanctuary", "for", "guests", "in", "her", "home", "through", "Airbnb", ",", "providing", "a", "personalized", "and", "affordable", "travel", "experience", "for", "visitors", "to", "the", "area", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The New York Public Library hosts a literary event featuring J.K. Rowling.", "tokens": ["The", "New", "York", "Public", "Library", "hosts", "a", "literary", "event", "featuring", "J", ".", "K", ".", "Rowling", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "I-person", "I-person", "I-person", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Buenos Aires launches a campaign to promote reading and literacy among its citizens.", "tokens": ["Buenos", "Aires", "launches", "a", "campaign", "to", "promote", "reading", "and", "literacy", "among", "its", "citizens", "."], "labels": ["B-location", "I-location", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "A new study reveals the impact of literature on mental health, conducted by researchers at The New York Public Library.", "tokens": ["A", "new", "study", "reveals", "the", "impact", "of", "literature", "on", "mental", "health", ",", "conducted", "by", "researchers", "at", "The", "New", "York", "Public", "Library", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Starbucks plans to open 100 new stores in the next fiscal year in order to expand its market presence.", "tokens": ["Starbucks", "plans", "to", "open", "100", "new", "stores", "in", "the", "next", "fiscal", "year", "in", "order", "to", "expand", "its", "market", "presence", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Congresswoman Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez proposed a new bill to regulate big tech companies and promote fair competition in the market.", "tokens": ["Congresswoman", "Alexandria", "Ocasio", "-", "Cortez", "proposed", "a", "new", "bill", "to", "regulate", "big", "tech", "companies", "and", "promote", "fair", "competition", "in", "the", "market", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-person", "I-person", "I-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Christine Madeleine Odette Lagarde appointed as the new head of the International Labor Organization.", "tokens": ["Christine", "Madeleine", "Odette", "Lagarde", "appointed", "as", "the", "new", "head", "of", "the", "International", "Labor", "Organization", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "I-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The International Labor Organization reports a significant decline in global unemployment rates for the first quarter of 2022.", "tokens": ["The", "International", "Labor", "Organization", "reports", "a", "significant", "decline", "in", "global", "unemployment", "rates", "for", "the", "first", "quarter", "of", "2022", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Economic experts predict steady growth in gross domestic product for the next year, despite ongoing challenges in the global economy.", "tokens": ["Economic", "experts", "predict", "steady", "growth", "in", "gross", "domestic", "product", "for", "the", "next", "year", ",", "despite", "ongoing", "challenges", "in", "the", "global", "economy", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The World Health Organization concludes their investigation into the origins of the recent viral outbreak in Asia.", "tokens": ["The", "World", "Health", "Organization", "concludes", "their", "investigation", "into", "the", "origins", "of", "the", "recent", "viral", "outbreak", "in", "Asia", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "New research suggests that consuming a diet high in fruits and vegetables can significantly lower the risk of heart disease.", "tokens": ["New", "research", "suggests", "that", "consuming", "a", "diet", "high", "in", "fruits", "and", "vegetables", "can", "significantly", "lower", "the", "risk", "of", "heart", "disease", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The pharmaceutical company Pfizer announces a breakthrough in the development of a potential HIV vaccine.", "tokens": ["The", "pharmaceutical", "company", "Pfizer", "announces", "a", "breakthrough", "in", "the", "development", "of", "a", "potential", "HIV", "vaccine", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Archaeologists uncover ancient artifacts believed to have belonged to Alexander the Great.", "tokens": ["Archaeologists", "uncover", "ancient", "artifacts", "believed", "to", "have", "belonged", "to", "Alexander", "the", "Great", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "I-person", "O"]}
{"sentence": "New documentary sheds light on the military tactics of Alexander the Great.", "tokens": ["New", "documentary", "sheds", "light", "on", "the", "military", "tactics", "of", "Alexander", "the", "Great", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "I-person", "O"]}
{"sentence": "University researchers discover new insights into the life and legacy of Alexander the Great.", "tokens": ["University", "researchers", "discover", "new", "insights", "into", "the", "life", "and", "legacy", "of", "Alexander", "the", "Great", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "I-person", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Goldman Sachs Group, Inc. wins prestigious award for corporate social responsibility.", "tokens": ["Goldman", "Sachs", "Group", ",", "Inc", ".", "wins", "prestigious", "award", "for", "corporate", "social", "responsibility", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Local entrepreneur credits Beyoncé for inspiring her to start successful business.", "tokens": ["Local", "entrepreneur", "credits", "Beyoncé", "for", "inspiring", "her", "to", "start", "successful", "business", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "B-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Small business owner shares how Goldman Sachs Group, Inc. mentorship program helped her company thrive.", "tokens": ["Small", "business", "owner", "shares", "how", "Goldman", "Sachs", "Group", ",", "Inc", ".", "mentorship", "program", "helped", "her", "company", "thrive", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Investigation reveals Rachel Kim listed as top frequent flyer in Southwest Airlines rewards program.", "tokens": ["Investigation", "reveals", "Rachel", "Kim", "listed", "as", "top", "frequent", "flyer", "in", "Southwest", "Airlines", "rewards", "program", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Travel industry insiders uncover Southwest Airlines as top choice for budget-conscious travelers.", "tokens": ["Travel", "industry", "insiders", "uncover", "Southwest", "Airlines", "as", "top", "choice", "for", "budget", "-", "conscious", "travelers", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Rachel Kim's travel tips and tricks make her a sought-after source for Southwest Airlines passengers.", "tokens": ["Rachel", "Kim", "'", "s", "travel", "tips", "and", "tricks", "make", "her", "a", "sought", "-", "after", "source", "for", "Southwest", "Airlines", "passengers", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "New York Fashion Week kicks off with a star-studded runway show.", "tokens": ["New", "York", "Fashion", "Week", "kicks", "off", "with", "a", "star", "-", "studded", "runway", "show", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Celebrity chef opens a new luxury restaurant in downtown Los Angeles.", "tokens": ["Celebrity", "chef", "opens", "a", "new", "luxury", "restaurant", "in", "downtown", "Los", "Angeles", "."], "labels": ["O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-location", "I-location", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Renowned interior designer to launch a new line of home decor products.", "tokens": ["Renowned", "interior", "designer", "to", "launch", "a", "new", "line", "of", "home", "decor", "products", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Coca-Cola launches new marketing campaign to commemorate its 100-year history.", "tokens": ["Coca", "-", "Cola", "launches", "new", "marketing", "campaign", "to", "commemorate", "its", "100", "-", "year", "history", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The World Trade Organization celebrates its 25th anniversary with a series of global events.", "tokens": ["The", "World", "Trade", "Organization", "celebrates", "its", "25th", "anniversary", "with", "a", "series", "of", "global", "events", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Karl Lagerfeld appointed as the new creative director of luxury fashion brand Chanel.", "tokens": ["Karl", "Lagerfeld", "appointed", "as", "the", "new", "creative", "director", "of", "luxury", "fashion", "brand", "Chanel", "."], "labels": ["B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "B-organization", "O"]}
{"sentence": "Designer Karl Lagerfeld launches new fragrance line in collaboration with renowned beauty brand.", "tokens": ["Designer", "Karl", "Lagerfeld", "launches", "new", "fragrance", "line", "in", "collaboration", "with", "renowned", "beauty", "brand", "."], "labels": ["O", "B-person", "I-person", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
{"sentence": "The Intergovernmental Panel on Climate Change reports that extreme weather events are becoming more frequent and intense worldwide, raising concerns about the impact of climate change on global communities.", "tokens": ["The", "Intergovernmental", "Panel", "on", "Climate", "Change", "reports", "that", "extreme", "weather", "events", "are", "becoming", "more", "frequent", "and", "intense", "worldwide", ",", "raising", "concerns", "about", "the", "impact", "of", "climate", "change", "on", "global", "communities", "."], "labels": ["B-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "I-organization", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O", "O"]}
