[
  {
    "sentence": "New York City's unemployment rate drops to 4.2 percent, signaling a strong job market recovery.",
    "span": "New York City",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00066564507375
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tokyo stock market sees a 3% increase following positive corporate earnings reports.",
    "span": "Tokyo",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00011402688140800001
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The New York City Chamber of Commerce reports a 10% increase in small business openings in the past year.",
    "span": "New York City",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0062042560971833334
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The New York City Chamber of Commerce reports a 10% increase in small business openings in the past year.",
    "span": "Chamber of Commerce",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.09236158396049998
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Art Institute of Chicago unveils new digital art collection.",
    "span": "Art Institute of Chicago",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -4.4092521099999994e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Renowned artist to create a new mural for the Public Art Fund in Rome.",
    "span": "Public Art Fund",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0034113838042500004
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Renowned artist to create a new mural for the Public Art Fund in Rome.",
    "span": "Rome",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0002042698346
  },
  {
    "sentence": "LeBron James scores 30 points to lead Lakers to victory at Madison Square Garden, New York City.",
    "span": "LeBron James",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.00015629112024999998
  },
  {
    "sentence": "LeBron James scores 30 points to lead Lakers to victory at Madison Square Garden, New York City.",
    "span": "Lakers",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.012101498142499998
  },
  {
    "sentence": "LeBron James scores 30 points to lead Lakers to victory at Madison Square Garden, New York City.",
    "span": "Madison Square Garden",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0006283355488833334
  },
  {
    "sentence": "LeBron James scores 30 points to lead Lakers to victory at Madison Square Garden, New York City.",
    "span": "New York City",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0003466392871666667
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Madison Square Garden, New York City, to host the World Heavyweight Championship boxing match next month.",
    "span": "Madison Square Garden",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0008372166213857143
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Madison Square Garden, New York City, to host the World Heavyweight Championship boxing match next month.",
    "span": "New York City",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.010846467073216667
  },
  {
    "sentence": "New York City Marathon sees record number of participants crossing the finish line at Central Park, near Madison Square Garden.",
    "span": "New York City Marathon",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.05658630356094286
  },
  {
    "sentence": "New York City Marathon sees record number of participants crossing the finish line at Central Park, near Madison Square Garden.",
    "span": "Central Park",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -7.16651938e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "New York City Marathon sees record number of participants crossing the finish line at Central Park, near Madison Square Garden.",
    "span": "Madison Square Garden",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.007015715822133332
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The Louvre Museum acquires a rare painting by Indian artist.",
    "span": "The Louvre Museum",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0018500796311857143
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The Louvre Museum acquires a rare painting by Indian artist.",
    "span": "Indian",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.040269188725
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Renowned Indian sculptor to debut exhibit at Taj Mahal.",
    "span": "Indian",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.178960456063
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Renowned Indian sculptor to debut exhibit at Taj Mahal.",
    "span": "Taj Mahal",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00014845700866666665
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Art installation inspired by the Taj Mahal to be displayed in India.",
    "span": "Taj Mahal",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00018023074194285714
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Art installation inspired by the Taj Mahal to be displayed in India.",
    "span": "India",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00014083742850000002
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Annette Winkler appointed as the new CEO of a major automotive company.",
    "span": "Annette Winkler",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.13087072808324998
  },
  {
    "sentence": "William C. Durant's pioneering contributions to the automotive industry remembered on his birth anniversary.",
    "span": "William C. Durant",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.003133207236242857
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The automotive industry pays tribute to Annette Winkler for her innovative leadership and vision.",
    "span": "Annette Winkler",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0017821953565
  },
  {
    "sentence": "A new study conducted by Dr. Jane Smith finds a correlation between higher education funding and student achievement.",
    "span": "Dr. Jane Smith",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -4.838071075714286e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The Department of Education announced a partnership with Dr. Jane Smith to improve the quality of early childhood education across the country.",
    "span": "Department of Education",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.000414423148995
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The Department of Education announced a partnership with Dr. Jane Smith to improve the quality of early childhood education across the country.",
    "span": "Dr. Jane Smith",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0001554463118485714
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Environmental activist Bill McKibben urges global action to protect the Amazon Rainforest.",
    "span": "Bill McKibben",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.00038708873379999993
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Environmental activist Bill McKibben urges global action to protect the Amazon Rainforest.",
    "span": "Amazon Rainforest",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.009846483979816667
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Study shows deforestation in the Amazon Rainforest accelerating at an alarming rate.",
    "span": "Amazon Rainforest",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -4.089921806666667e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "International organization launches campaign to preserve the biodiversity of the Amazon Rainforest.",
    "span": "International organization",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.018791821629266667
  },
  {
    "sentence": "International organization launches campaign to preserve the biodiversity of the Amazon Rainforest.",
    "span": "Amazon Rainforest",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.10883945207160002
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Poland wins legal battle to continue logging in Bialowieza Forest.",
    "span": "Poland",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.084623190060125
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Poland wins legal battle to continue logging in Bialowieza Forest.",
    "span": "Bialowieza Forest",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.001074702011575
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The Everglades facing threat from invasive species, experts warn.",
    "span": "The Everglades",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -4.7021001457142854e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "David Sheldrick Wildlife Trust rescues and rehabilitates orphaned elephants in Kenya.",
    "span": "David Sheldrick Wildlife Trust",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0005986994223944445
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Toronto experiences record-breaking heat wave, with temperatures reaching 40°C.",
    "span": "Toronto",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.000377908341
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Kim Jong Un announces plans for historic summit with South Korea.",
    "span": "Kim Jong Un",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.08873882558528334
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Mass shooting in downtown Toronto leaves five dead and several injured.",
    "span": "Toronto",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -3.1693180875000005e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The World Health Organization congratulates Greta Thunberg for her efforts to raise awareness about climate change.",
    "span": "World Health Organization",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00044138331038333345
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The World Health Organization congratulates Greta Thunberg for her efforts to raise awareness about climate change.",
    "span": "Greta Thunberg",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.000243636660705
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The government announced a new initiative to improve access to mental health services for adolescents, following Greta Thunberg's advocacy for youth mental health.",
    "span": "Greta Thunberg",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.010678455596737501
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Oxfam report reveals alarming rise in global income inequality.",
    "span": "Oxfam",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0006524669846333333
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Oxfam's latest study highlights the impact of gender inequality on poverty levels.",
    "span": "Oxfam",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -1.0226587521666668e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Government accused of ignoring Oxfam's warnings about increasing homelessness.",
    "span": "Oxfam",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -2.4749567066666667e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Miami police department announces new community outreach program.",
    "span": "Miami",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0583627316935
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Miami police department announces new community outreach program.",
    "span": "police department",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00251633951872
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Local Miami artist wins prestigious national art award.",
    "span": "Miami",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.290994558492925
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Local Miami artist wins prestigious national art award.",
    "span": "artist",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0001119640135
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Miami residents express concerns over rising sea levels and coastal erosion.",
    "span": "Miami",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0007110672337500001
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Sao Paulo Stock Exchange sets new record as economic indicators point to strong growth.",
    "span": "Sao Paulo Stock Exchange",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0009740640452875
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Investors flock to Sao Paulo Stock Exchange as inflation rates remain stable.",
    "span": "Sao Paulo Stock Exchange",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -4.596598511250001e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Sao Paulo Stock Exchange reacts positively to government's new economic policies.",
    "span": "Sao Paulo Stock Exchange",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00174421273852875
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Detroit police arrest three suspects in connection with a series of robberies in the downtown area.",
    "span": "Detroit",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.21534061427875
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Gun violence continues to plague Detroit neighborhoods, with multiple shootings reported over the weekend.",
    "span": "Detroit",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -2.886209396e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Authorities in Detroit are investigating a string of carjackings targeting drivers in the East side of the city.",
    "span": "Detroit",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00085961262365
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Cape Town to experience heavy rainfall and strong winds in the coming week.",
    "span": "Cape Town",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0007060505619833333
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Severe snowstorm hits the Himalayas, causing travel disruptions and power outages.",
    "span": "Himalayas",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0018168253761666666
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Olympic gymnast Simone Biles donates $100,000 for relief efforts in areas affected by extreme weather.",
    "span": "Simone Biles",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -7.067991847142858e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "New health and wellness center opening in Mumbai to promote healthy living and fitness.",
    "span": "Mumbai",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00238261044938
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Actress from Mumbai spotted shopping in Los Angeles, setting a new fashion trend.",
    "span": "Mumbai",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -7.860211093999999e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Actress from Mumbai spotted shopping in Los Angeles, setting a new fashion trend.",
    "span": "Los Angeles",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0009156431994
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Renowned celebrity chef from Los Angeles to launch a new restaurant concept in Mumbai.",
    "span": "Los Angeles",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -2.6251534700000002e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Renowned celebrity chef from Los Angeles to launch a new restaurant concept in Mumbai.",
    "span": "Mumbai",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00255645977865
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Joe Biden spotted at National Basketball Association game.",
    "span": "Joe Biden",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -5.271474713999999e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Fashion designers from around the world showcase their latest creations at the prestigious Paris Fashion Week.",
    "span": "Paris Fashion Week",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.013281518735649998
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The bustling shopping districts of Tokyo attract fashion enthusiasts with their eclectic mix of traditional and cutting-edge styles.",
    "span": "Tokyo",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -6.155819246e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Luxury fashion brands open flagship stores in The Dubai Mall, catering to the affluent clientele of the Middle East.",
    "span": "The Dubai Mall",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.07258707043728334
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Luxury fashion brands open flagship stores in The Dubai Mall, catering to the affluent clientele of the Middle East.",
    "span": "Middle East",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00047825843494
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Environmental group files lawsuit against corporation for alleged toxic waste dumping, citing violations of federal regulations.",
    "span": "environmental group",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.5600429204765833
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Violent protests erupt in Rio de Janeiro following controversial government decision.",
    "span": "Rio de Janeiro",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0010772777284666667
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Rio de Janeiro Mayor declares state of emergency in response to record-breaking heatwave.",
    "span": "Rio de Janeiro",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.011753604620700001
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Rio de Janeiro police chief resigns amidst corruption scandal.",
    "span": "Rio de Janeiro",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0005074335342716667
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Twitter chairman resigns amid pressure from activist investors.",
    "span": "Twitter",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00111849768825
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Amazon announces plans to invest $1.2 billion in building new data centers.",
    "span": "Amazon",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.004948647130025
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tech giant Twitter unveils new feature to combat misinformation on its platform.",
    "span": "Twitter",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -8.50565341375e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Taylor Swift wins Grammy for Album of the Year.",
    "span": "Taylor Swift",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0005235635574
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Taylor Swift wins Grammy for Album of the Year.",
    "span": "Grammy",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00231209501875
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Hollywood blockbuster 'Mystic River' to be adapted into a TV series.",
    "span": "Hollywood",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.01516079917458
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Hollywood blockbuster 'Mystic River' to be adapted into a TV series.",
    "span": "Mystic River",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.13432282433144
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Hollywood blockbuster 'Mystic River' to be adapted into a TV series.",
    "span": "TV series",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0016002776168
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Brad Pitt and Angelina Jolie to star in new romantic comedy together.",
    "span": "Brad Pitt",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -1.569008924e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Brad Pitt and Angelina Jolie to star in new romantic comedy together.",
    "span": "Angelina Jolie",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.004244164255142857
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tesla Motors unveils new electric vehicle with longer range and faster charging capabilities.",
    "span": "Tesla Motors",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0005333562096
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Ford announces plans to invest $22 billion in electric vehicle production over the next five years, aiming to transition its lineup to all-electric models.",
    "span": "Ford",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -3.9290581750000005e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Renowned automotive designer, John Smith, set to debut cutting-edge concept car at upcoming international auto show.",
    "span": "John Smith",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.00102495716826
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The Buddhist Peace Fellowship organizes a meditation retreat for peace and social justice.",
    "span": "Buddhist Peace Fellowship",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.000177902447625
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The Dalai Lama to speak at the annual conference hosted by the Buddhist Peace Fellowship.",
    "span": "Dalai Lama",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0003176987689666667
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The Dalai Lama to speak at the annual conference hosted by the Buddhist Peace Fellowship.",
    "span": "Buddhist Peace Fellowship",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00011638296731666667
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Local Buddhist Peace Fellowship chapter raises funds for humanitarian aid in Myanmar.",
    "span": "Buddhist Peace Fellowship",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.025605200357867498
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Local Buddhist Peace Fellowship chapter raises funds for humanitarian aid in Myanmar.",
    "span": "Myanmar",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00015813250917499997
  },
  {
    "sentence": "American Civil Liberties Union files lawsuit against government over immigration policy.",
    "span": "American Civil Liberties Union",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.027106896686471427
  },
  {
    "sentence": "New immigration bill proposed by American Civil Liberties Union aims to protect undocumented immigrants.",
    "span": "American Civil Liberties Union",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -2.3966228642857144e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Immigration rights rally organized by American Civil Liberties Union draws thousands to Washington D.C.",
    "span": "American Civil Liberties Union",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0011858927066142856
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Immigration rights rally organized by American Civil Liberties Union draws thousands to Washington D.C.",
    "span": "Washington D.C.",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.007496797235985715
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Anna Wintour steps down as editor-in-chief of Vogue after 32 years.",
    "span": "Anna Wintour",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -2.3591589e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Anna Wintour steps down as editor-in-chief of Vogue after 32 years.",
    "span": "Vogue",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00027753060685
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Fashion industry leaders gather in Paris for the annual runway shows.",
    "span": "Paris",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00011098516175
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Anna Wintour's impact on the fashion world discussed in new documentary.",
    "span": "Anna Wintour",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.005330054340842857
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tesla's CEO Elon Musk announces plan to expand company's production in China.",
    "span": "Tesla",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00072116889275
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tesla's CEO Elon Musk announces plan to expand company's production in China.",
    "span": "Elon Musk",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -4.87073034e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tesla's CEO Elon Musk announces plan to expand company's production in China.",
    "span": "China",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.000363461298425
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Global retail giant Walmart reports record-breaking quarterly profits.",
    "span": "Walmart",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -6.095557335e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Los Angeles police arrest three suspects in connection with a string of violent robberies.",
    "span": "Los Angeles",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.060500569079120006
  },
  {
    "sentence": "California man sentenced to 20 years in prison for drug trafficking.",
    "span": "California",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -2.135226325e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Police investigate shooting at a nightclub in downtown Los Angeles.",
    "span": "Los Angeles",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0001049611654
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The Migration Policy Institute releases new report on the impact of immigration on the US economy.",
    "span": "Migration Policy Institute",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.02829347342166667
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The Migration Policy Institute releases new report on the impact of immigration on the US economy.",
    "span": "US",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00041591415725
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Immigration reform bill proposed by senators backed by the Migration Policy Institute.",
    "span": "senators",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.33473412102594
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Immigration reform bill proposed by senators backed by the Migration Policy Institute.",
    "span": "Migration Policy Institute",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0008280149577833334
  },
  {
    "sentence": "New study by the Migration Policy Institute reveals the challenges faced by immigrants in accessing healthcare services.",
    "span": "Migration Policy Institute",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -3.0152244366666668e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "LeBron James scores a game-winning three-pointer to lead the Lakers to victory over the Warriors.",
    "span": "LeBron James",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -3.702632266666667e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "LeBron James scores a game-winning three-pointer to lead the Lakers to victory over the Warriors.",
    "span": "Lakers",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -1.2948404725e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "LeBron James scores a game-winning three-pointer to lead the Lakers to victory over the Warriors.",
    "span": "Warriors",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0004253368
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The New York Yankees sign a record-breaking contract with All-Star pitcher.",
    "span": "New York Yankees",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.3009216251878667
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Simone Biles makes history with her incredible performance at the Gymnastics World Championships.",
    "span": "Simone Biles",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.00017273873086285713
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Simone Biles makes history with her incredible performance at the Gymnastics World Championships.",
    "span": "Gymnastics World Championships",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -1.83572706875e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Al-Qaeda claims responsibility for the 1998 U.S. embassy bombings in East Africa.",
    "span": "Al-Qaeda",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0015471830658000001
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Al-Qaeda claims responsibility for the 1998 U.S. embassy bombings in East Africa.",
    "span": "U.S. embassy",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.055413811830471435
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Al-Qaeda claims responsibility for the 1998 U.S. embassy bombings in East Africa.",
    "span": "East Africa",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0011852102854
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Former Al-Qaeda member provides insight into the organization's founding and early activities.",
    "span": "Al-Qaeda",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -9.108291766e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Lebron James signs a multi-million dollar contract with the Los Angeles Lakers.",
    "span": "Lebron James",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0011081578811666666
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Lebron James signs a multi-million dollar contract with the Los Angeles Lakers.",
    "span": "Los Angeles Lakers",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00010502804766666667
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The Tokyo Olympics committee announces new safety measures for the upcoming Games.",
    "span": "Tokyo Olympics",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.02166097704988833
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Serena Williams makes a stunning comeback at the US Open, securing her spot in the semi-finals.",
    "span": "Serena Williams",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -1.338548465e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Serena Williams makes a stunning comeback at the US Open, securing her spot in the semi-finals.",
    "span": "US Open",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00035765432974
  },
  {
    "sentence": "United We Dream organizes protest for immigrant rights in downtown Los Angeles.",
    "span": "United We Dream",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0003653811511666667
  },
  {
    "sentence": "United We Dream organizes protest for immigrant rights in downtown Los Angeles.",
    "span": "Los Angeles",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0005218058472
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Anti-Defamation League releases report on anti-immigrant sentiment in the U.S.",
    "span": "Anti-Defamation League",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.002425505539325
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Anti-Defamation League releases report on anti-immigrant sentiment in the U.S.",
    "span": "U.S.",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0004551048858
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Principal David Lee resigns amid allegations of financial mismanagement at local high school.",
    "span": "Principal David Lee",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0021872873221666666
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Sydney Opera House to host international education summit with top researchers and policy makers.",
    "span": "Sydney Opera House",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0005493065469999999
  },
  {
    "sentence": "New report from National Student Clearinghouse reveals decline in college enrollment rates across the country.",
    "span": "National Student Clearinghouse",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -1.19798749e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Jennifer Lopez to visit Angkor Wat in Cambodia for her next music video.",
    "span": "Jennifer Lopez",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.019387231002166664
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Jennifer Lopez to visit Angkor Wat in Cambodia for her next music video.",
    "span": "Angkor Wat",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0014079400220000002
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Jennifer Lopez to visit Angkor Wat in Cambodia for her next music video.",
    "span": "Cambodia",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0005147243838000001
  },
  {
    "sentence": "American Society of Travel Agents announces new tour packages to Cambodia's Angkor Wat.",
    "span": "American Society of Travel Agents",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0089116773082125
  },
  {
    "sentence": "American Society of Travel Agents announces new tour packages to Cambodia's Angkor Wat.",
    "span": "Cambodia",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00125028940325
  },
  {
    "sentence": "American Society of Travel Agents announces new tour packages to Cambodia's Angkor Wat.",
    "span": "Angkor Wat",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00010676078061666666
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Cambodia sees a surge in tourism as travelers flock to visit Angkor Wat.",
    "span": "Cambodia",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00079053424314
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Cambodia sees a surge in tourism as travelers flock to visit Angkor Wat.",
    "span": "Angkor Wat",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -1.845164099e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The upcoming film festival will feature the latest works from renowned directors around the world.",
    "span": "film festival",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0019331893427999998
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Oscar-winning actress Emma Stone to star in the new biopic about the life of astronaut Sally Ride.",
    "span": "Emma Stone",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.000123410223
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Oscar-winning actress Emma Stone to star in the new biopic about the life of astronaut Sally Ride.",
    "span": "Sally Ride",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0018308397164399997
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Venice, Italy selected as the location for the shooting of the highly-anticipated action film sequel.",
    "span": "Venice, Italy",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.13011561272514285
  },
  {
    "sentence": "American Atheists sue school district over prayer in classrooms.",
    "span": "American Atheists",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.055726545767366666
  },
  {
    "sentence": "American Atheists sue school district over prayer in classrooms.",
    "span": "school district",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0318115044762
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Survey shows growing number of Americans identifying as atheists.",
    "span": "Americans",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.9901977458125
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Survey shows growing number of Americans identifying as atheists.",
    "span": "atheists",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0212012014475
  },
  {
    "sentence": "American Atheists hold rally in support of separation of church and state.",
    "span": "American Atheists",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0029736903728833333
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Beyoncé to headline virtual concert in support of Black-owned businesses.",
    "span": "Beyoncé",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.09953017105154999
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Cardi B launches new fashion line in collaboration with luxury brand.",
    "span": "Cardi B",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -2.8782624499999998e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Royal Caribbean International announces partnership with popular TV show for new cruise entertainment.",
    "span": "Royal Caribbean International",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -6.815651196666665e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Bank of America Corporation announces plans to expand its presence in Sydney.",
    "span": "Bank of America Corporation",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.044898622730428564
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Bank of America Corporation announces plans to expand its presence in Sydney.",
    "span": "Sydney",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00019032392425
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Sydney stock market experiences a surge in trading volume as investors react to economic indicators.",
    "span": "Sydney",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -3.316534738e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Bank of America Corporation reports record-breaking profits in the latest fiscal quarter.",
    "span": "Bank of America Corporation",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -1.1994775642857143e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "United Nations Economic Commission for Europe predicts strong economic growth for Australia in the next quarter.",
    "span": "Australia",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.000243411287
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Nissan announces plans to invest in new manufacturing facilities, boosting the economy in the Midwest.",
    "span": "Nissan",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0006983647399800001
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Nissan announces plans to invest in new manufacturing facilities, boosting the economy in the Midwest.",
    "span": "Midwest",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.000472403870825
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Australia's economic recovery surpasses expectations, with the United Nations Economic Commission for Europe praising the government's policies.",
    "span": "Australia",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.011926080152150001
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Australia's economic recovery surpasses expectations, with the United Nations Economic Commission for Europe praising the government's policies.",
    "span": "United Nations Economic Commission for Europe",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -1.8524487288888887e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The renowned author Virginia Woolf's novels continue to be celebrated for their innovative narrative techniques and exploration of modernist themes.",
    "span": "Virginia Woolf",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0018671809443
  },
  {
    "sentence": "A new biography reveals previously unknown details about Virginia Woolf's personal life and the impact it had on her literary works.",
    "span": "Virginia Woolf",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -1.4498052055e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Literary scholars gather at a conference to discuss the enduring legacy of Virginia Woolf and her contributions to the development of feminist literature.",
    "span": "Virginia Woolf",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.00018852700128333332
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Fashion designer Stella McCartney launches new sustainable clothing line.",
    "span": "Stella McCartney",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.00126379591305
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Paris becomes the epicenter of global fashion as haute couture takes the spotlight.",
    "span": "Paris",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.027470157073475
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Paris becomes the epicenter of global fashion as haute couture takes the spotlight.",
    "span": "haute couture",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0008435420843166666
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The European Union reaches a new trade agreement with Turkey, easing tensions in Ankara.",
    "span": "The European Union",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -5.8680430166666665e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The European Union reaches a new trade agreement with Turkey, easing tensions in Ankara.",
    "span": "Turkey",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00211941409175
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The European Union reaches a new trade agreement with Turkey, easing tensions in Ankara.",
    "span": "Ankara",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.000642421027425
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Ilhan Omar calls for bipartisan support to address immigration reform in Congress.",
    "span": "Ilhan Omar",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.022227097975550003
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Turkey's president criticized the European Union for what he called a lack of support in handling the refugee crisis in Ankara.",
    "span": "Turkey",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.010454769532616667
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Turkey's president criticized the European Union for what he called a lack of support in handling the refugee crisis in Ankara.",
    "span": "The European Union",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.003917917917075
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Turkey's president criticized the European Union for what he called a lack of support in handling the refugee crisis in Ankara.",
    "span": "Ankara",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -6.7810058875e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Teach for America expands its program to Johannesburg, South Africa.",
    "span": "Teach for America",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -2.4902828928571423e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Teach for America expands its program to Johannesburg, South Africa.",
    "span": "Johannesburg",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -7.1949630625e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Teach for America expands its program to Johannesburg, South Africa.",
    "span": "South Africa",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00054431712478
  },
  {
    "sentence": "University of Cape Town partners with Teach for America to improve education in South Africa.",
    "span": "University of Cape Town",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -9.178813457142857e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "University of Cape Town partners with Teach for America to improve education in South Africa.",
    "span": "Teach for America",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -5.4687109416666665e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "University of Cape Town partners with Teach for America to improve education in South Africa.",
    "span": "South Africa",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -8.598687548e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Teach for America CEO discusses plans to address education disparities in Johannesburg.",
    "span": "Teach for America",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -2.3914094685714288e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Teach for America CEO discusses plans to address education disparities in Johannesburg.",
    "span": "CEO",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.10691106369600001
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Teach for America CEO discusses plans to address education disparities in Johannesburg.",
    "span": "Johannesburg",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -1.1458358949999999e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Veterans of Foreign Wars to hold annual memorial service for fallen soldiers.",
    "span": "Veterans of Foreign Wars",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.000597554804125
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Army National Guard troops deployed to support humanitarian relief efforts in hurricane-ravaged areas.",
    "span": "Army National Guard",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00047419985078333334
  },
  {
    "sentence": "National Military Museum opens new exhibition featuring the history of the Armed Forces.",
    "span": "National Military Museum",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.09373091017873332
  },
  {
    "sentence": "National Military Museum opens new exhibition featuring the history of the Armed Forces.",
    "span": "Armed Forces",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0001201477128
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Researchers from the United Nations Environment Programme discover new species of coral in the depths of the Pacific Ocean.",
    "span": "United Nations Environment Programme",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.01889239927142857
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Scientists working with the United Nations Environment Programme predict a significant increase in global temperatures by the end of the century.",
    "span": "United Nations Environment Programme",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -2.921014165714286e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Buenos Aires Marathon sees record number of participants this year.",
    "span": "Buenos Aires",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0008701436099142857
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Augusta National Golf Club announces plans for major renovation ahead of next year's Masters tournament.",
    "span": "Augusta National Golf Club",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.039166734342400006
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Promising young athlete from Georgia breaks high school track record in 100m dash.",
    "span": "Georgia",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -7.5495940375e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Universal Pictures releases highly anticipated blockbuster movie.",
    "span": "Universal Pictures",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00024025809433999998
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Famous actor signs multi-picture deal with Universal Pictures.",
    "span": "actor",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.013835606524760003
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Famous actor signs multi-picture deal with Universal Pictures.",
    "span": "Universal Pictures",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0121696201565
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Upcoming film festival to feature exclusive screenings of Universal Pictures' latest releases.",
    "span": "Universal Pictures",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0030161519331599997
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Beijing Normal University launches new online education platform.",
    "span": "Beijing Normal University",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00018531561685714284
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Researchers at Beijing Normal University discover link between physical activity and academic performance.",
    "span": "Beijing Normal University",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -1.987924611428571e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Beijing Normal University ranked top in education research and innovation.",
    "span": "Beijing Normal University",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -5.213077985714285e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Richard Branson's Virgin Galactic successfully launches its first manned spaceflight.",
    "span": "Richard Branson",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0008985137494666667
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Richard Branson's Virgin Galactic successfully launches its first manned spaceflight.",
    "span": "Virgin Galactic",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00053377879042
  },
  {
    "sentence": "SpaceX announces partnership with Richard Branson's Virgin Orbit for satellite launches.",
    "span": "SpaceX",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -2.110193568e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "SpaceX announces partnership with Richard Branson's Virgin Orbit for satellite launches.",
    "span": "Richard Branson",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.00011360398896666665
  },
  {
    "sentence": "SpaceX announces partnership with Richard Branson's Virgin Orbit for satellite launches.",
    "span": "Virgin Orbit",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00011958250772
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Renowned entrepreneur Richard Branson invests in new clean energy technology startup.",
    "span": "Richard Branson",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -7.486126246666667e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tom Hanks to star in new film celebrating Berlin's cultural heritage.",
    "span": "Tom Hanks",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -4.5786568500000004e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tom Hanks to star in new film celebrating Berlin's cultural heritage.",
    "span": "Berlin",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.000984550064325
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Renowned chef to open new restaurant in the heart of Berlin's artistic district.",
    "span": "Berlin",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -3.6014314249999996e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Volkswagen Group announces plans to invest $2 billion in electric vehicle production.",
    "span": "Volkswagen Group",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0002591396565857143
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The latest automotive recall affects over 100,000 vehicles manufactured by Volkswagen Group.",
    "span": "Volkswagen Group",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -2.337021069e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Volkswagen Group partners with a major tech company to develop autonomous driving technology for their vehicles.",
    "span": "Volkswagen Group",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -1.9579122e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "United States Department of Defense announces new cyber security initiative.",
    "span": "United States Department of Defense",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0002384441785625
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tensions rise between India and Pakistan after the Delhi bombing.",
    "span": "Delhi",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0081079499978
  },
  {
    "sentence": "United States Department of Defense deploys additional troops to the Middle East.",
    "span": "United States Department of Defense",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0008295610802499999
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Australian Defence Force deploys troops to Fort Bragg for joint military training.",
    "span": "Australian Defence Force",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -9.246917036666667e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Australian Defence Force deploys troops to Fort Bragg for joint military training.",
    "span": "Fort Bragg",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.015608013067950002
  },
  {
    "sentence": "North Carolina National Guard partners with Australian Defence Force for disaster relief exercise.",
    "span": "North Carolina National Guard",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00014516492214285717
  },
  {
    "sentence": "North Carolina National Guard partners with Australian Defence Force for disaster relief exercise.",
    "span": "Australian Defence Force",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0011663332906666666
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Joint military exercise at Fort Bragg strengthens ties between Australian Defence Force and US Army.",
    "span": "Fort Bragg",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0002819437609333333
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Joint military exercise at Fort Bragg strengthens ties between Australian Defence Force and US Army.",
    "span": "Australian Defence Force",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00017383791706666667
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Joint military exercise at Fort Bragg strengthens ties between Australian Defence Force and US Army.",
    "span": "US Army",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -1.521327402e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The National Center for Education Statistics reports a decline in high school graduation rates.",
    "span": "National Center for Education Statistics",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.000186534188625
  },
  {
    "sentence": "A study by the National Center for Education Statistics reveals a widening achievement gap among students in rural areas.",
    "span": "National Center for Education Statistics",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -2.65516060125e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The Rainforest Action Network launches campaign to protect biodiversity in the Amazon rainforest.",
    "span": "Rainforest Action Network",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0010944738927142858
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The Rainforest Action Network launches campaign to protect biodiversity in the Amazon rainforest.",
    "span": "Amazon rainforest",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0010052288948833334
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Everglades National Park announces plan to restore wetlands and improve wildlife habitat.",
    "span": "Everglades National Park",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0002746917815
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Environmentalist group partners with local schools to educate students on the importance of preserving the Everglades National Park.",
    "span": "Everglades National Park",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.002005866117125
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Dubai police arrest international drug trafficker.",
    "span": "Dubai",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0046253798874000005
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Immigration and Customs Enforcement cracks down on human trafficking ring.",
    "span": "Immigration and Customs Enforcement",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -6.5631839e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Attenborough's naturalist, Jane Goodall, to receive lifetime achievement award.",
    "span": "Attenborough's naturalist",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.034677074556299994
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Attenborough's naturalist, Jane Goodall, to receive lifetime achievement award.",
    "span": "Jane Goodall",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.00033858140136666664
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Attenborough's naturalist, WWF, launches campaign to protect endangered species.",
    "span": "Attenborough's naturalist",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -1.489539761111111e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Attenborough's naturalist, WWF, launches campaign to protect endangered species.",
    "span": "WWF",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -8.787175952e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Wangari Maathai, the renowned environmentalist, is set to lead a campaign to protect the natural habitats of endangered species in Africa.",
    "span": "Wangari Maathai",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -6.24623465111111e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Wangari Maathai, the renowned environmentalist, is set to lead a campaign to protect the natural habitats of endangered species in Africa.",
    "span": "Africa",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.003522094093725
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The government has announced a new initiative to conserve the wildlife population, with a focus on preserving the habitats of endangered species, in honor of Wangari Maathai's legacy.",
    "span": "Wangari Maathai",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -4.361276706666667e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "A wildlife sanctuary in Kenya, established with the support of Wangari Maathai, has successfully reintroduced several rare species back into their natural habitat.",
    "span": "Kenya",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.04288191528655
  },
  {
    "sentence": "A wildlife sanctuary in Kenya, established with the support of Wangari Maathai, has successfully reintroduced several rare species back into their natural habitat.",
    "span": "Wangari Maathai",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0008409934748249999
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Beyoncé announces new collaboration with Ford Motor Company to support community grants program.",
    "span": "Beyoncé",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -1.4994734216666666e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Beyoncé announces new collaboration with Ford Motor Company to support community grants program.",
    "span": "Ford Motor Company",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00013679491055
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Interview with Beyoncé on her upcoming humanitarian trip to South Africa.",
    "span": "Beyoncé",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -9.744058399166666e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Interview with Beyoncé on her upcoming humanitarian trip to South Africa.",
    "span": "South Africa",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -9.042564760000001e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Ford Motor Company CEO discusses partnership with UNICEF for global education initiatives.",
    "span": "Ford Motor Company",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -1.9385402700000003e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Ford Motor Company CEO discusses partnership with UNICEF for global education initiatives.",
    "span": "UNICEF",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0014165400234833333
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Local woman raises $10,000 for children's hospital through charity marathon.",
    "span": "woman",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.029653173057825
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Local woman raises $10,000 for children's hospital through charity marathon.",
    "span": "children's hospital",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0010960816138333334
  },
  {
    "sentence": "High school student organizes food drive to help struggling families in the community.",
    "span": "high school student",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.16392541225516666
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Firefighters rescue elderly man from burning building, bringing him to safety.",
    "span": "firefighters",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0047011860048
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Firefighters rescue elderly man from burning building, bringing him to safety.",
    "span": "elderly man",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0016395619033799998
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The American Civil Liberties Union files lawsuit on behalf of Mary Smith, alleging wrongful imprisonment.",
    "span": "American Civil Liberties Union",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00020610761095714284
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The American Civil Liberties Union files lawsuit on behalf of Mary Smith, alleging wrongful imprisonment.",
    "span": "Mary Smith",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0002937325056
  },
  {
    "sentence": "American Civil Liberties Union calls for reform in juvenile justice system after recent spike in youth crime rates.",
    "span": "American Civil Liberties Union",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -1.184151352857143e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Legendary musician Bob Dylan to release new album next month.",
    "span": "Bob Dylan",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0006598549034000001
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Bob Dylan's classic album \"Highway 61 Revisited\" celebrates 55th anniversary.",
    "span": "Bob Dylan",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.00020168927389999997
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Folk singer Bob Dylan honored with prestigious music award.",
    "span": "Bob Dylan",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -9.003320354e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Walt Disney World to host an exclusive concert series featuring top artists from around the world.",
    "span": "Walt Disney World",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0005581067632857143
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Walt Disney World's new immersive theater experience takes audiences on a magical journey through beloved Disney classics.",
    "span": "Walt Disney World",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -2.3029628192857144e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The National Gallery of Art opens new exhibit featuring works by Monet and Renoir.",
    "span": "The National Gallery of Art",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0662053474926375
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The National Gallery of Art opens new exhibit featuring works by Monet and Renoir.",
    "span": "Monet",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -1.530863696e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The National Gallery of Art opens new exhibit featuring works by Monet and Renoir.",
    "span": "Renoir",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.00033928115256
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Renowned author to speak at The National Gallery of Art's literary event next week.",
    "span": "The National Gallery of Art",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00070168551
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Renowned pastor Rick Warren to host nationwide religious event to promote unity and fellowship among diverse faith communities.",
    "span": "Rick Warren",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0031215164208799996
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Sikh American Legal Defense and Education Fund launches initiative to combat discrimination and promote religious freedom for Sikh Americans.",
    "span": "Sikh American Legal Defense and Education Fund",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.005946706778922728
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Human Rights Watch criticizes China's treatment of Uighur minority.",
    "span": "Human Rights Watch",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0028624543019999996
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Human Rights Watch criticizes China's treatment of Uighur minority.",
    "span": "China",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00747682644375
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Human Rights Watch criticizes China's treatment of Uighur minority.",
    "span": "Uighur",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.12312526800315667
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Human Rights Watch calls for investigation into alleged war crimes in Syria.",
    "span": "Human Rights Watch",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -9.988180533333334e-06
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Human Rights Watch calls for investigation into alleged war crimes in Syria.",
    "span": "Syria",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -8.300760725e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "European Union partners with Human Rights Watch to address refugee crisis.",
    "span": "European Union",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0038847575144800007
  },
  {
    "sentence": "European Union partners with Human Rights Watch to address refugee crisis.",
    "span": "Human Rights Watch",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0005053853723333333
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Twitter announces new feature to combat misinformation on its platform.",
    "span": "Twitter",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.000721293979
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tech giant Apple partners with Twitter to integrate new social media features on its devices.",
    "span": "Apple",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0002053545849
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tech giant Apple partners with Twitter to integrate new social media features on its devices.",
    "span": "Twitter",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -8.303007641e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Twitter CEO Jack Dorsey steps down, citing the need for new leadership to steer the company through challenging times.",
    "span": "Twitter",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00071919455215
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Twitter CEO Jack Dorsey steps down, citing the need for new leadership to steer the company through challenging times.",
    "span": "Jack Dorsey",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -2.4829037516666666e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Local volunteers rally to support Red Cross relief efforts after natural disaster.",
    "span": "Red Cross",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00507892661828
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Red Cross blood drive collects record donations in the local community.",
    "span": "Red Cross",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -3.318772156e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Local Red Cross chapter hosts emergency preparedness seminar for residents.",
    "span": "Red Cross",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00051330177218
  },
  {
    "sentence": "European Union leaders reach historic agreement on climate change goals.",
    "span": "European Union",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0034112561596
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Greece requests financial assistance from the European Union to address economic crisis.",
    "span": "Greece",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0011491067469600001
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Greece requests financial assistance from the European Union to address economic crisis.",
    "span": "European Union",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -2.2699264359999997e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Michael Phelps breaks Olympic record with his 23rd gold medal.",
    "span": "Michael Phelps",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.16324226763160002
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Major League Baseball announces new rule changes for the upcoming season.",
    "span": "Major League Baseball",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -4.3601778999999996e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Naomi Osaka advances to the semi-finals after a stunning victory in the quarter-finals.",
    "span": "Naomi Osaka",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -3.134427971666667e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Sony Pictures Entertainment announces partnership with Apple Music for exclusive film soundtracks.",
    "span": "Sony Pictures Entertainment",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -2.2901910383333338e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Sony Pictures Entertainment announces partnership with Apple Music for exclusive film soundtracks.",
    "span": "Apple Music",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0008611656579400001
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Pop star Taylor Swift signs multi-million dollar deal with Sony Pictures Entertainment for original content production.",
    "span": "Taylor Swift",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.00015804237868
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Pop star Taylor Swift signs multi-million dollar deal with Sony Pictures Entertainment for original content production.",
    "span": "Sony Pictures Entertainment",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00018643653631666667
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Actor Will Smith to star in upcoming blockbuster movie produced by Sony Pictures Entertainment in collaboration with Apple Music.",
    "span": "Will Smith",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -2.563167474e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Actor Will Smith to star in upcoming blockbuster movie produced by Sony Pictures Entertainment in collaboration with Apple Music.",
    "span": "Sony Pictures Entertainment",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -4.30613905e-06
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Actor Will Smith to star in upcoming blockbuster movie produced by Sony Pictures Entertainment in collaboration with Apple Music.",
    "span": "Apple Music",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -1.2948404479999999e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Ted Cruz calls for reforms to United Nations Security Council.",
    "span": "Ted Cruz",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -5.0235311199999997e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "United Nations Security Council debates new resolution proposed by Ted Cruz.",
    "span": "Ted Cruz",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.00040032335799999993
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Ted Cruz criticizes the United Nations Security Council's handling of recent conflicts.",
    "span": "Ted Cruz",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -1.065969454e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Ted Cruz criticizes the United Nations Security Council's handling of recent conflicts.",
    "span": "United Nations Security Council",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -2.1497009914285712e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Toyota Motor Corporation to open new assembly plant in Sydney.",
    "span": "Toyota Motor Corporation",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -3.8715041466666666e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Toyota Motor Corporation to open new assembly plant in Sydney.",
    "span": "Sydney",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.000468185908
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Bomb explosion in Baghdad kills at least 20 people.",
    "span": "Baghdad",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0010037491742166667
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Toyota Motor Corporation reports record-breaking quarterly sales.",
    "span": "Toyota Motor Corporation",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -9.531233016666666e-06
  },
  {
    "sentence": "LeBron James speaks out on police brutality, calling for accountability and change in partnership with the ACLU.",
    "span": "LeBron James",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -1.3941768666666668e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "LeBron James speaks out on police brutality, calling for accountability and change in partnership with the ACLU.",
    "span": "ACLU",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.001062555389025
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Local police department hosts annual community safety fair.",
    "span": "police department",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0011678365969
  },
  {
    "sentence": "New community center opens in downtown area, offering various programs for residents.",
    "span": "community center",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.08382673053346
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Local high school student receives scholarship for academic achievement.",
    "span": "high school student",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.017381954613233334
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Local family opens up their home to travelers through Airbnb, transforming their spare room into a cozy guest retreat.",
    "span": "Airbnb",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0004218254601
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Retired couple funds their global adventures by renting out their property on Airbnb when they're away, turning their travel dreams into a reality.",
    "span": "Airbnb",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -1.485566392e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Single mother creates a welcoming sanctuary for guests in her home through Airbnb, providing a personalized and affordable travel experience for visitors to the area.",
    "span": "Airbnb",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0007939449045199999
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The New York Public Library hosts a literary event featuring J.K. Rowling.",
    "span": "The New York Public Library",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00081383712915
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The New York Public Library hosts a literary event featuring J.K. Rowling.",
    "span": "J.K. Rowling",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.00015013481011
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Buenos Aires launches a campaign to promote reading and literacy among its citizens.",
    "span": "Buenos Aires",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.008284706819057143
  },
  {
    "sentence": "A new study reveals the impact of literature on mental health, conducted by researchers at The New York Public Library.",
    "span": "The New York Public Library",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -2.08009457625e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Starbucks plans to open 100 new stores in the next fiscal year in order to expand its market presence.",
    "span": "Starbucks",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0001193008282
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Congresswoman Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez proposed a new bill to regulate big tech companies and promote fair competition in the market.",
    "span": "Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.05534835124578583
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Christine Madeleine Odette Lagarde appointed as the new head of the International Labor Organization.",
    "span": "Christine Madeleine Odette Lagarde",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -2.456534375454545e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Christine Madeleine Odette Lagarde appointed as the new head of the International Labor Organization.",
    "span": "International Labor Organization",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0001405302595
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The International Labor Organization reports a significant decline in global unemployment rates for the first quarter of 2022.",
    "span": "International Labor Organization",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -7.530750766666667e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The World Health Organization concludes their investigation into the origins of the recent viral outbreak in Asia.",
    "span": "World Health Organization",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0006490240921666668
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The World Health Organization concludes their investigation into the origins of the recent viral outbreak in Asia.",
    "span": "Asia",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.000451954464075
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The pharmaceutical company Pfizer announces a breakthrough in the development of a potential HIV vaccine.",
    "span": "Pfizer",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0021513712288166666
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The pharmaceutical company Pfizer announces a breakthrough in the development of a potential HIV vaccine.",
    "span": "HIV",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.167952223099825
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Archaeologists uncover ancient artifacts believed to have belonged to Alexander the Great.",
    "span": "Alexander the Great",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.01209551283216667
  },
  {
    "sentence": "New documentary sheds light on the military tactics of Alexander the Great.",
    "span": "Alexander the Great",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -3.214019526666667e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "University researchers discover new insights into the life and legacy of Alexander the Great.",
    "span": "Alexander the Great",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0045601262248166664
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Goldman Sachs Group, Inc. wins prestigious award for corporate social responsibility.",
    "span": "Goldman Sachs Group, Inc.",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00016840595471000002
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Local entrepreneur credits Beyoncé for inspiring her to start successful business.",
    "span": "Beyoncé",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.00013880164111666665
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Small business owner shares how Goldman Sachs Group, Inc. mentorship program helped her company thrive.",
    "span": "Goldman Sachs Group, Inc.",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -2.8432961154e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Investigation reveals Rachel Kim listed as top frequent flyer in Southwest Airlines rewards program.",
    "span": "Rachel Kim",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -5.9627092399999995e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Investigation reveals Rachel Kim listed as top frequent flyer in Southwest Airlines rewards program.",
    "span": "Southwest Airlines",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0001890999008
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Travel industry insiders uncover Southwest Airlines as top choice for budget-conscious travelers.",
    "span": "Southwest Airlines",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -5.319339773333334e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Rachel Kim's travel tips and tricks make her a sought-after source for Southwest Airlines passengers.",
    "span": "Rachel Kim",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -6.606769860000001e-06
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Rachel Kim's travel tips and tricks make her a sought-after source for Southwest Airlines passengers.",
    "span": "Southwest Airlines",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -8.061054328000001e-06
  },
  {
    "sentence": "New York Fashion Week kicks off with a star-studded runway show.",
    "span": "New York Fashion Week",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.023399109868857144
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Celebrity chef opens a new luxury restaurant in downtown Los Angeles.",
    "span": "Los Angeles",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.006986779974
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Renowned interior designer to launch a new line of home decor products.",
    "span": "interior designer",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.009479013574066665
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Coca-Cola launches new marketing campaign to commemorate its 100-year history.",
    "span": "Coca-Cola",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00020911242571666668
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The World Trade Organization celebrates its 25th anniversary with a series of global events.",
    "span": "World Trade Organization",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -5.7051926000000006e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Karl Lagerfeld appointed as the new creative director of luxury fashion brand Chanel.",
    "span": "Karl Lagerfeld",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -4.212478991428571e-06
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Karl Lagerfeld appointed as the new creative director of luxury fashion brand Chanel.",
    "span": "Chanel",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -5.067269296e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Designer Karl Lagerfeld launches new fragrance line in collaboration with renowned beauty brand.",
    "span": "Karl Lagerfeld",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.00012488040398571428
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Experts from The Intergovernmental Panel on Climate Change warn that rising global temperatures are leading to unpredictable and severe weather patterns, posing a threat to vulnerable regions and populations.",
    "span": "The Intergovernmental Panel on Climate Change",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -1.5888151119166667e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The Intergovernmental Panel on Climate Change's latest findings reveal the detrimental effects of climate change on weather systems, prompting calls for urgent action to mitigate the risks posed to societies and ecosystems.",
    "span": "The Intergovernmental Panel on Climate Change",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -7.465036252500001e-06
  },
  {
    "sentence": "UNESCO launches new initiative to improve access to quality education in developing countries.",
    "span": "UNESCO",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00026836853876
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Local university partners with UNESCO to promote cultural diversity in higher education.",
    "span": "UNESCO",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -3.1663380459999996e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Education minister meets with UNESCO representatives to discuss funding for educational infrastructure projects.",
    "span": "education minister",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.010213029133730001
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Education minister meets with UNESCO representatives to discuss funding for educational infrastructure projects.",
    "span": "UNESCO",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.03217755345682
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Harvard University announces new scholarship program for low-income students.",
    "span": "Harvard University",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0015488747433333335
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Renowned educator Dr. Jane Smith appointed as the new president of Yale University.",
    "span": "Dr. Jane Smith",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0014398787170857143
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Renowned educator Dr. Jane Smith appointed as the new president of Yale University.",
    "span": "Yale University",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -8.93484143e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "High school graduation rates in the United States reach an all-time high.",
    "span": "United States",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00036869216360000003
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Google invests $1 billion in renewable energy projects.",
    "span": "Google",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.001081506344425
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Tech giant Google acquires AI startup for undisclosed sum.",
    "span": "Google",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -1.9236397275e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Google faces antitrust investigation from European Union.",
    "span": "Google",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0018370280689999998
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Google faces antitrust investigation from European Union.",
    "span": "European Union",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.000133181991
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Samantha Nguyen elected as the new mayor of London, England.",
    "span": "Samantha Nguyen",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0007403864697571428
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Samantha Nguyen elected as the new mayor of London, England.",
    "span": "London",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.002173748703
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Samantha Nguyen elected as the new mayor of London, England.",
    "span": "England",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00083843651955
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Google announces plans to open a new office in London, bringing hundreds of jobs to the city.",
    "span": "Google",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -1.5511283999999998e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Google announces plans to open a new office in London, bringing hundreds of jobs to the city.",
    "span": "London",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -3.85455581e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Local business owner Samantha Nguyen partners with Google to provide free digital skills training in London, England.",
    "span": "Samantha Nguyen",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -2.5124207328571427e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Local business owner Samantha Nguyen partners with Google to provide free digital skills training in London, England.",
    "span": "Google",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -1.02663224e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Local business owner Samantha Nguyen partners with Google to provide free digital skills training in London, England.",
    "span": "London",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -7.822647075e-06
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Local business owner Samantha Nguyen partners with Google to provide free digital skills training in London, England.",
    "span": "England",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00021888422692499998
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Russian scientists conduct study on the ecological impact of tourism on Lake Baikal.",
    "span": "Russian",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.09731762672949999
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Russian scientists conduct study on the ecological impact of tourism on Lake Baikal.",
    "span": "Lake Baikal",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.07199937626
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Chinese government invests in projects to protect the ecosystem of Lake Baikal.",
    "span": "Chinese",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -6.018728991666666e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Chinese government invests in projects to protect the ecosystem of Lake Baikal.",
    "span": "Lake Baikal",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.1887039936725
  },
  {
    "sentence": "International team of researchers discover new species of freshwater fish in Lake Baikal.",
    "span": "Lake Baikal",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0424014003068
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Rihanna's new album reached the top spot on the charts.",
    "span": "Rihanna",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.00050096287506
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The highly anticipated concert tour featuring Rihanna and Beyoncé has been postponed.",
    "span": "Rihanna",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -4.9971597480000005e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The highly anticipated concert tour featuring Rihanna and Beyoncé has been postponed.",
    "span": "Beyoncé",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -9.926835950000001e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Rihanna launches her own beauty and fashion line.",
    "span": "Rihanna",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -4.015068233e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Famous painter Julian Rivera unveils new exhibit at the Metropolitan Museum of Art.",
    "span": "Julian Rivera",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -4.2350755083333336e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Renowned sculptor Maria Sanchez to receive prestigious award for lifetime achievement in the arts.",
    "span": "Maria Sanchez",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.00012120515174
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Local art gallery to host charity auction featuring works by internationally acclaimed artist David Lee.",
    "span": "David Lee",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.00017038343504000003
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Adidas launches a new sustainable clothing line to reduce environmental impact.",
    "span": "Adidas",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00047599688692
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Zara to open flagship store in New York City's Times Square.",
    "span": "Zara",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -6.2729994399999996e-06
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Zara to open flagship store in New York City's Times Square.",
    "span": "New York City",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.056634120560833334
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Zara to open flagship store in New York City's Times Square.",
    "span": "Times Square",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0032561853958
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Fashion designer Stella McCartney partners with Adidas for a new vegan footwear collection.",
    "span": "Stella McCartney",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.00025839093566666665
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Fashion designer Stella McCartney partners with Adidas for a new vegan footwear collection.",
    "span": "Adidas",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -1.4825862162499999e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "John Peterson helps raise $10,000 for local animal shelter.",
    "span": "John Peterson",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0088732099426
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Local community rallies around John Peterson after devastating house fire.",
    "span": "John Peterson",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -1.790727674e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "John Peterson organizes charity marathon to support children's hospital.",
    "span": "John Peterson",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.00558594994192
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Leonardo DiCaprio to star in upcoming Martin Scorsese film.",
    "span": "Leonardo DiCaprio",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.00010739622608125
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Leonardo DiCaprio to star in upcoming Martin Scorsese film.",
    "span": "Martin Scorsese",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0014403596838428571
  },
  {
    "sentence": "New film production studio opens in Los Angeles, aiming to attract top Hollywood talent such as Leonardo DiCaprio.",
    "span": "Los Angeles",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.00016098286379999998
  },
  {
    "sentence": "New film production studio opens in Los Angeles, aiming to attract top Hollywood talent such as Leonardo DiCaprio.",
    "span": "Leonardo DiCaprio",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0016540738554357143
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Netflix announces collaboration with Leonardo DiCaprio's production company for new environmental documentary film.",
    "span": "Netflix",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -8.463748550000001e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Netflix announces collaboration with Leonardo DiCaprio's production company for new environmental documentary film.",
    "span": "Leonardo DiCaprio",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -4.101235328571428e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Professor David Johnson from Buenos Aires, Argentina, receives prestigious award from the National Society for the Gifted and Talented.",
    "span": "Professor David Johnson",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0659170588396
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Professor David Johnson from Buenos Aires, Argentina, receives prestigious award from the National Society for the Gifted and Talented.",
    "span": "Buenos Aires",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0063229943515
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Professor David Johnson from Buenos Aires, Argentina, receives prestigious award from the National Society for the Gifted and Talented.",
    "span": "Argentina",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -3.712688116666667e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Professor David Johnson from Buenos Aires, Argentina, receives prestigious award from the National Society for the Gifted and Talented.",
    "span": "National Society for the Gifted and Talented",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0002107026131358333
  },
  {
    "sentence": "New educational program in Buenos Aires, Argentina, aims to support gifted students in collaboration with Professor David Johnson.",
    "span": "Buenos Aires",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -8.82736347857143e-06
  },
  {
    "sentence": "New educational program in Buenos Aires, Argentina, aims to support gifted students in collaboration with Professor David Johnson.",
    "span": "Argentina",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -1.34848219e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "New educational program in Buenos Aires, Argentina, aims to support gifted students in collaboration with Professor David Johnson.",
    "span": "Professor David Johnson",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -6.00656395e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "National Society for the Gifted and Talented appoints international education expert, Professor David Johnson, as honorary advisory board member.",
    "span": "National Society for the Gifted and Talented",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0009109104619333332
  },
  {
    "sentence": "National Society for the Gifted and Talented appoints international education expert, Professor David Johnson, as honorary advisory board member.",
    "span": "Professor David Johnson",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -1.64450451025e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Beyoncé to launch new fashion line in collaboration with Adidas.",
    "span": "Beyoncé",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.000143239239055
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Beyoncé to launch new fashion line in collaboration with Adidas.",
    "span": "Adidas",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.000176060752
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Louis Vuitton store in Shanghai to host exclusive fashion show for international designers.",
    "span": "Louis Vuitton",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00196808755369
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Louis Vuitton store in Shanghai to host exclusive fashion show for international designers.",
    "span": "Shanghai",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0016857586791750002
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Fashion industry leaders discuss sustainability goals at annual conference in Paris.",
    "span": "Paris",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -7.2876213625e-05
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Dr. Drew Pinsky warns about the dangers of excessive screen time for children during the pandemic.",
    "span": "Dr. Drew Pinsky",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.00023383353255
  },
  {
    "sentence": "New study from the CDC shows a significant increase in obesity rates among young adults in the United States.",
    "span": "CDC",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.00049544599
  },
  {
    "sentence": "New study from the CDC shows a significant increase in obesity rates among young adults in the United States.",
    "span": "United States",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0001386499562
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Dr. Drew Pinsky advocates for improved mental health resources for healthcare workers on the front lines of the COVID-19 crisis.",
    "span": "Dr. Drew Pinsky",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.356089367908925
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Travel expert John Smith recommends a visit to the historic city of Rome for its rich culture and iconic landmarks.",
    "span": "John Smith",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.00038923635239999997
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Travel expert John Smith recommends a visit to the historic city of Rome for its rich culture and iconic landmarks.",
    "span": "Rome",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0004150256575
  },
  {
    "sentence": "According to the spokesperson for the airline company, new direct flights to Bali will be launched next month to meet the increasing demand for travel to the popular destination.",
    "span": "Bali",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.0030050271167999998
  },
  {
    "sentence": "CEO of the tourism board, Lisa Johnson, shares her insights on the impact of the pandemic on the travel industry and the strategies for recovery.",
    "span": "Lisa Johnson",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.0006578687725300001
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Two suspects arrested in connection with the bank robbery in downtown Chicago.",
    "span": "suspects",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.17187226087732
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Two suspects arrested in connection with the bank robbery in downtown Chicago.",
    "span": "bank",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.49936271350775
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Police detective reveals new evidence in the murder case of a local businessman.",
    "span": "detective",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.22575841147390002
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Police detective reveals new evidence in the murder case of a local businessman.",
    "span": "businessman",
    "entity_type": "person",
    "average_logprob": -0.007029307456749999
  },
  {
    "sentence": "Gang-related shooting leaves three injured in the Bronx.",
    "span": "Bronx",
    "entity_type": "location",
    "average_logprob": -0.15370899068886001
  },
  {
    "sentence": "The World Bank predicts a significant decrease in agricultural productivity due to the extreme weather conditions in the coming months.",
    "span": "World Bank",
    "entity_type": "organization",
    "average_logprob": -0.0015085832564
  },
  {
